Chapter 1000: A Trap

All of a sudden, a streak of white light flew into the array, protected by a burst of spatial law powers, before striking Han Li on the body.

Han Li was very startled by this, and he only had time to look down to discover that it was a marking jade pendant before a burst of tremendous tearing force converged toward him from all directions.

The air around him constricted, and he felt as if his body were about to be torn apart at the seams. Even his enormous spiritual sense had become rather scattered, making it impossible for him to focus his attention.

A resounding boom rang out, and the entire Space Passage Pagoda shuddered violently as a streak of silver light erupted into the heavens from the tip of the pagoda.

At the same time, a burst of silver light erupted out of the rhomboid crystals embedded into the outer walls of the pagoda before sweeping through the air in all directions.

All of the silver light lingered for a few seconds before abruptly fading away, and most of the rhomboid crystals on the outer wall of the pagoda had been ruined, while the rest had become completely dull and devoid of luster, indicating that they had been almost entirely drained of energy.

Moments later, Shi Pokong emerged from the pagoda with his entourage, and his brows were still tightly furrowed in contemplation, but he was looking a bit more relaxed than before.

......

There was an antiquated daoist temple that was surrounded by lush mountains somewhere in the Immortal Realm.

The temple had been constructed along the mountain, and it stretched for dozens of kilometers.

In a small col near the temple was a white stone array that was no more than a thousand feet in radius, and it was surrounded by stone pillars that were riddled with dense clusters of runes.

At this moment, there were close to a hundred cultivators dressed in two types of different attire gathered around the array, and all of them were looking on with solemn expressions.

The group seemed to have two leaders, one of whom was a white-robed middle-aged man who wasn't particularly tall or imposing, but was giving off a vast and authoritative aura.

He was accompanied by a tall and thin elderly man with sunken cheeks and withered skin, giving him a very wizened appearance.

"Where did you get this information from, Brother Tao Ji? Is that man really going to be appearing here today?" the elderly man suddenly asked.

"I'll admit that I can't be certain, Fellow Daoist Jin Chuan. I received an interrealm message last night, claiming that the culprit who killed Yu'er will be appearing on this Returning Dragon Temple teleportation platform today. There wasn't enough time for me to verify the message, and I came here with all of the people that I could gather. I knew that you were nearby, so I decided to ask for your help as well," the man by the name of Tao Ji replied.

"It's fine. If I recall correctly, Yu'er's killer was only a mere True Immortal. Was there really a need to gather so many people just to have him killed?" Jin Chuan asked.

"The message claimed that Yu'er's killer has become far more powerful than he was back then, and that I should regard him as a High Zenith cultivator," Tao Ji replied in a hesitant manner.

"How is that possible? There's no way anyone could possibly go from the True Immortal Stage to the High Zenith Stage in such a short time! If you ask me, this is most likely a trap. You've made a lot of enemies over the years, so you have to be on your guard," Jin Chuan said in a disbelieving manner.

"That may be the case, but I don't want to pass up any opportunity of hunting down Yu'er's killer, no matter how slim. Besides, even if this is a trap, I have you to help me, so what do I have to fear?" Tao Ji replied.

"I suppose that's true. I'd say this lineup that you've assembled would be enough to give even a Great Encompassment cultivator a huge headache," Jin Chuan chuckled.

"I was only able to assemble five peak-Golden Immortal cultivators and fewer than fifty cultivators of the mid and late-Golden Immortal Stages, so if it wasn't for the people that you had brought with you, there's no way I would be able to unleash the full power of this Bipolar Yin Yang Array," Tao Ji said.

"You mentioned that this man is cultivating the laws of time, right? It sounds like he has a real death wish," Jin Chuan harrumphed coldly.

"He's most likely just some hillbilly that stumbled onto this path without knowing secrets involved. Having said that, the fact that he was able to kill Yu'er as a mere True Immortal and also kill Gongshu Jiu after that indicates that he must've made some decent strides in his cultivation of time law powers," Tao Ji mused.

"So what? As soon as he enters this Bipolar Yin Yang Array, he'll be completely at our mercy. Rest assured, as long as he shows up today, there's no way he'll be leaving this place alive," Jin Chuan said with a cold smile.

Tao Ji's tense expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he was just about to say something when his expression suddenly changed slightly.

"Here he comes!" Jin Chuan said as his eyes lit up with excitement.

As soon as his voice trailed off, all of the nearby clouds abruptly began to churn violently before converging over the col to conceal the entire sky.

"Set up the array!" Tao Ji commanded in a serious manner, and the nine peak-Golden Immortal cultivators present gave a collective affirmative response, then positioned themselves evenly around the teleportation platform with nine cultivators of the mid and late-Golden Immortal Stages behind each of them.

Together, the ninety cultivators made a string of hand seals while chanting an incantation, and countless array patterns on the ground and the surrounding stone pillars lit up, releasing a layer of black and white light that folded inward from all directions like a giant pocket.

All of a sudden, there was a flash of lightning in the dark clouds above, following which a burst of incredibly powerful spatial fluctuations erupted forth, and a pillar of silver light came crashing down from above.

The teleportation platform shuddered violently, and Han Li appeared at the base of the pillar of silver light.

In the instant that he appeared, the vast pocket of black and white light instantly closed itself over the teleportation platform.

Immense spatial tearing force was generated during interrealm teleportations, so if anyone below the High Zenith Stage were to attempt teleportation over such a vast distance, there was a very good chance that they would be torn apart and killed on the spot.

Han Li's tremendous physical constitution ensured that he remained unscathed, but even so, he was feeling very light-headed, and his entire body was throbbing with pain, making it difficult just to remain standing.

The light-headed sensation was quickly quelled by his Spirit Refinement Technique, while a small jade pendant fell down by his feet with a faint crack.

He bent down to pick up the jade pendant, then looked around to discover that half of the people around the teleportation platform were dressed in Immortal Palace robes, and he couldn't help but heave a faint sigh.

You sure are persistent, Shi Pokong...

From Jin Chuan's perspective, Han Li was very unremarkable in appearance, and a hesitant look appeared on his face as he asked, "Is that him?"

"It certainly is," Tao Ji replied as he glowered intently at Han Li.

Even though he had never seen Han Li before, for some reason, from the instant that he laid eyes upon him, his intuition told him that this was undoubtedly the man who had killed his son.

"Should I call you Li Feiyu or Han Li?" Tao Ji asked in a cold voice.

"Have we met before?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"No, but you've met my son, Tao Yu. Not only that, you also killed him!" Tao Ji replied in a cold voice.

Only upon hearing this did it occur to Han Li that this middle-aged man bore some resemblance to Tao Yu, and a look of realization appeared in his eyes.

"It's time for you to finally pay for what you've done! Activate the array!" Tao Ji commanded, and as soon as the order was issued, the teleportation platform shuddered, following which all of the surrounding air constricted around Han Li.

His brows furrowed slightly as he discovered that all of the world's origin qi in the surrounding area had suddenly vanished without a trace, and it was as if he had returned to the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

A smile of amusement and exasperation appeared on Han Li's face at this thought.

Tao Ji's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of Han Li's unfazed reaction, and he commanded, "Activate the Bipolar Yin Yang Stones!"

All of the Golden Immortal cultivators immediately switched to a different hand seal upon hearing this, and a series of circles of strange runes appeared around the array, causing the black and white light in the array to separate down the middle.

The white light went to the left, while the black light went to the right, and they gradually took on a substantial form, transforming into a pair of enormous millstones, one black and one white, both of which were revolving rapidly as they compressed toward the center.

Han Li was standing between the pair of millstones, and he could feel tremendous pressure sweeping toward him from both sides, locking him firmly into place and completely immobilizing him.

Chapter 1001: Is That All You've Got?

Bursts of powerful tearing force swept through the air on either side of Han Li, sweeping up gusts of ferocious wind that lashed against his cheeks.

Being subjected to such immense pressure was far from comfortable, and Han Li reflexively extended his elbows outward to either side, but he was only able to slightly dispel the pressure, while the two millstones continued to close in on him.

It seemed that Han Li was completely powerless to resist, and a pleased smile appeared on Tao Ji's face upon seeing this.

In contrast, Jin Chuan was looking on with an unconvinced expression, clearly under the opinion that this was massive overkill.

"Keep it up, everyone! Destroy this scoundrel's physical body, but make sure to leave his soul behind. I'm going to use it to light a sky lantern to comfort my son's soul in the heavens!" Tao Ji yelled.

The ninety Golden Immortals behind him immediately gave a collective affirmative response.

They were extremely fortunate to have been chosen to be part of this array, and this experience was going to have unfathomable benefits on their future cultivation, not to mention the reward of ten Immortal Origin Stones that each of them was going to receive. On top of that, their target appeared to be a complete pushover, and they could hardly think of a better job to be assigned.

With that in mind, all of them were pouring forth their immortal spiritual power without reservation to power the array.

The runes on the two millstones were glowing radiantly, and the pressure emanating from them was becoming stronger and stronger, causing Han Li's joints to creak and groan audibly, but he still appeared quite calm and composed.

This was a perfect opportunity for him to gauge just how powerful his own physical body had become after his time in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so he was slowly acclimating himself to the pressure exerted upon him by the millstones without putting up any meaningful resistance.

Of course, he was still putting on an act to humor Tao Ji, feigning an agonized expression, as if he really were struggling to withstand the pressure.

Before long, the two millstones had drawn so close to each other that it seemed like they were in direct contact, and it was no longer possible to see Han Li between them.

"Looks like you were misled, Brother Tao. At this rate, he's going to be crushed in just a moment or two. You should prepare to capture his soul. Otherwise, if they go too far, his soul could be destroyed too," Jin Chuan said with a smile.

"I can't believe Yu'er was killed by such an incompetent scoundrel! He must've been too complacent and underestimated his opponent. It's my fault for being too lenient with him," Tao Ji sighed as he shook his head with a remorseful expression.

"I wouldn't put the blame on Yu'er. The only reason why this scoundrel is completely powerless to retaliate is because we set up this Bipolar Yin Yang Array in advance, so this is not a true reflection of his power," Jin Chuan consoled.

"No matter. Yu'er has finally been avenged now," Tao Ji sighed, and it was as if a heavy load had been lifted from his shoulders.

Right at this moment, a strange sound suddenly rang out from between the two millstones, and the two of them hurriedly peered into the array, upon which they were stunned to discover that a small gap had reappeared between the pair of millstones.

At the same time, Han Li's mocking voice rang out from within the array.

"Is that all you've got? I must say, I'm very disappointed."

Tao Ji and Jin Chuan's expressions changed drastically upon hearing this, and the former hurriedly yelled, "Crush him!"

All of the Golden Immortals immediately redoubled their efforts, pouring forth more immortal spiritual power into the Bipolar Yin Yang Array.

However, even though the two millstones were glowing brighter than ever and releasing even more formidable pressure, they were still slowly being forced apart bit by bit.

The feigned look of agony on Han Li's face had faded away, and it was replaced by a calm and composed expression.

A stunned look appeared on Tao Ji's face upon seeing this, and he hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a golden flying sword that suspended itself in mid-air before him.

Etched onto the blade of the sword were nine flame symbols next to each other, and it was giving off bursts of scorching heat.

He slid a finger over the sword, and the first fire symbol lit up to release a layer of crimson fire, forming a serrated, fiery edge around the sword.

Tao Ji took a glance at Han Li, then slid his finger over the second flame symbol, which also lit up to release a layer of orange flames over its crimson counterpart.

With the emergence of this layer of flames, the surrounding temperature soared, and the nearby air began to shimmer and warp.

Tao Ji continued to glide his finger over the length of the sword, and the fire symbols on it lit up one after another, with each one producing a new layer of flames.

Each layer of fire was a different color from the rest, and before long, seven layers of flame had appeared over the flying sword, making it resemble a fiery, rainbow fan.

Waves of scorching heat were sweeping through the entire col, setting all of the surrounding vegetation alight, and even the Golden Immortals inside the array were struggling to withstand the heat, feeling as if their blood were boiling in their veins.

"He does seem to possess remarkable physical prowess, but surely you didn't need to use seven Radiant Flame Symbols at once!" Jin Chuan exclaimed with a surprised expression.

Tao Ji offered no response as he thrust both palms forward, and the fiery flying sword hurtled directly into the Bipolar Yin Yang Array as a streak of rainbow light.

Han Li was completely unfazed by the formidable fire law power fluctuations emanating from the sword. In fact, he was eager to use it to test out his own newfound physical prowess.

With that in mind, Han Li channeled the starpower within his own body, meeting the oncoming flying sword directly with his own chest.

A resounding boom rang out as the tip of the rainbow flying sword struck his chest, releasing bursts of scorching heat that instantly incinerated his robes, but the sword wasn't able to pierce even a millimeter into his body.

Blinding rainbow light erupted throughout the entire array to inundate Han Li, and bursts of rainbow flames erupted in all directions, causing the array to tremble violently.

All of the Golden Immortals outside the array began swaying unsteadily, and moments later, the flames faded away to reveal Han Li again.

The clothes in front of his chest had been burned away, but he was completely unscathed, and there wasn't even a single scorch mark on his body.

"Impossible!" Jin Chuan exclaimed with an astonished expression.

"His physical body is far more powerful than we imagined! Be on your guard, Brother Jin Chuan," Tao Ji warned with tightly furrowed brows as he summoned his flying sword back to yourself.

"If that's all you've got, then it's my turn!" Han Li declared with a cold smile, then immediately channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, and profound acupoints lit up all over his body as he plunged his fingers straight into the black and white millstones with ease.

Immediately thereafter, he channeled his Giant Mountain Ape bloodline, and his muscles bulged as tufts of golden fur appeared over his body, transforming into a giant golden ape that was around a hundred feet tall in the blink of an eye.

He then tugged violently on the pair of giant millstones, and they were instantly wrenched into his grasp, causing the entire array to tremble violently.

All of the Golden Immortals that were manning the array were immediately struck by backlash, shuddering violently while throwing up large mouthfuls of blood.

"Get back!" Tao Ji hurriedly yelled in a frantic voice, but it was already too late.

As Han Li seized control of the two millstones, a burst of tremendous, compressive force swept through the entire array, trapping all of the Golden Immortals inside.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li hurled both of the millstones at the Golden Immortals, who were unable to take any evasive measures, so they could only frantically summon their protective treasures with horrified looks on their faces as they struggled in futility to save themselves.

Two earth-shattering booms rang out as the pair of giant millstones came crashing down, easily overwhelming the resistance put up by the Golden Immortals, and not a single one of them was able to escape.

All of them had been crushed into mincemeat, and even their nascent souls had been eradicated.

"How dare you!" Jin Chuan roared in a furious voice as he sprang up into the sky before making a hand seal, and a blue spirit domain instantly appeared over the entire col.

"So one of you is cultivating the laws of fire, while the other is cultivating the laws of water. You two certainly complement each other well," Han Li remarked with a smile as dense clouds of steam suddenly began to rise up around him.

He quickly reverted back to his normal human form as he spoke, while Jin Chuan continued to make a string of hand seals, releasing a tremendous aura that caused his robes to flap audibly around him.

Chapter 1002: Crushed with Ease

With a sweep of Jin Chuan's sleeve, a torrential downpour suddenly began to cascade down from the heavens, instantly filling the entire area within a radius of ten thousand feet around Han Li.

There was faint azure and purple light shimmering within the otherwise innocuous-looking rain droplets, indicating to Han Li that they were tinged with poison.

With that in mind, he threw a punch upward, and a burst of white starlight erupted out of his fist, forming a starlight barrier that eradicated all of the rain falling from above.

Immediately thereafter, he prepared to spring up into the air, only to discover that his feet had become firmly rooted to the ground.

A puddle of azure water had appeared beneath his feet, and it had wrapped itself tightly around his legs, locking him firmly into place.

The puddle of water was giving off a jade-like gleam, and circles of strange patterns could be seen within it, giving off tremendous water law power fluctuations.

Han Li attempted to lift his own legs, only to discover that they had become incredibly heavy, as if they had become one with the land.

"Save your energy," Jin Chuan sneered with a triumphant expression. "I've connected my Water Binding Technique to the underground water veins in this entire area, so you're currently being bogged down by the weight of countless underwater rivers..."

All of a sudden, Jin Chuan's voice abruptly trailed off as the triumph on his face turned to shock and horror.

As it turned out, all of Han Li's close to a thousand profound acupoints had lit up as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might, allowing him to free himself from Jin Chuan's Water Binding Technique with ease.

Immediately thereafter, he vanished from the spot before abruptly reappearing before Jin Chuan an instant later while throwing an almighty punch.

Despite his astonishment, Jin Chuan reacted very quickly, and a rippling light erupted out of his chest, forming an azure light barrier that rippled like water.

Han Li's fist struck the azure light barrier, and he was instantly struck by the false sensation that his fist had missed its target. The tremendous force behind his punch was completely deflated, and he was unable to make contact with Jin Chuan's chest.

"Hurry, Brother Tao!" Jin Chuan yelled in a frantic manner, and as soon as his voice trailed off, Tao Ji abruptly appeared no more than a thousand feet behind Han Li.

His entire body was shrouded in crimson flames, and he was making a hand seal as he let loose a thunderous roar.

All nine of the flame symbols on his golden flying sword li up, adding two more layers of fire to the previous seven, one black and one white.

Even though it was only two additional layers of flames, their emergence caused the aura of the flying sword to swell by severalfold, making it comparable in power to a fifth-grade immortal treasure.

The flying sword shot forth through the air, reaching Han Li in the blink of an eye, but almost at the exact same moment, Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him, revolving incessantly as it released rays of golden light in all directions.

As soon as the blazing sword pierced into the rays of golden light, it was slowed down drastically, to the point that it had almost stopped entirely.

The sword was trembling incessantly as the nine-colored flames around it incinerated the surrounding rays of golden light, but it was still only able to continue onward at a snail's pace.

Tao Ji was certain that this would prove to be the decisive blow, and he was completely rooted to the spot upon seeing this.

As for Jin Chuan, he had also been caught within the golden light, causing his spiritual sense to almost entirely congeal, so he was still yet to react to what was unfolding before him.

"How pathetic. You two have truly disappointed me," Han Li sighed as he channeled his true spirit bloodlines, and a burst of crimson light rose up from his body as he instantly transformed into a devilish deity with three heads and six arms.

Out of his three heads, one was that of the golden ape, another belonged to a mighty dragon, and the final one was a giant bird head with a pair of golden pupils. This was one of the forms that he could attain by using his true spirit bloodlines alongside his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

After adopting this form, Han Li's fist was still sealed within the rippling azure light barrier, but he simply reached out with one of his other five hands, which pierced through the light barrier with ease before plunging into Jin Chuan's chest to gouge out his heart.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li crushed the heart in his grasp.

Jin Chuan was still trapped by Han Li's time law powers, and the nascent soul in his dantian didn't even get a chance to escape before it was eradicated by another punch from Han Li.

At the same time, Han Li swiveled around before reaching out with two of his hands to grab onto the golden flying sword that had been arduously trudging its way toward him this entire time.

A burst of incredibly intense heat surged into his body through his hands, and his blood was almost set alight in a similar sensation to what he had previously experienced from his true spirit bloodline backlash.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face as he grabbed onto the blade of the sword, disregarding the scorching heat that it was releasing as he began twisting the sword with his hands.

The sword struggled with all its might, trying to break free, but it was all in futility.

The power generated by the combination of Han Li's true spirit bloodlines and Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts was far too much for the flying sword to contend with, and a metallic screeching sound rang out as it gradually began to twist and warp, following which it exploded into pieces with a resounding boom.

Waves of scorching heat erupted in all directions as Han Li's hands were charred black, and the acrid smell of burnt flesh was wafting through the air.

However, Han Li paid no heed to this as he reverted back to his human form before turning to Tao Ji with a derisive sneer.

In the instant that the flying sword was shattered, Tao Ji had thrown up a large mouthful of blood before fleeing for his life as a long streak of crimson fire.

However, Han Li's time spirit domain had already encompassed the entire surrounding area in a radius of several dozen kilometers, and even though the time-slowing effect of the spirit domain wasn't as potent as that of the Mantra Treasured Axis, it still greatly hampered Tao Ji's speed.

"It's too late to run away now!" Han Li sneered as he withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis into his body, following which it began to revolve in reverse at his behest.

At the same time, he stomped a foot heavily down onto the ground, launching himself through the air as an arc of silver lightning.

As soon as Han Li vanished from the spot, Tao Ji discovered that he was no longer able to determine Han Li's exact location, even with his spiritual sense, and a look of shock and horror appeared on his face.

He hurriedly made a hand seal, unleashing a blood-incinerating secret technique that enhanced his speed by twofold as he continued to flee into the distance.

Right at this moment, an arc of silver lightning appeared beside him, following which Han Li's voice rang out.

"Where are you going, Elder Tao? Weren't you going to crush me before making my soul into a sky lantern?"

Tao Ji continued fleeing in a blind panic, but Han Li seemed to be intentionally toying with him, merely keeping up with his speed while refraining from attacking.

"If Tao Yu hadn't tried to kill me in the Immortal Realm, none of this would've happened to you or him. You only have yourself to blame for not raising your son properly."

Tao Ji had already enhanced his own speed to the very limit, but he was still unable to get away.

"You should be thankful that I'm not like you, and I don't have a habit of refining the souls of others into lanterns. Instead, I only refined his soul into a Golden Soul Pill," Han Li continued.

"You bastard!"

Tao Ji was finally unable to stand Han Li's taunting any longer, and he stopped cold in his tracks, following which a fiery spirit domain erupted out of his body, but only encompassed an area with an approximate radius of a thousand feet, within which the air temperature was rapidly rising.

At the same time, a burst of red light emerged from his dantian, and cracks that looked as if they were filled with molten lava appeared over his skin as an incredibly formidable aura erupted out of his body.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as waves of scorching fire law powers swept through the air in all directions, causing the surrounding space to warp and twist with their incredible heat.

Han Li had already retreated far into the distance at this point, but at the same time, he was peering intently into the epicenter of the explosion with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

After a moment of observation, a cold sneer appeared on his face as he scoffed, "Do you really think that's going to work?"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he immediately flew directly into the explosion, and as he did so, he discovered that the fire law power fluctuations around him were very weak, far weaker than what should've been unleashed from a true self-detonation.

Immediately thereafter, he spotted several hundred fist-sized balls of fire up ahead, but instead of scattering like normal flames, they collectively sped away in a certain direction while converging to fuse together again.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph as he swept a sleeve through the air, letting loose eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that released a vast net of golden lightning.

The net of lightning encompassed all of the fist-sized fireballs, causing them to explode into countless tiny specks of fire.

All of the flying swords then flew back to Han Li at his behest, and hanging from one of them was a storage ring.

"If you're going to fake a self-detonation to serve as a decoy for your escape, then at least destroy your storage treasure as well. If you're not willing to even make that sacrifice, how are you going to convince anyone?" Han Li scoffed as he plucked the storage ring from the flying sword.

He then stowed the storage ring away before flying back to the col from before.

A long time after his departure, a speck of light emerged from an ancient tree in the forest down below, then rose up into the air before vanishing into the distance.

Chapter 1003: Creation Crystals

There was a dimly lit palace in the Golden Origin Immortal Palace with crimson patterns etched all over its walls and floor, forming a giant array.

These array patterns were flashing incessantly while giving off a cold aura drifted throughout the entire palace.

At the center of the array stood a black stone pillar with seven branches, at the top of each of which was an antiquated oil lamp with a green flame burning inside.

Not only did the green flames not provide a sense of illumination and comfort, they only made the palace appear more eerie and sinister.

All of a sudden, the green flames within the lamps swelled to several times their original size, then flew out of their respective lamps to hover in mid-air.

A series of green array patterns appeared in the surrounding space, connecting the seven flames to form a heptagram.

A soul fragment then appeared at the center of the array amid a flash of black light, forming an indistinct face that belonged to none other than Tao Ji.

"Thank heavens I set up these Seven Star Lamps in advance. Otherwise, I would truly be dead right now," Tao Ji murmured to himself, following which a look of burning resentment surfaced in his eyes.

"Han Li, you killed my son and ruined my cultivation base! I'm going to make you pay for everything! I may not be able to kill you, but I'll ensure that you die by someone else's hand at all costs!"

Tao Ji's soul fragment then opened its mouth, and the nine green flames within the array quickly flew into its mouth, giving it a more substantial form.

At the same time, a faint crack rang out as a hole that was around a foot in size appeared at the base of the black stone pillar, following which a humanoid talisman flew out from within before fusing as one with the soul fragment.

The combination of the two formed a black, humanoid body that looked as if it were entirely composed of ink.

Tao Ji moved around a little, testing out his own new body, then gave a pleased nod before flying outside.

Close to an hour later, Tao Yu arrived at a golden palace.

"Elder Tao!"

There was a servant standing on each side of the palace gate, and both of them were quite surprised to see Tao Ji in his current state.

"I have an urgent matter to report to the palace master," Tao Ji declared.

"Please wait a moment while we report your arrival, Elder Tao," one of the servants replied before turning to enter the palace.

Right at this moment, an authoritative voice rang out from within the palace.

"There's no need for that. Come in, Elder Tao."

Tao Ji immediately entered the palace, then passed through a giant hall and a corridor that was several thousand feet long, upon which a huge garden appeared before him.

There were all types of flowers and plants of different vibrant colors planted in the garden, culminating in an indescribable aroma.

At the center of the garden was a white pergola, inside of which stood a white-robed figure, who was observing a red floral tree outside the pergola.

The white-robed figure turned around, revealing himself to be a middle-aged man, and he asked, "What could be so urgent that you've used a Heavenly Shadow Talisman to manifest this body to come and see me?"

The man's appearance was rather unremarkable, with the exception of his eyes, which were extremely deep and all-encompassing, as if he had seen everything there was to be seen in this world.

"I did indeed use a Heavenly Shadow Talisman to manifest this body, but only because my physical body was destroyed, so I had no choice," Tao Ji replied with a grief-stricken expression.

"What? Your physical body was destroyed? Who did that to you?" the white-robed man asked in an alarmed voice.

"It was a fugitive on our Heavenly Court's Immortal Slaying List by the name of Han Li. He goes by the alias of Li Feiyu," Tao Ji replied through tightly gritted teeth.

"I remember him, he's wanted for cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique and killing an immortal official. If I recall correctly, your son seemed to have also died by his hands, and there's a reward of five thousand Immortal Origin Stones on offer for his head. Is he in the Golden Origin Immortal Region right now?

“I can understand that you would go after him for vengeance for your son, but according to the information that we have on hand, he was only a True Immortal at the time of your son's death. Even if he's made some advancements in his cultivation base, there's no way he should've been able to defeat you."

The white-robed man was rattling off details about Han Li as if he knew them like the back of his hand, giving one an impression of omniscience.

"Our information on him may have been incorrect. Right now, he's already reached the High Zenith Stage, and his physical prowess is extremely formidable. He was able to easily break free from the Bipolar Yin Yang Array set up by Fellow Daoist Jin Chuan, myself, and close to a hundred Golden Immortals, all of whom perished by his hands, while I'm the lone survivor," Tao Ji said in a grim voice.

"What? He's at the High Zenith Stage? And you're saying he's a dual cultivator who also excels in bodily refinement? That's impossible!" the white-robed man exclaimed with a stunned expression.

"I'm telling the truth! Please take a look at this, Palace Master, I recorded our battle using a Heavenly Soul Bead," Tao Ji said as he opened his mouth to release a small, translucent bead.

The white-robed man cast an incantation seal onto the translucent bead, and it immediately began to glow radiantly, displaying a recording of the battle between Han Li and Tao Ji.

After watching the recording, the white-robed man murmured to himself with an incredulous expression, "He really has reached the High Zenith Stage, and it's only been about three thousand years since he appeared on the Immortal Slaying List."

"The only plausible explanation is that he had to have concealed his own cultivation base back then. No wonder my son died by his hands," Tao Ji said in a resentful manner.

"I don't think that's the case. Prior to putting someone on the Immortal Slaying List, the Heavenly Court always makes sure to conduct a thorough investigation into that person, and particular care is taken in determining their cultivation base, so there's no way there would've been a mistake there," the white-robed man replied with a shake of his head.

"In that case, could he really have progressed from the True Immortal Stage to the High Zenith Stage in no more than three thousand years while simultaneously making such extraordinary progress in bodily cultivation as well? That's impossible! There's no way his cultivation base could've improved so rapidly unless he has access to some type of unfathomable treasure that can drastically accelerate his cultivation progress..."

All of a sudden, his voice trailed off here as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

"Have you thought of something, Elder Tao?" the white-robed man asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"I have indeed, Palace Master," Tao Ji replied.

"What is it?" the white-robed man asked.

"A long time ago, my son sent some messages to me regarding Han Li, and I recall that some mention was made of some type of treasure that contained time law powers. I didn't look into it as I was grieving over the loss of my son, but could it be that this has something to do with the rapid progress he's made in his cultivation?" Tao Ji mused.

"What did the message say?" the white-robed man hurriedly asked.

"It's been a very long time, so I can't quite recall, but I've preserved all of the messages, and I'll get someone to bring them to us right away," Tao Ji replied, then pulled out a communication array plate before issuing a verbal instruction into it.

Shortly thereafter, a golden-robed young man flew in from outside, then knelt down before the two men.

"No need for formalities. Did you bring the things that I asked for?" Tao Ji asked.

"Here are all of the messages from Cousin Tao Yu," the golden-robed young man replied with a nod as he pulled out a stack of jade slips before setting them down onto the stone table inside the pergola.

The white-robed man paid no heed to the golden-robed young man as he picked up one of the jade slips, while Tao Ji dismissed the young man before picking up another one of the jade slips.

With their powers, they were able to quickly read through most of the jade slips, and right at this moment, an excited look appeared on the white-robed man's face, having just read through the contents of the jade slip in his hand.

"Have you found it, Palace Master?" Tao Ji asked.

The white-robed man took a glance at Tao Ji, then handed the jade slip over to him.

Tao Ji accepted the jade slip, then injected his spiritual sense into it, and inside was a message from Tao Yu, vaguely mentioning that he was investigating someone in possession of crystals that contained time law powers.

"Yes, this is the one! Do you think these time law crystals have something to do with his rapid cultivation base progression, Palace Master?" Tao Ji hurriedly asked.

"That doesn't matter anymore. Contact the temple right away and inform them that we've discovered a lead on Creation Crystals!" the white-robed man said in an excited manner as he began to make his way deeper into the garden in an urgent manner.

"You're saying these crystals are Creation Crystals?" Tao Ji exclaimed as he hurriedly followed along.

"I can't be fully certain, but I'm fairly confident that that's the case. According to the information that we have on hand, Creation Crystals can accelerate one's cultivation, and they can even accelerate the maturation of spirit plants. It can't just be a coincidence that this man has displayed such extraordinary cultivation progression and is also in possession of time law crystals. There's a very good chance that those crystals are none other than Creation Crystals!" the white-robed man replied.

"In that case, that does sound like a strong possibility! Forgive me for not considering such a possibility, Palace Master," Tao Ji said.

All of a sudden, the white-robed man stopped in his tracks before turning to Tao Ji with a suspicious expression.

"What's wrong, Palace Master?" Tao Ji asked with a perplexed expression.

"Elder Tao, did you really not make that connection, or did you intentionally hide this information because you wanted to claim the Creation Crystals for yourself, and you only revealed this information to me because Han Li was too powerful for you to defeat?" the white-robed man interrogated as he glowered intently at Tao Ji.

At the same time, an enormous aura erupted out of his body, exerting tremendous pressure upon Tao Ji.

"I wouldn't dare to intentionally withhold information on something so vital to the fortunes of our Nine Origins Temple, Palace Master! I genuinely never made the connection!" Tao Ji implored in a frantic voice as he fell to his knees.

The white-robed man paid no heed to Tao Ji's frantic cries as the pressure emanating from his body became more and more intense.

Meanwhile, Tao Ji was trembling in fear as he kowtowed over and over again.

"Regardless of whether you're telling the truth or not, I suppose you should be commended for finding this lead on Creation Crystals. You can go now. The immortal Palace will choose a suitable body for you to possess," the white-robed man said as his aura slowly subsided.

"Thank you, Palace Master," Tao Ji said in a grateful manner while panting heavily in the wake of immense pressure exerted upon him.

The white-robed man gave a cold harrumph before abruptly vanishing from the spot, while Tao Ji rose to his feet before departing as a sinister grin flashed over his face.

Chapter 1004: Chaotic Place

Moments later, the white-robed man appeared in a palace deep within the Golden Origin Immortal Palace.

Hovering inside the palace was a golden plate that was around a foot in size, and it was radiating bright golden light, forming a complex communication array.

He pulled out a purple badge, on one side of which was engraved the words "Nine Origins Temple" in small, golden text, while the other side of the badge bore an image depicting a piece of majestic scenery.

The white-robed man was just about to place the badge into the communication array when he suddenly stopped what he was doing, then withdrew the badge before making his way into another palace.

From there, he sat down onto the main chair, and as soon as he did so, two figures appeared before him amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

One of them was a gray-haired elderly man with a nose that was close to twice the length of the average person's, and he had a pair of small eyes that were constantly darting around from side to side, as well as a thin, whisker-like mustache, giving him the appearance of a giant rat.

The other figure was a brawny, black-robed man with his arms crossed in front of his chest and a mighty saber carried on his back.

"How can we help you, Palace Master?" the two figures asked as they cupped their fists in a collective salute.

The elderly man's voice was quite sharp, matching his rat-like appearance, while the black-robed man's voice was very coarse and abrasive, much like the sound of steel needles scraping over stone.

"Lü Yun, make a trip to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region to investigate Han Li. I want an exhaustive investigation starting from his time in the lower realms, and make sure not to omit even the smallest of details," the white-robed man instructed.

"Yes, Palace Master," the gray-robed elderly man replied with a nod.

"Hei Dao, go to the Heavenly Pine Temple to search for Han Li. Make sure to find him, but do not alert him to your presence," the white-robed man ordered, and the black-robed man also gave an affirmative response.

"Go," the white-robed man said with a dismissive wave of his hand, and the two figures standing before him vanished in unison.

The white-robed man sat back in his chair as a faint smile appeared on his face.

At this moment, Han Li was flying through the air as a streak of blue light atop a blue flying carriage.

He had found the blue flying carriage in Daoist Master Bone Shine's bone ring, and it was not inferior in caliber to his previous green jade flying carriage.

He was seated on the flying carriage with his legs crossed, examining the over one hundred tools that he had claimed from Tao Ji and the others.

Han Li picked up Tao Ji's storage ring, then injected his spiritual sense into it, and moments later, a golden badge appeared in his grasp amid a flash of golden light. Engraved onto one side of the badge was a golden dragon, while the name "Tao Ji" was engraved on the other side, beneath which were the words "Golden Origin Immortal Palace" in small text.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

Having been at odds with the Heavenly Court for so many years, he had developed a decent understanding of the immortal palaces, and in particular, he had become very familiar with what some of the identity badges of the immortal palaces entailed, so he knew that this badge was an elder badge Golden Origin Immortal Palace.

He stowed the badge away, then examined the contents of Jin Chuan's storage tool, and he was quickly able to determine that he was an elder of the Heavenly Water Sect, a large sect in the Golden Origin Immortal Region.

As for those Golden Immortals, half of them served the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, while the other half were from the Heavenly Water Sect.

Some of these Golden Immortals had been very important figures in the immortal palace and the Heavenly Water Sect, but for the current Han Li, the only things of value in their storage tools were their Immortal Origin Stones.

Hence, he casually split everything else up into several categories, planning to sell them all at a later date for Immortal Origin Stones. Once he did that, he would have enough Immortal Origin Stones to support the average High Zenith cultivator's cultivation for at least a million years.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he processed this new information.

The Golden Origin Immortal Region was one of the largest immortal regions under the Heavenly Court's control, so the leader of the Golden Origin Immortal Palace had to be at least a Great Encompassment cultivator.

Even though he had ensured that there were no survivors to tell the tale from the Golden Origin Immortal Palace or the Heavenly Water Sect, there was still no guarantee that his enemies wouldn't be able to find him.

Having said that, at this point, it hardly mattered if he killed more Heavenly Court cultivators or not. His identity had already been exposed, and there was no way that the Heavenly Court would ever let him off the hook, so what did it matter if he killed another elder and a few dozen Golden Immortals?

He was no longer the mere True Immortal that he had been when he first ascended to the Immortal Realm, and he was confident that he would at least be able to ensure self-preservation even in the face of a Great Encompassment cultivator.

However, the Golden Origin Immortal Palace was tied to the Heavenly Court, which had Dao Ancestors among its ranks. Prior to this, it was unlikely that he would've attracted the attention of those Dao Ancestors, but that could be subject to change from here onward. Han Li was very confident in his own powers, but certainly not so confident that he would dare to take on the entire Heavenly Court.

Hence, it seemed that he would have to go into hiding for now.

With that in mind, Han Li quickly summoned a few scriptures pertaining to the Golden Origin Immortal Region that he had sourced from the storage tools of Tao Ji and the others.

The fact that these scriptures were in the possession of the likes of Tao Ji naturally indicated that their contents were extremely useful, and with Han Li's current spiritual sense and memory functions, he was able to rapidly read through multiple scriptures at once.

All of a sudden, he made a hand seal, and the flying carriage began traveling in a different direction from before.

Over ten years flew by in a flash.

Somewhere in the Golden Origin Immortal Region, a streak of blue light was racing through the heavens, and it drew to a gradual halt, revealing a blue flying carriage.

Ahead of the flying carriage was a massive, golden mountain range with enormous mountains that pierced all the way up into the clouds. On top of that, the mountain range stretched as far as the eyes could see in either direction, resembling an enormous, golden barricade.

The golden mountain range was enshrouded in dense golden mist, giving it an air of mystery.

"We've finally arrived," Han Li said with a relieved expression as he observed the mountain range up ahead.

Standing beside him was a black-robed young woman, and it was none other than Weeping Soul, who had awakened not long ago.

At this moment, she was still looking slightly pale, and she was observing the massive mountain range up ahead with an intrigued look in her eyes.

This Golden Origin Mountain Range was the largest mountain range in the entire Golden Origin Immortal Region. In contrast with the complex terrain and environment of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, the Golden Origin Immortal Region only had a single, vast continent, and the Golden Origin Mountain Range stretched over close to half of the entire continent.

In terms of area, the Golden Origin Mountain Range was definitely the largest mountain range that Han Li had ever witnessed.

On top of that, it was also a place that was fraught with perils and riches.

The Golden Origin Immortal Region was extremely abundant with metal-attribute spiritual qi, and the Golden Origin Mountain Range was where all of the metal-attribute spirit veins in the entire immortal region were gathered.

The mountain range was rife with metal-attribute spiritual qi, giving rise to countless metal-attribute spirit materials, attracting treasure-hunting cultivators from all over the entire immortal region.

However, due to the excessive abundance of metal-attribute spiritual qi in the Golden Origin Mountain Range, many natural metal force fields were present deep within the mountain range, and the deeper one ventured into the mountain range, the more powerful these force fields became.

Furthermore, the tremendous metal-attribute spiritual qi in the Golden Origin Mountain Range had given rise to many types of interesting metal beasts. The bodies of these beasts were formed by metal-attribute spiritual qi, and not only were they very formidable to begin with, they were also unaffected by the metal force fields in the mountain range, giving them an additional advantage over cultivators in battle.

The metal force fields, metal beats, and other hazards in the mountain range claimed the lives of countless treasure-hunting cultivators every year, but even so, countless cultivators were still venturing into the mountain range every single day.

The immortal palace naturally wasn't just going to ignore such an enormous natural treasure vault. In fact, the Golden Origin Immortal Palace was situated in the western region of the Golden Origin Mountain Range, and it had always been trying to seize control of the mountain range.

Unfortunately for them, the mountain range was simply too massive, and the Golden Origin Immortal Palace was only able to claim a small area in the western region of the mountain region, while the rest was split among countless immortal powers.

As a result, there were conflicts constantly taking place between the powers present in the mountain range, and Han Li had come here precisely because he wanted to take advantage of the chaotic environment here.

At this point, he had already opened over nine hundred profound acupoints, and his past experience told him that this would make it far easier for him to continue opening immortal acupoints in the future.

On top of that, he had a vast number of Immortal Origin Stones in his possession, so he was in a perfect position to go into seclusion and make some rapid advances in his cultivation base.

The attack from Tao Ji and the others had instilled within him a sense of urgency, and with that in mind, he adopted a disguise using his Reincarnation Mask, transforming into a brawny man with a thick beard.

On top of that, he had also suppressed his own cultivation base to the early-Golden Immortal Stage.

"Should I adopt a disguise as well, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"There's no need for that, no one knows you here in the Golden Origin Immortal Region," Han Li replied with a shake of his head, following which the flying carriage made its way into the Golden Origin Mountain Range at his behest.

Up close, the Golden Origin Mountain Range was even more majestic, and Han Li and Weeping Soul were made to resemble two tiny specks of dust as they stood before it.

The world's origin qi here was very abundant, but the vast majority of it was of the metal attribute, making it a perfect environment for those using metal-attribute cultivation arts, but it was rather inhospitable for other cultivators.

However, the environment didn't have any impact on Han Li as he depended on pills for his cultivation, as opposed to the world's origin qi in the outside world.

"Where do we go from here, Master? Are you going to find a place to go into seclusion in this mountain range?" Weeping Soul asked.

"There are many cities established by different immortal powers in the Golden Origin Mountain Range, so let's do some exploring first. If it's safer on the outskirts of the mountain range, then we can just go into seclusion somewhere nearby," Han Li replied, and Weeping Soul nodded in response.

Chapter 1005: Rescue

The flying carriage continued onward, and before long, it had traveled tens of thousands of kilometers into the mountain range.

As it was flying over a golden mountain, a burst of golden light suddenly flashed on the mountain face, and a golden, wolf-like beast abruptly pounced at the carriage like a golden arrow.

Han Li flicked a finger through the air, releasing a streak of golden sword qi that struck the creature, slicing it in half from head to toe.

Large volumes of golden blood erupted through the air, following which the two halves of the creature's body were caught by a burst of azure light.

The creature's body had been warm and pliable just a second ago, but in the wake of its demise, its body quickly began to harden, and it was already beginning to resemble two halves of a golden statue.

"So this is a metal beast?" Weeping Soul asked with a curious expression.

Han Li examined the two halves of the creature's body momentarily, then broke off a piece to discover that it was no different from a piece of metal ore.

Han Li tossed the two halves of the body aside with slightly furrowed brows.

These metal beasts weren't powerful enough to pose any threat to him, but the problem was that they could fuse as one with the mountains, granting them exceptional self-concealment.

This metal beast was only a very low-level one, but he wasn't confident in his ability to detect more powerful ones in this environment.

With that in mind, it seemed like this was not a good place to go into seclusion.

Thus, the two of them continued onward.

Right at this moment, bursts of soundwaves converted from spiritual sense were transmitted through the area from the left.

The voice belonged to a woman, and it was desperately crying for help, striking the listener with a sense of sympathy.

Furthermore, these spiritual sense fluctuations were quite peculiar, and they were able to transmit themselves directly into the hearts of Han Li and Weeping Soul.

This form of spiritual sense conversion was far more advanced than normal spiritual sense voice transmission, and Han Li was rather intrigued.

Weeping Soul turned to Han Li with a hint of pity in her eyes as she asked, "Master, should we..."

Han Li wasn't one to stick his nose into other people's business, but he didn't want to turn down Weeping Soul, so he said, "Let's go take a look."

Thus, the flying carriage swiveled around at his behest, and he used a secret technique to conceal it as it flew toward the source of the sound.

A short while later, the flying carriage drew to a halt beside a canyon, within which a battle was taking place between an azure-robed young woman and five balls of golden light.

The young woman was the one who was calling for help, and it seemed that she was in quite a dire situation.

The protective spiritual light around her had been whittled down to a thin layer, and she was frantically warding off the surrounding attacks while releasing more of those soundwaves to cry for help.

A hint of surprise appeared in Han Li's eyes as he noticed a long azure fox tail trailing along behind the young woman, indicating that she was a being of the fox race, and her cultivation base was at the mid-True Immortal Stage.

She was surrounded by five daoist priests that were dressed in golden robes, and there was a golden horse design emblazoned onto each robe, seemingly the emblem of a certain sect.

The five of them were only at the early-True Immortal Stage, but they held a decisive numbers advantage.

Each of them was holding a large golden flag, forming a ring of golden light that suppressed the young woman.

The leader of the five daoist priests was a square-faced man with a lecherous grin on his face, and he chuckled, "Hand over the Golden Wyrm Beast inner core and surrender yourself over to us. It would be a waste to kill you, considering your pure Azure Fox bloodline, so instead, we'll offer you up to our master for his birthday present."

"Your Azure Fox Tribe is only a tiny tribe that could be eradicated by other powers in this mountain range at any moment. Our Golden Horse Sect is hundreds of times more powerful than your tribe, and our master is a Golden Immortal, so you should be honored to become a maidservant of his!" another daoist priest guffawed.

"If I hadn't been worn down during my battle against the Golden Wyrm Beast, there's no way the five of you could trap me!" the young woman spat through gritted teeth.

"Let's not waste any more time here, Senior Martial Brother. Use the Five Gold Radiant Light Array to break through her protective demonic light, then seal her cultivation base so we can offer her up to Master. He's always wanted an Azure Fox maidservant, so he'll definitely be very pleased and reward us handsomely," another one of the daoist priests yelled.

"We can't do that. The Five Gold Radiant Light Array is too powerful, and it could harm her cultivation foundation. If that happens, we won't be able to offer her up to Master. Right now, she's already close to a spent force, so we just need to wear her down a little more," the square-faced daoist priest said with a shake of his head.

"Senior Martial Brother is right!"

"It would be a terrible waste to ruin such a precious gift out of impatience!"

"That's right, all we need to do is wear her down a little more."

All of the other daoist priests immediately chimed in in agreement.

The azure-robed young woman was furious to hear this, and the azure light around her abruptly brightened as a strands of azure fox fur shot out of her tail, screeching through the air before striking the ring of golden light around her.

The golden ring immediately began to tremble violently while being rapidly worn down, and the five daoist priests hurriedly released mouthfuls of blood essence into the flags in their hands upon seeing this.

The golden flags instantly flew out of their grasp before fusing into the ring of golden light, and at the same time, the five of them began to make a rapid string of hand seals, fortifying the golden ring against the strands of fox fur.

This final act of resistance seemed to have exhausted what little remained of the young woman's power, and the azure light around her body quickly faded away, while she began to sway unsteadily on her feet.

The five daoist priests were ecstatic to see this, and their leader flew toward the azure-robed young woman while making a grab for her with a perverted look on his face.

Han Li remained completely unmoved by this, but Weeping Soul was furious, and she turned to him with an urgent expression as she called out, "Master!"

"Don't worry, she'll be fine," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

Sure enough, as soon as his voice trailed off, the situation took an abrupt turn.

The young woman had been swaying unsteadily on her feet, but as soon as the square-faced daoist priest drew close to her, she abruptly steadied herself as a cold look flashed through her eyes.

The daoist priest was very alarmed to see this, knowing that he had fallen into a trap, and he immediately tried to stop in his tracks, but it was already too late.

The azure-robed young woman raised both of her arms, and several streaks of azure light shot out of her hands before striking the square-faced daoist priest.

The streaks of azure light were extremely sharp and pierced through protective spiritual light around the square-faced daoist priest with ease, upon which they were revealed to be a set of fingernails.

The square-faced daoist priest was struck in several vital regions, and blood gushing out of his mouth as he fell to the ground with an indignant expression, following which his aura rapidly faded away.

With that, the azure-robed young woman really had used up the last of her demonic power, and she also collapsed to the ground, completely powerless to resist any longer.

"Senior Martial Brother! How dare you!"

The other four daoist priests were furious to see this, and they unleashed a torrential downpour of attacks upon her.

The young woman displayed no fear at all as she calmly watched all of the attacks raining down upon her, and she was making a hand seal behind her back as a look of finality flashed through her eyes.

Right at this moment, a ball of azure light abruptly appeared above her, and all of the oncoming attacks sank into the azure light as if it were a ball of quicksand.

In the next instant, all of the attacks were sent flying back several times faster than they had come, instantly piercing through the bodies of the four daoist priests to eradicate them on the spot.

The azure-robed young woman was astonished to see this, but she continued to hold the hand seal behind her back.

Right at this moment, Han Li and Weeping Soul descended out of the sky, and the young woman's expression changed slightly as she detected their tremendous auras.

She struggled to her feet with some difficulty, then extended a curtsey toward them.

"Thank you for saving my life, seniors."

"There's no need for formalities, you've exerted yourself far too much already," Weeping Soul hurriedly said as she swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of black light to help steady the young woman.

The azure-robed young woman displayed no aversion to Weeping Soul's kind gesture, and a bright smile appeared on her face as she released her hand seal.

"What's your name? Which power in the Golden Origin Mountain Range do you belong to? And who were those people?" Han Li asked.

He had saved the young woman at Weeping Soul's request, but that didn't mean that she could be spared from interrogation.

"My name is Ye Susu, and I'm from the Azure Fox Tribe. Those people were disciples of the Golden Horse Sect, and they've always been at odds with our Azure Fox Tribe. I was out hunting a Golden Wyrm Beast, and they took advantage of the fact that I was exhausted from my battle to try and capture me. If the two of you hadn't saved me, I would've self-detonated to avoid capture," the young woman explained in a respectful manner.

A thoughtful look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

He had chosen to save Ye Susu mostly for Weeping Soul's sake, but another factor that influenced his decision was that she was a being of the fox race, so he had thought that perhaps she had something to do with the Heavenly Fox Tribe, where Liu Le'er currently was, but it seemed like that was not the case.

"How many people are there in the Golden Horse Sect, and how powerful is the sect?" Han Li asked.

"The Golden Horse Sect is the most powerful sect in this area. It has over ten thousand disciples, with several Golden Immortals among them, and their grand elder is already at the late-Golden Immortal Stage," Ye Susu replied.

Han Li gave a slight nod upon hearing this.

At the moment, Ye Susu was in terrible condition, and her complexion was deathly pale, while her body was trembling slightly, but she still gritted her teeth and remained standing as she answered Han Li's questions.

"You should take a moment to rest and recover from your injuries," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light that vanished into Ye Susu's body.

Ye Susu felt a massive surge of warmth enter her body, and the injuries that she had sustained began to rapidly heal. In the blink of an eye, her complexion had returned to normal, and she was no longer trembling.

After healing all of her injuries, the burst of warmth surged into the demon core in her dantian, causing it to expand slightly.

Ye Susu hurriedly sat down with her legs crossed and began channeling her cultivation arts to take full advantage of this opportunity.

Chapter 1006: Long Separation

"Is she alright, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"She's fine, it's just that her cultivation foundation was compromised from excessive demonic power expenditure, but I've already smoothed out those problems for her. It seems like you're very fond of this girl. I've never seen you be so friendly to anyone else," Han Li remarked with an inquisitive expression.

"Her soul aura is very clean and pure, like a spring in the mountains. It's very comforting to me, and perhaps that's why I'm drawn to her," Weeping Soul explained in a slightly embarrassed manner.

"You can detect soul auras now?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

"After I awakened from my unconscious state, I discovered that I had made some strides in my law power cultivation base, allowing me to detect the soul auras of others, using which I can determine their personalities. With this ability up my sleeve, no one can hide their true nature from me," Weeping Soul replied with a smug expression, and Han Li was quite intrigued to hear this.

If this ability really were as Weeping Soul described, then it was quite extraordinary. No matter how powerful one's spiritual sense was, it was still impossible for one to look directly into the heart of someone else, so this was certainly a very remarkable ability to possess.

"What's my soul aura like?" Han Li asked in a curious manner.

"Your soul aura is too vast for me to assess clearly, but overall, you have a very just and righteous aura," Weeping Soul replied.

"I certainly wouldn't dare to say that I'm a just and righteous man. All I can say is that I have a relatively clear conscience," Han Li said with a shake of his head.

"Given how perilous the path of cultivation is, those who are too kind of heart or too weak of will cannot hope to progress far down this path. Sometimes, one has to be a little cold-hearted. Otherwise, they risk hurting themselves and even those precious to them.

“While it can appear to others that you're a little cold and detached, you have a moral code that you abide by in everything that you do, and that's certainly far from common for cultivators of your caliber," Weeping Soul said in an earnest manner.

"It seems like not only are you now able to see into the hearts of others, you're also seeing the world much more clearly," Han Li remarked with a faint smile.

He then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light that carried the storage tools of the five Golden Horse Sect cultivators to him.

He was naturally not interested in the treasures in their possession, but they did have some scriptures that contained information about the Golden Origin Mountain Range, which were quite useful to Han Li in his current situation.

Han Li pulled out those scriptures before carefully reading through them, while Weeping Soul remained by his side in silence.

Over two hours flew by in a flash, and as Ye Susu rose to her feet, she was looking in much better spirits. Not only had she made a full recovery, her aura had been significantly elevated as well.

"Words cannot express my gratitude, Senior. Not only have you saved my life, you've also expended your own power to help advance my cultivation base. Is there anything I can do for you in return?" Ye Susu asked.

"It's nothing, don't worry about it," Han Li replied with a dismissive wave.

"If you don't mind, I'd like to invite the two of you to stay in our tribe's Azure Fox City for a while. Please give me the opportunity to show my gratitude and display some hospitality," Ye Susu said with a hopeful look in her eyes.

Weeping Soul turned to Han Li upon hearing this, and Ye Susu also turned her gaze to Han Li.

"Sure. We're currently traveling the Golden Origin Mountain Range and don't have a specific destination in mind anyway," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Please come with me, seniors," Ye Susu said with an elated expression, then opened her mouth to release a ball of azure flames that incinerated the bodies of the five Golden Horse Sect cultivators, following which she swept a sleeve through the air to summon a flying boat.

The three of them drifted onto the flying boat, which began to fly deeper into the mountain range.

"By the way, may I ask your names, seniors?" Ye Susu asked.

"My name is Han Li, and her name is Weeping Soul. There's no need to refer to us as seniors, just call us by our names," Han Li replied, choosing not to give an alias this time.

In order to protect himself, he had been forced to use different aliases wherever he went, and he had grown quite weary of it.

At this point, his identity was no longer a secret, so there was no need for him to hide it any longer.

"I can't do that, seniors! The two of you saved my life, so it would be terribly rude of me to refer to you directly by name. I may be a demon, but I know the importance of etiquette," Ye Susu hurriedly replied in a serious manner.

Han Li merely gave a faint smile and didn't dwell on this subject any longer.

"My master was the one who saved you, while I did nothing, so don't refer to me as your senior. Just call me Weeping Soul," Weeping Soul said with a wide smile as she latched onto Ye Susu's hand.

Ye Susu took a timid glance at Han Li upon hearing this, and only after gauging his reaction to ensure that he wasn't displeased did she strike up a conversation with Weeping Soul.

Their personalities seemed to mesh quite well as Ye Susu was very outgoing and talkative, while Weeping Soul was very curious about this new immortal region, and they quickly became good friends.

A short while later, the flying boat arrived in a massive col.

The col was several thousand kilometers in size, and there was a giant city inside it.

The city was almost entirely constructed from golden materials, and its walls were extremely tall, not much shorter than the surrounding mountains.

There were also dozens of enormous golden stone pillars standing around the city, at the top of each of which was a giant golden ball that was several thousand feet in size.

Right at this moment, several streaks of light approached the flying boat from up ahead, following which several Azure Fox beings emerged.

The leader of the group was a tall and thin man, and he immediately greeted with an elated expression, "Welcome back, Young Mistress!"

However, he then caught sight of Han Li and Weeping Soul, and his brows furrowed slightly in wariness as he asked, "Who are you two?"

"Don't be so rude!" Ye Susu snapped with a displeased expression. "They are esteemed guests who have saved my life!"

The man's mouth gaped open slightly in shock upon hearing this, and it seemed that he wanted to ask Ye Susu about what had happened to her, but ultimately refrained from doing so.

"Please forgive me," he apologized as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li and Weeping Soul.

Han Li paid no heed to the Azure Fox beings as he took a casual glance at the city down below.

There was quite a large wood-attribute spirit vein underground beneath the col, filling the entire area with abundant wood-attribute spiritual qi that gave rise to masses of lush vegetation.

The Azure Fox Tribe had found quite a good place to settle in, one that was abundant with both metal and wood-attribute spiritual qi.

Even though the city down below was constructed from a golden material, it was very different from the golden rocks all over the Golden Origin Mountain Range. Whatever this material was, it was etched with black patterns that resembled the rings of a tree, and it was giving off a glacial aura.

Upon noticing Han Li's intrigued expression, Ye Susu explained, "This is Dark Gold Rock. It's found deep within the Golden Origin Mountain Range and can keep out metal beasts. Almost all of the cities in the Golden Origin Mountain Range are constructed from this material. Otherwise, it would be impossible to live in this mountain range with metal beasts capable of lurking within the walls."

Han Li had seen descriptions of Dark Gold Rock in the scriptures carried by the Golden Horse Sect cultivators, and he gave a slight nod in response.

Meanwhile, the tall and thin man briefly examined Han Li and Weeping Soul's cultivation bases, upon which his expression instantly changed slightly, and he hurriedly extended another apology before leading the trio down toward the city below.

"How is my mother right now, Ye Ping?" Ye Susu asked through voice transmission.

"Our chief's condition hasn't worsened thanks to the effects of the Green Wave Pond and the treatment administered by Elder Qiu," Ye Ping replied.

"Good. I've gathered enough materials for the Bloodform Origin Restoration Array during this outing, and I'm definitely going to cure mother once and for all!" Ye Susu declared with a determined expression.

However, it seemed that Ye Ping was far from elated to hear this.

Even though the two of them were conversing through voice transmission, they were naturally unable to keep their conversation secret from Han Li, and he turned to Ye Susu with a contemplative expression.

The four of them quickly landed in front of the city gate, above which was a plaque that read "Azure Fox City".

There were guards stationed at the city gate, but Han Li's group was granted free passage thanks to Ye Susu's presence.

Beyond the city gates was a wide stone road that was lined with buildings, most of which appeared to be shops.

These buildings were constructed from wood, and the construction style adopted was also very different from what was commonly seen in normal cities. Some of the buildings were even constructed from primitive logs that hadn't been treated at all, presenting a rather refreshing sight to behold.

Furthermore, there were also many tall trees planted in the city, and Ye Susu smiled as she said, "Our Azure Fox City isn't very large, but it has some decent sights to offer."

"This is indeed a very nice place," Han Li replied with a nod as he took a glance at Weeping Soul, who was clearly also quite fond of this place, looking around in an intrigued manner.

Han Li was naturally very pleased to see her so happy, but at the same time, a hint of melancholy welled up in his heart.

Ever since Weeping Soul's awakening, she had become a lot more optimistic and outgoing, much like an average human girl, and that made him think of Jin Tong.

It had already been many years since they parted ways, and he had no idea where she and Xiao Bai were. Were they safe? Had she already found what she was searching for?

Chapter 1007: Hidden Area

"My mother is the chief of our Azure Fox Tribe, but she's been rather unwell of late, so she's been recovering in seclusion, and she won't be able to welcome the two of you. Please allow me to apologize on her behalf," Ye Susu said in an apologetic manner.

"That's fine. We are the visitors here, so we should be the ones to go to the owner of this place. Seeing as she's in seclusion, we don't go to interrupt her. Would I be able to trouble you to take us on a tour of the city, Fellow Daoist Ye?" Han Li asked.

"Of course!" Ye Susu replied in an eager manner, then dismissed Ye Ping and the others as she led Han Li and Weeping Soul deeper into the city.

Azure Fox City was several thousand kilometers in size, and even though its terrain was generally quite flat, there were several rivers and some short mountains in the city. On top of that, the entire city was rife with lush greenery, making for some fine scenery.

Before long, dusk had arrived, and Ye Susu led Han Li and Weeping Soul to the center of the city, where a cluster of tall palaces was situated.

The cluster of palaces took up an area of roughly two hundred to three hundred acres, and they were all constructed from wood as well.

In front of the main palace was a giant azure fox statue that was roaring up to the heavens. The statue was several thousand feet tall and nine tails, and it appeared to have been carved out of some type of green jade.

"This place is called the Heavenly Fox Palace, and it's where the chief of our Azure Fox Tribe resides," Ye Susu introduced.

"The Heavenly Fox Palace? Why is it not called the Azure Fox Palace?" Han Li asked.

"The name was decided by my ancestors, and I'm not sure about the reasons behind the decision," Ye Susu replied with a shake of her head.

Han Li simply nodded in response and didn't dwell on the subject.

"There are several peaceful courtyards beside the Heavenly Fox Palace reserved for the esteemed guests of our tribe. It's already quite late, so you can rest there for the night, and I'll return tomorrow," Ye Susu said as she led the two of them to a neaby courtyard.

After that, Ye Susu called over two Azure Fox Tribe servants before instructing them to station themselves outside the courtyard, and only then did she depart.

Han Li watched her departing figure for a moment, then entered the courtyard with Weeping Soul.

There was a small, brick path in the courtyard, to the left of which was a floral garden, while on the right was a miniature bamboo forest. The flowers and bamboo trees were swaying gently in the night breeze, giving off a faint, pleasant fragrance.

Han Li gave a pleased nod before sitting down in the main hall, and he was joined by Weeping Soul, who asked, "Are you planning to go into seclusion here in Azure Fox City, Master?"

"Why would you think that?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

A mischievous grin appeared on Weeping Soul's face as she replied, "Given how you normally like to do things, if you had no intention of staying in Azure Fox City for a long period of time, then you would've stopped at saving Ye Susu.

“Instead, you expended some of your energy to aid her in her cultivation, and you agreed to come here with her. On top of that, you instructed her to lead us on a tour of the city just now so that we can gain a better understanding of the city of the city, isn't that right?"

Han Li gave a nod of approval as he replied, "The Azure Fox Tribe is an unremarkable tribe in the Golden Origin Mountain Range, and their settlement is quite secluded, making this a very good hiding place. On top of that, I detected no potential hazards during the tour of the city."

"That's all well and good, but the problem is that the Azure Fox Tribe seems to be quite wary of humans. Of course, if you display some of your power, they'll have no choice but to let us stay, but that would be far from an ideal solution," Weeping Soul said with slightly furrowed brows.

During their tour of the city, they had noticed that the Azure Fox beings that they had passed by had all been observing them with enmity in their eyes, and they would've most likely already been attacked had they not been accompanied by Ye Susu.

"Not to worry, I have a plan," Han Li said with a smile as he cast his gaze toward the eastern side of the city.

......

Late at night, the gentle moonlight was spilling down from the heavens into the serene Azure Fox City.

An azure figure was flying through the city before landing in a lush forest in the eastern region of the city, and it was none other than Ye Susu.

She had changed into a luxurious azure palace dress, and there was an azure jade crown on her head, giving her air of regal authority.

There was an azure fox statue standing in front of the forest, but it was only around half the height of the average person, and it was very dilapidated, seemingly nothing more than an ordinary, rundown statue.

However, Ye Susu was regarding it with the utmost care as she joined her palms together before extending a respectful bow toward it, following which she sliced open the tip of her own finger before dripping a drop of blood onto it.

Two beams of azure light instantly shot out of the statue's eyes before vanishing into the space up ahead, and the space instantly began to ripple and tremble.

A layer of bright, azure light also surfaced over the palm of Ye Susu's hand as she extended her hand into the space up ahead before making a gentle, pulling motion, and a spatial opening that was around ten feet tall appeared before her.

After looking around briefly to ensure that there was nothing amiss, Ye Susu stepped into the spatial opening, upon which it immediately closed.

Right at this moment, a barely visible shadow appeared nearby, then flew into the spatial opening right before it completely closed.

Ye Susu's vision blurred momentarily, following which she found herself standing in front of a basin that was several dozen kilometers in size.

There weren't many buildings in the basin, but there were large plots of spirit farmland, seemingly with many types of spirit medicines planted inside.

However, there were light barriers around these plots of spirit farmland to conceal what was inside, with only the medicinal fragrance wafting out of the light barriers providing some indication of what was planted inside.

Ye Susu flew directly onward, and that indistinct shadow appeared behind her before revealing itself to be none other than Han Li, and he turned to the plots of spirit farmland with a surprised look in his eyes.

Given his expertise in spirit medicines, he could tell just from the medicinal aroma alone that the spirit medicines planted here were quite remarkable. In fact, this place was not inferior to his own medicinal garden in the Flower Branch domain.

One had to realize that the medicinal garden in the Flower Branch domain was a culmination of countless time and effort, in conjunction with the Heaven Controlling Vial, so it was very remarkable that the Azure Fox Tribe had managed to create something on a similar level, given that it wasn't a particularly powerful tribe.

With that in mind, he descended toward the plots of spirit farmland for a closer look.

......

Meanwhile, Ye Susu had already flown deep into the basin, arriving at a gently rippling green pond.

Situated beside the pond were several large, azure rocks, and she gently patted one of them, upon which it immediately sank down to reveal a dark opening, revealing a long staircase that led deep underground.

It didn't take long for Ye Susu to reach the bottom of the staircase, where she arrived in a large stone chamber, embedded into the ceiling of which were several fist-sized white jewels that basked the entire place in a gentle, white glow.

There were specks of starlight flashing on the surrounding walls, clearly indicating the presence of some type of restriction.

Inside the stone chamber was a white jade bed with an azure-robed young woman laying on it, and her lower body was encased within a miniature blue mountain of ice that was several dozen feet tall.

The mountain of ice was giving off bone-chilling glacial qi, and the temperatures in the stone chamber were extremely low, with frost clinging to all of the walls, the floor, and the ceiling.

The woman's complexion was deathly pale, and her teeth were tightly gritted, while veins were bulging on her forehead, indicating that she was enduring immense agony.

Large droplets of sweat were flowing down from her forehead, only to be instantly frozen solid as soon as they dripped down into the air.

A woman in a white dress was standing at the head of the bed with her hands pressed into the azure-robed woman's shoulders, injecting bright azure into her body.

The aura of the woman in white indicated that she was at the early-Golden Immortal Stage, and upon hearing the sound of Ye Susu's approaching footsteps, she looked up with a surprised expression, then stopped what she was doing as she greeted, "Welcome back, Young Mistress."

The azure-robed woman on the bed also opened her eyes to look at Ye Susu, and she forced a smile onto her own face as she said in a gentle voice, "Come here, Susu."

"Mother!" Ye Susu hurried over to the bed before clasping onto the azure-robed woman's hand, and tears immediately began welling up in her eyes.

"Don't cry, Susu, I'm fine. Too much glacial qi has entered my body recently, but I can ward it off with Elder Qiu's help. Where did you go? You were away for so long. Did you encounter any danger?" the azure-robed woman asked in a gentle voice.

"I paid a visit to Golden Rhinoceros City to exchange for some things. On the way back, I encountered a few Golden Horse Sect cultivator's, and I was in a little bit of danger, but thankfully, I was saved by a pair of seniors who just so happened to be passing by..."

With that, she delivered a brief recount of her outing.

"What?! You invited a human cultivator into our Azure Fox City? How could you, Young Mistress? You should be well aware that those detestable human cultivators are ones that did this to our chief!" Elder Qiu scolded in a cold voice after hearing Ye Susu's story.

A hint of resentment appeared in Ye Susu's eyes upon hearing this, but she immediately suppressed it as she replied, "It's true that humans did this to my mother, but we can't condemn all human cultivators because of that.

“Right now, the Golden Origin Immortal Region is ruled over by humans, and if our Azure Fox Tribe wants to develop, then we'll have to interact with humans. As the leaders of our Azure Fox Tribe, we should set aside our personal emotions to do what's best for our tribe."

At this moment, Han Li was standing in a dark shadow outside the hall, and a hint of approval flashed through his eyes upon hearing this.

Elder Qiu's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and she was just about to say something else, but the azure-robed woman raised a hand to stop her.

"I agree with Susu on this matter. Seeing as those two fellow daoists are both at the Golden Immortal Stage, if we can establish good relations with them, then that would be immensely beneficial to the future development of our Azure Fox Tribe."

Elder Qiu was silent for a moment, then acquiesced, "In that case, we'll do as you say, Chief."

"Thank you, Mother!" Ye Susu said with an elated expression.

Chapter 1008: Mother-and-Daughter Bond

"While it's a good idea to recruit more allies to strengthen our tribe, your safety is a higher priority, Susu. Our Azure Fox Tribe currently rests on your shoulders. I'm already like this, so you must remain safe," the azure-robed woman sighed.

"What are you saying, Mother? You're definitely going to recover!" Ye Susu protested in a vehement manner.

"Yes, yes, I'll be sure to get better," the azure-robed woman hurriedly agreed, but the look in her eyes betrayed the pessimism deep in her heart.

Ye Susu lowered her head, and a decisive look flashed through her eyes as she suddenly reached out with a finger like lightning.

Bright, white light was glowing on her fingertip as he tapped it against the azure-robed woman's forehead, and the latter's eyes widened in shock, following which she quickly fell unconscious.

"What are you doing, Young Mistress!" Elder Qiu exclaimed.

Ye Susu offered no response as she pulled out a crimson rune pen, then began inscribing array patterns onto the ground around the jade bed while pulling out various array tools.

Elder Qiu wanted to raise further questions, but she refrained from doing so at the sight of Ye Susu's focused expression.

Half a day passed by in the blink of an eye, and as the sun was beginning to rise outside, Ye Susu finally stopped what she was doing, having created a complex crimson array around the jade bed.

"What's this, Young Mistress?" Elder Qiu asked.

"It's the Bloodform Origin Restoration Array," Ye Susu replied.

"What?! Isn't that the array that strips one of their bloodline power before injecting it into someone else's body? Do you intend to inject your own Azure Fox bloodline power into your mother's body to help her ward off the glacial qi? I can't allow you to do that!

“The Bloodform Origin Restoration Array is far too harmful to the user, and once your bloodline power is stripped away, it'll be impossible to recover it! Your cultivation foundation will be destroyed, and you could even revert back into a fox with no intelligence!" Elder Qiu exclaimed in an alarmed voice.

"As long as I can save my mother, none of that matters," Ye Susu replied with a placid expression, and there was a peaceful smile on her face.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, clearly touched by Ye Susu's moving display.

"In that case, allow me to take your place. My cultivation base is superior to yours, so there will be a higher chance of success for me," Elder Qiu said.

"No. Your cultivation base may be superior to mine, but I have the purer Azure Fox bloodline. On top of that, when using the Bloodform Origin Restoration Array to combine bloodlines, the more closely related the two subjects are, the higher the chance of success," Ye Susu said in a determined manner.

Elder Qiu had no response for this.

"The frost poison that my mother has been afflicted by is extremely formidable, so even with this array, there's only roughly a 50% chance that Mother will be saved. If things go wrong, then both of us could die in the array. If that happens, you'll be the only Golden Immortal left in our Azure Fox Tribe, so your safety is actually more important than mine.

“Even if Mother and I perish here, there will still be hope for our Azure Fox Tribe's future, but if something happens to you, then our Azure Fox Tribe will truly be doomed," Ye Susu continued.

Elder Qiu remained silent, and it was unclear what she was thinking.

"Leave everything here to me, Elder Qiu. If my mother and I don't make it, then the Azure Fox Tribe will have to fall upon your shoulders," Ye Susu said in a serious manner, following which she prepared to step into the array, only for Elder Qiu to suddenly catch her by her wrist.

"Young Mistress, you just said that as leaders of our Azure Fox Tribe, we should set aside our own personal emotions and think for the greater good. You possess excellent aptitude, and your Azure Fox bloodline is even purer than mine and your mother's, so your potential is limitless. Given Chief's current condition, even the Bloodform Origin Restoration Array may not be enough to save us.

“This may be a little cruel for me to say, but for the sake of our Azure Fox Tribe, I think it's best not to take the risk, and I think Chief would agree with me," Elder Qiu said with a torn expression.

"No, I'm not doing this for myself. I may possess some aptitude, but right now, I'm only at the mid-True Immortal Stage, and no one knows if I'll be able to become a Golden Immortal in the future. Objectively speaking, sacrificing a True Immortal for a 50% chance to save a Golden Immortal is a very good deal," Ye Susu said as she gently pulled her own wrist out of Elder Qiu's grasp.

An urgent look appeared on Elder Qiu's face upon hearing this, but she couldn't think of a good counterargument to this.

"My mother was wounded by those scoundrels from the Heavenly Water Sect in order to save me, and you almost met your demise in the process as well. If I don't do this for her, I'm going to carry guilt for the rest of my life. With this flaw in my mental state, even a breakthrough to the late-True Immortal Stage would be a distant pipe dream, let alone becoming a Golden Immortal," Ye Susu said in a decisive manner.

Elder Qiu knew that there was no dissuading her, so she could only heave a forlorn sigh before stepping away.

"Our Azure Fox Tribe will be counting on you, Elder Qiu," Ye Susu said with a faint smile, then stepped into the array before sitting down with her legs crossed at the head of the bed.

She then made a strange hand seal while chanting a mysterious incantation, and the crimson array on the ground instantly began to glow brightly, releasing radiant crimson light that swirled around rapidly within the array.

Formidable energy fluctuations erupted out of the array before sweeping through the air in all directions, and Elder Qiu hurriedly cast a few incantation seals into the walls of the stone chamber upon seeing this.

The restrictions on the walls instantly brightened, releasing dazzling starlight to contain the energy fluctuations, but they were too violent to be fully contained, and some of the energy fluctuations were still able to escape.

Elder Qiu paid no heed to this as she stared intently at the two people in the array, and right at this moment, countless strands of crimson light rose up from all over the array before entering Ye Susu's body.

A hint of surprise appeared on Han Li's face as he observed from the shadows.

A pained look appeared on Ye Susu's face, but she immediately suppressed it as she continued chanting her incantation.

More and more strands of crimson light surged out of the surrounding array before vanishing into her body, and a series of azure patterns began to appear over her skin, giving off radiant azure light and a formidable bloodline aura.

At the same time, an azure fox projection appeared behind her. The projection had a very regal and majestic appearance, but it only had two tails.

Right at this moment, Ye Susu reached out with one hand before pressing it down onto her mother's glabella.

Countless strands of crimson light shot out of the palm of her hand before surging into her mother's glabella, and faint, azure patterns could be seen entering her body along with the strands of crimson light.

A series of glowing azure patterns appeared over the woman's skin as well, but they were a little dimmer than the azure patterns on Ye Susu's body.

However, as more and more strands of crimson light surged into her glabella, the azure patterns on her body gradually grew brighter, while the azure patterns on Ye Susu's body slowly dimmed over time.

At the same time, her complexion had turned very pale, and the azure fox projection behind her was also displaying signs of fading.

However, there was an elated look in her eyes as she pointed a finger forward, and a beam of azure light shot out of her fingertip before vanishing into her mother's dantian.

The woman's body instantly began to glow like a radiant azure sun, following which all of the azure light condensed to form a layer of azure flames that spread toward the blue ice that her lower body was sealed in.

As soon as the two came into contact with each other, the blue ice immediately began to slowly melt, and a hopeful look appeared in Elder Qiu's eyes upon seeing this.

However, Han Li was shaking his head as he peered deep into the blue ice with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Before long, the blue ice had melted from the woman's waist down to her calves, but at this point, the rate at which the ice was melting slowed drastically, and it began to resist the advancement of the azure flames.

At this point, the azure patterns on Ye Susu's body had already dimmed significantly, and the azure fox projection behind her was also barely visible.

Her eyes narrowed slightly as she cast her gaze toward the remaining chunk of blue ice, and she let loose a low roar, upon which the crimson array beneath her lit up even further, sending countless strands of crimson light surging into her body.

The remaining azure bloodline in her body instantly completely faded away, forming a ball of azure light that made its way into the woman's body.

The azure flames were fueled by this ball of azure light, forcing back the blue ice a little further, but ultimately, it was unable to completely eradicate the ice.

Not only that, but a burst of blue light suddenly appeared on the azure-robed woman's calf, and it began to retaliate against the azure flames, forcing them back with ease.

An extremely formidable glacial aura erupted forth, and the blue ice quickly began to spread over the azure-robed woman's lower body again.

At the same time, the layers of frost in the stone chamber rapidly thickened, and even the crimson array on the ground was completely encased in blue ice.

At this moment, Ye Susu was completely spent, and she could barely even remain conscious as she looked around with a fearful expression.

Elder Qiu's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and she reflexively took a step forward, only for Ye Susu to turn to her with a shake of her head.

Elder Qiu gritted her teeth with a torn expression as she stopped in her tracks.

All of a sudden, the azure-robed woman shuddered as he snapped wide awake, and upon taking a brief glance at her surroundings, she immediately figured out what had happened.

She let loose a low roar, and the azure flames on her body swelled slightly to temporarily keep the expanding blue ice at bay as she hurriedly yelled, "Elder Qiu, take Susu and leave..."

Before she had a chance to finish her sentence, a burst of blue flames erupted forth, easily overwhelming the azure flames, and the blue ice continued to spread rapidly, reaching all the way up to the woman's chest in the blink of an eye.

At the same time, Ye Susu's body was also rapidly becoming encased in ice.

A conflicted look appeared on Elder Qiu's face upon seeing this, and she was just about to throw caution to the wind and rush into the array when a black figure abruptly appeared in front of her.

It was none other than Han Li.

Chapter 1009: Rescue

Elder Qiu was quite startled by this turn of events, but she was immediately able to identify Han Li as a human, and a look of burning hatred appeared in her eyes as she sprang forward to attack Han Li.

"Stay put if you want these two to live!" Han Li warned as he casually swept a sleeve through the air, and a burst of azure light flew out of his hand to ward off the ferocious blue flames.

The blue flames immediately began to rear up like an infuriated wild beast, crashing against the azure light with all its might, but to no avail.

Elder Qiu stopped in her tracks upon seeing this, but she was still glowering intently at Han Li, and her hand remained raised aloft, ready to strike at any moment.

Han Li paid no heed to her as he swept his sleeve through the air once again, releasing another burst of azure light that fused with the first one to rapidly force back the blue flames.

The blue flames had been far too powerful for Ye Susu and her mother to resist, yet Han Li was able to easily suppress it back down to the woman's calf.

He swept his sleeve through the air a third time, releasing a ball of silver flames that transformed into a silver fire raven, which plunged headfirst into the blue flames.

A cry of elation rang out as a burst of scorching heat erupted out of the silver flames, instantly melting away all of the blue ice in the stone chamber.

A surprised look appeared in Elder Qiu's eyes upon seeing this, but she still didn't let down her guard.

Shortly thereafter, the silver fire raven re-emerged, clutching a fist-sized ball of blue fire in its beak, which it promptly devoured before letting loose an elated cry, as if it had just enjoyed a delicious meal.

After that, the silver fire raven flew back up Han Li's sleeve.

At this point, the blue ice that encapsulated the bodies of Ye Susu and her mother had already completely vanished, and both of them were rooted to the spot with stunned looks on their faces.

All of a sudden, an agonized look appeared on Ye Susu's face, and her body began to slowly shrink as tufts of azure fur appeared over her skin.

"Susu!" the azure-robed woman yelled in an alarmed manner as she sat up on the bed.

"Don't move!" Han Li warned in a cold voice, following which two bursts of azure light shot out of his hands before vanishing into the bodies of Ye Susu and her mother, upon which the two of them were instantly immobilized.

"What are you doing, you human scum?!" Elder Qiu roared in a furious voice as she pounced at him from behind, but Han Li didn't even spare her a glance as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing five translucent threads of light that vanished into her body in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, she was also completely immobilized, and despite her best efforts, she wasn't able to lift even a single finger.

Meanwhile, Han Li released a burst of crimson light into the array on the ground with his other hand, and the array immediately lit up once again.

Countless strands of crimson light surged out of it before wrapping themselves around Ye Susu and her mother, forming a crimson bridge between them.

In the next instant, Han Li appeared beside the azure-robed woman in the blink of an eye, then rested a palm down upon her forehead.

A burst of crimson light shot out of the palm of his hand before surging into the azure-robed woman's body, and the azure bloodline patterns reappeared over her skin, only to immediately dim significantly.

The burst of crimson light then flowed out of the azure-robed woman's body, carrying some of her bloodline power as it surged into Ye Susu's body.

The bloodline patterns on Ye Susu's body also reappeared, and her body returned to normal, while the tufts of fox fur quickly faded away.

Not only that, but the burst of crimson light was also rapidly replenishing the energy that she had expended from operating the array, and some color quickly returned to her cheeks.

After that, the mobility of the trio was restored at Han Li's behest, and the azure-robed woman stood up from the bed.

Perhaps it was because she had been bedridden for too long, but she was a little unsteady on her feet, and Ye Susu hurriedly grabbed onto her.

"Mother, this is the Senior Han that I was telling you about. Senior Han, this is my mother, the chief of our Azure Fox Tribe," Ye Susu introduced.

"It's a pleasure to meet you, Fellow Daoist Han. My name is Ye Luo. Thank you for eradicating the frost poison in my body and restoring Susu's Azure Fox bloodline. Words cannot express my gratitude to you. If you need anything from our Azure Fox Tribe, feel free to let me know," the azure-robed woman said in a serious manner.

Elder Qiu's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but she didn't say anything.

"There's no need to thank me. I'm currently a guest staying in Azure Fox City, so it's only right that I help my host in her time of need," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"Your powers are truly unfathomable, Senior Han. Not only did you eradicate the frost poison in my mother's body with ease, you also returned my bloodline power to me. How did you do that?" Ye Susu asked with a look of admiration in her eyes.

"I know a thing or two when it comes to bloodline powers. On top of that, you were very fortunate in that the bloodline power in your body hadn't completely faded away. Otherwise, even I wouldn't have been able to save you," Han Li explained in an ambiguous manner.

"Thank you for saving our chief and young mistress, Fellow Daoist Han, but how were you able to enter this place? This has always been a secret area of our Azure Fox Tribe," Elder Qiu said, and even though she was offering words of gratitude, her tone was very confrontational and abrasive.

"This is Elder Ye Qiu of our tribe, Fellow Daoist Han. Elder Qiu, don't be so rude! Fellow Daoist Han does not deserve to be interrogated after everything that he's done for us!" Ye Luo scolded.

"It's fine, it's only natural for Elder Qiu to have such a reaction. I'm quite well versed in detection secret techniques, and I was taking a stroll when I detected some particularly violent energy fluctuations coming from this place. Hence, I decided to do some investigating, and I barged in uninvited after witnessing the urgency of the situation," Han Li explained with a smile.

"I see. Thank heavens Senior Han was able to get here in a timely manner," Ye Susu said with a hint of lingering fear in her eyes.

"All of this was caused by you! How could you be so rash? If Fellow Daoist Han hadn't saved us, the consequences would've been unimaginable!" Ye Luo scolded.

Ye Susu lowered her head upon hearing this, but there was a pout on her face, and she clearly didn't feel like she had done anything wrong.

Ye Luo was naturally not very pleased to see this, but she didn't scold Ye Susu any further, presumably not wanting to do so in Han Li's presence.

"Susu, take Fellow Daoist Han back to his residence. I'll pay you a visit in person tomorrow, Fellow Daoist Han," Ye Luo said.

"In that case, I'll be taking my leave now," Han Li replied as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

Ye Luo returned the salute, while Elder Qiu continued to observe him with a cold look of distrust in her eyes.

Han Li naturally didn't care about how Elder Qiu regarded him, and he turned and made his way outside, immediately followed by Ye Susu.

Before long, the two of them had reached the surface, and Han Li stopped in his tracks as he looked down at the plots of spirit farmland in the basin.

"I noticed this place as I was passing through. I can see that there are some spirit medicines of a very high caliber growing here. Has your Azure Fox Tribe always been adept in nurturing spirit plants?" Han Li asked.

It seemed that a huge weight had been lifted from Ye Susu's shoulders in the wake of her mother's recovery, and she was a lot more relaxed as she smiled and said, "I'm surprised that you're able to see into the plots of farmland with all of these restrictions in place, Senior Han. Then again, with your powers, I suppose I shouldn't be surprised that you can see through these restrictions."

Han Li merely smiled and offered no response.

"I don't mean to brag, but when it comes to growing spirit medicines, our Azure Fox Tribe is the undisputed number one authority in the entire Golden Origin Mountain Range! Do you require any spirit plants for your cultivation, Senior Han? Here's a list of all of the spirit plants grown in our tribe. If you need any of them, feel free to tell me," Ye Susu said as she offered a jade slip to Han Li.

"I am indeed looking for some spirit plants," Han Li replied as he accepted the jade slip, then inspected its contents with his spiritual sense before giving a slight nod.

He had already assessed all of the plots of spirit farmland, and the jade slip did indeed contain an exhaustive list of everything growing here, so Ye Susu hadn't tried to hide anything from him.

"Please forgive Elder Qiu for her cold attitude, Senior Han. Her parents and her two brothers were all killed by human cultivators, so she's always harbored deep enmity toward human cultivators, and she's not targeting you," Ye Susu explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

This did indeed explain things, but it wasn't like Elder Qiu's frosty attitude had weighed on his mind at all anyway.

With that, the two of them promptly departed.

......

Inside the underground stone chamber, Ye Qiu cast several layers of restrictions one after another.

Ye Luo heaved a faint sigh upon seeing this, then said, "Elder Qiu, I know that you sorely resent human cultivators, but Fellow Daoist Han has helped us on more than one occasion, so please try to rein in your animosity. At the very least, try not to be so rude in his presence."

"Do you think he's helping us out of the kindness of his heart?" Ye Qiu sneered.

"What's that supposed to mean?" Ye Luo asked as her brows furrowed slightly.

Chapter 1010: History

"He proclaimed that he came here after sensing the energy fluctuations released by the array, but I don't think that's true. Even if his detection secret techniques really are so powerful that he can detect what was happening in here through multiple layers of restrictions, there's no way that the restrictions around the Wood God Basin would've failed to detect him upon his infiltration, yet those restrictions didn't register his intrusion at all.

“I suspect that he snuck into this place with Young Mistress, and he's been lurking in the shadows this entire time with unclear intentions," Ye Qiu speculated in a cold voice.

"That may be true, but that's all just speculation on your end. Even if Fellow Daoist Han did sneak into this place, he clearly doesn't harbor any animosity toward our tribe. Otherwise, he could've easily killed the three of us just now, and our tribe would be powerless to oppose him," Ye Luo said.

"If that's what you think, then I won't say anything further on this matter," Ye Qiu replied after a brief silence.

"Regardless of what his intentions are, the fact that he was able to eradicate the frost poison in my body so easily indicates that he's definitely far more powerful than us, so we cannot afford to make an enemy out of him, do you understand?" Ye Luo said in a serious manner.

"I do, but if I find out that he harbors any ill intentions toward our tribe, I'm not going to let him do as he pleases, even if it means having to give up my own life!" Ye Qiu replied with a cold expression.

Ye Luo gave her a gentle pat on the shoulder and didn't say anything further.

"You've only just had the frost poison in your body eradicated, so you should take some time to rest, Chief. I'll be taking my leave now," Ye Qiu declared before departing, and following her departure, Ye Luo sat back down onto the jade bed with her legs crossed.

The night passed by in an uneventful fashion.

The next morning, Ye Luo and Ye Susu visited Han Li's courtyard together, but Ye Qiu wasn't with them, while Weeping Soul was cultivating in the Flower Branch domain, so she wasn't present, either.

"Our Azure Fox City is quite secluded, and it can't compare with the other more developed cities of the Golden Origin Mountain Range. On top of that, there aren't any opulent residential areas in the city, so we can only offer this shabby courtyard for you to stay in," Ye Luo said in an apologetic manner.

After a day of rest, she was looking much better.

"This is perfect, I prefer this type of peaceful environment anyway," Han Li said with a smile as he invited the two of them into the room.

"I'm glad to hear that, Fellow Daoist Han. If you need anything from me, feel free to let me know," Ye Luo replied with a nod.

"Thank you, Chief. Now that you mention it, I would like to acquire some of the spirit plants grown by your tribe. Here's the list of things that I want," Han Li said as he pulled out a jade slip before offering it to Ye Luo.

On the way to the Golden Origin Mountain Range, he had been collecting ingredients required to refine a High Zenith Stage pill called the Cerulean Pill.

At the moment, he possessed a tremendous amount of wealth in the form of Immortal Origin Stones, as well as precious materials from the Gray Realm, the Devil Realm, and the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

He had already gathered most of the ingredients required to refine Cerulean Pills through purchases of exchanges using his Reincarnation Palace mask, and in a stroke of luck, all of the remaining ingredients could be found in Azure Fox City.

Ye Luo was already aware of the promise that Ye Susu had made to Han Li, but her expression still changed slightly upon witnessing the list enclosed in the jade slip.

"I understand that the spirit plants that I require are all of quite a high caliber and age, but rest assured, I'm not planning to acquire these spirit plants from your tribe free of compensation," Han Li said as he set a storage tool down onto the table.

Ye Luo briefly injected her spiritual sense into the storage tool to inspect its contents, and a hint of elation immediately appeared on her face, following which an embarrassed look surfaced in her eyes as she sighed, "I should be offering these spirit plants to you free of charge for you've done for my daughter and me, but recently, our tribe has been struggling financially, so I'm going to shamelessly accept this."

"Don't say that, it's only right that I compensate you for the fruits of your tribe's labors," Han Li replied with a wave of his hand.

"Susu, go and gather everything on Fellow Daoist Han's list," Ye Luo instructed as she handed the jade slip to Ye Susu, who gave an affirmative response before departing.

"Fellow Daoist Han, please pardon my intrusion, but may I ask for what purpose you've come to our Azure Fox City?" Ye Luo asked.

"Rest assured, Chief, I bear no ill will toward Azure Fox City. It's just that I like the safe and peaceful environment here, and I would like to cultivate in seclusion here for some time. Is that alright?" Han Li asked.

"That's it?" Ye Luo asked with a surprised expression.

"That's all. To be frank, your Azure Fox Tribe doesn't have anything else that can catch my interest, so you don't have to worry," Han Li replied with a casual wave.

Ye Luo had been carefully observing Han Li's expression this entire time, and she could tell that he wasn't lying. Hence, she was very relieved as she smiled and said, "I see, it appears that my concerns were unnecessary. If you only wish to cultivate in our city, then you're very much welcome to do so, and you can stay for as long as you like."

"Thank you, Chief. However, I want to ask you to keep my presence in your city a secret as that would be beneficial for both of us," Han Li said in a meaningful manner.

Ye Luo faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded in agreement.

Having made their intentions clear with each other, both of them were feeling more relaxed, and they began to chat about various aspects of the Golden Origin Mountain Range.

"Chief Ye, I read in some scriptures that there aren't many native demonic tribes in the Golden Origin Mountain Range, and that most of them moved in from outside of the mountain range. Your Azure Fox Tribe is adept in wood-attribute abilities and illusory techniques, which seems rather out of place here. Could it be that your tribe also moved into the mountain range from elsewhere?" Han Li asked.

"That's right, our tribe did indeed move into the mountain range from outside a very long time ago," Ye Luo replied with a nod.

"May I ask where your tribe came from?" Han Li asked.

"I'm not sure. There are no exact records of this in the scriptures in our tribe. I recall seeing a journal left behind by an ancestor of our tribe, stating that we came from the southern region of the Golden Origin Continent. However, there are no other records backing up that claim, so I'm unsure of its validity. Why do you ask this, Fellow Daoist Han?" Ye Luo asked with a puzzled expression.

"Many years ago, I encountered another tribe of fox beings with the Liu surname, and I felt like your two tribes were rather similar, so I was curious," Han Li explained with a smile.

Ye Luo's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this.

"A fox tribe with the Liu surname? According to our tribe's scriptures, not long after we settled here, a female ancestor by the name of Liu Mei arrived in our tribe, and she was the one who bestowed upon us our spirit plant nurturing techniques. Come to think of it, both Susu and I are descendants of this female ancestor.

“However, Ancestor Liu Mei never mentioned anything about her life, so she was an extremely mysterious figure in our tribe's history. Could it be that she had some ties with this fox tribe that you speak of?"

"I'm afraid I don't know the answer to that question. I've had no in-depth interactions with this other fox tribe, so I don't know if they're also adept in nurturing spirit plants," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

A hint of disappointment appeared on Ye Luo's face upon hearing this, but she was still unwilling to give up, and she asked, "Would you be able to tell me about that fox tribe in more detail, Fellow Daoist Han?"

Han Li saw no reason to refuse, so he gave her a brief recount of his encounter with that other fox tribe during his journey through the primordial land, but of course, he intentionally omitted some of the more sensitive details.

After hearing Han Li's story, Ye Luo fell silent with a contemplative look on her face.

Right at this moment, Ye Susu flew in from outside, then handed a storage tool to Han Li as she said, "All of the spirit plants on your list are in there, Senior Han."

Han Li inspected the contents of the storage tool briefly with his spiritual sense, following which he gave a pleased nod.

"Thank you for telling me all of this, Fellow Daoist Han. We've already taken up far too much of your time, so we'll be taking our leave now," Ye Luo said as she stood up before promptly departing with Ye Susu.

Han Li escorted them out of the room before closing the door.

Han Li stood in silence for a moment, then suddenly asked, "What do you think of Chief Ye Luo? Was she being truthful with me just now?"

As soon as his voice trailed off, a door of light appeared beside him, and Weeping Soul stepped out of it.

"Chief Ye Luo has a very pure soul, and she's not one to tell lies often. I've been carefully observing her soul fluctuations this entire time, and there were no abnormalities, so she was telling the truth," Weeping Soul replied.

"Good," Han Li replied with a pleased nod.

Following her awakening, Weeping Soul's law abilities had taken significant strides, allowing her to peer into the hearts of others and determine whether someone was telling the truth by assessing their soul fluctuations, and that saved him a lot of trouble.

"Master, was that other fox tribe you were referring to the Heavenly Fox Tribe where Sister Liu Le'er currently is?" Weeping Soul asked.

"That's right. I wanted to see if there was some connection between the two, Han Li confirmed with a nod."

"Does that mean that the Azure Fox Tribe is a branch of the Heavenly Fox Tribe?" Weeping Soul asked.

"Fox 3 possesses the bloodline of the Heavenly Fox Tribe, and I can sense that the Azure Fox bloodline of Ye Susu and Ye Luo are rather similar to Fox 3's bloodline. That, in conjunction with this revelation about Liu Mei, tells me that the two tribes are most likely connected," Han Li mused.

"You were helped by the Heavenly Fox Tribe in the past, so I'm assuming that part of the reason you've decided to stay here is so that you can protect the Azure Fox Tribe, right, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"That was part of my consideration, but I can only protect them for the time being, so I'll leave some things behind to help them protect themselves when I leave. For now, I have to go into seclusion to begin cultivating right away. I've had a lingering sense of foreboding this entire time recently, as if there's some danger approaching, so I have to be prepared," Han Li replied.

Chapter 1011: An Incredible Man

Weeping Soul's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and she replied, "Your instincts have always been quite accurate, so it looks like I'll need to go into seclusion as well. I may not be able to advance my cultivation base any further, but at the very least, I have to recover to my former peak."

Han Li didn't waste any more time with words as he began to set up some restrictions around the courtyard.

After that, he set up some more restrictions inside the courtyard and in his and Weeping Soul's rooms. Only after ensuring that all of the appropriate preparations had been completed did the two of them go into seclusion in their respective rooms.

Han Li entered the secret chamber in his room before sitting down with his legs crossed, and after meditating for half a day to prime himself into the best possible condition, he flipped a hand over to summon his silver cauldron.

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, which swept over the ground to produce all of the ingredients required to refine Cerulean Pills.

He then opened his mouth to release a Essence Fire Raven, which transformed into a silver flame beneath the cauldron, and from there, he began tossing ingredients into the cauldron one after another.

......

At this moment, Ye Luo, Ye Qiu, and Ye Susu were gathered in a conference hall in Azure Fox City.

"Are you really going to allow that human cultivator to take up residence in our city, Chief? I don't think that's a good idea. We don't know where he came from, and he's a human cultivator. Most of our brethren harbor deep animosity toward humans, so the decision to allow him to stay in the city will inevitably be met with resistance," Ye Qiu said with tightly furrowed brows.

"Rest assured, Elder Qiu, Fellow Daoist Han is only staying in our city to cultivate in seclusion, so he won't be out and about much. On top of that, he asked me to keep his presence in our city a secret, so we can just declare to everyone that he's already left our city," Ye Luo replied.

"But he's still a human, and an extremely powerful one at that! Keeping him in our city is like allowing a sword to constantly hang over our heads!" Ye Qiu protested.

"Fellow Daoist Han has helped us so much, and all he's asking is to stay in our city to cultivate in peace. It would be far too petty of us to refuse such a small request," Ye Luo said.

"I don't think Senior Han and Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul are bad people, Elder Qiu. On top of that, our Azure Fox Tribe has been in constant danger in recent years, so we could really use a powerful ally like him," Ye Susu chimed in.

"In that case, I suppose I have no choice but to agree. However, his origins are still unclear, so I think we should arrange for some people to conduct surveillance on him in secret," Ye Qiu acquiesced.

"Alright, I'll leave that to you then, Elder Qiu. Don't forget that Fellow Daoist Han is adept in detection secret techniques, so make sure to be extra careful that you don't let him find out what you're doing," Ye Luo replied with a nod.

"You can count on me," Ye Qiu replied before quickly departing.

......

Three years later.

Han Li remained seated in his secret chamber, and right at this moment, the lid of his silver cauldron flew up to hover in mid-air at his behest.

Immediately thereafter, five blue pills flew out from within before landing in a jade vial.

Each pill was around the size of a longan, and they were as blue as the sky, giving off a rich medicinal aroma.

At this point, there were already dozens of jade vials placed beside him, and a strong medicinal aroma could be smelled even through the vials.

A pleased look appeared on Han Li's face at the sight of these jade vials.

These Cerulean Pills were the first High Zenith Stage pills that he had refined, and in the beginning, he had experienced much difficulty, but thanks to his Mantra Treasured Axis and his past pill refinement experience, the success rate quickly began to climb.

He swept a sleeve through the air to stow his cauldron and Essence Fire Raven away, following which he tipped a Cerulean Pill out of one of the jade vials before devouring it.

Radiant golden light rose up from his body, illuminating the entire secret chamber a bright, golden color.

......

Over a hundred flew in the blink of an eye.

A white-robed middle-aged man was seated on a golden dragon throne in a majestic palace in the Golden Origin Immortal Palace.

It was none other than Palace Master Dongfang Bai, and at this moment, his gaze was focused on a figure standing before him in the palace. Even though there was no trace of anger on his face, the person being observed was still feeling extremely tense and uneasy.

The figure standing in the palace wasn't particularly tall, but he was quite handsome. It was a young boy dressed in a colorful robe, and he appeared to be no more than fourteen to fifteen years of age, but he possessed a pair of eyes that looked as if they had seen far more than just a decade and a half in this world would allow.

"Elder Tao, I didn't acquire this body for you so you can sit around and do nothing. Why is it that you still haven't tracked down that Han Li even though it's already been over a century?" Dongfang Bai asked.

"Ever since Han Li left the Heavenly Pine Temple, he immediately went into hiding, seemingly aware that we would go after him. He hasn't appeared in any of the major cities in the immortal region, so he must be hiding in some secluded place, making it very difficult to track him down," the young boy hurriedly explained.

It hadn't been long since Tao Ji possessed this new body, and he was still rather unaccustomed to his own tender and child-like voice.

Dongfang Bai's expression darkened slightly upon hearing, making Tao Ji feel even more uneasy, and he hurriedly continued, "The fact that he hasn't appeared in any major cities means that he won't have been able to access any long-distance teleportation arrays. Hence, he must still be in our Golden Origin Immortal Region. Just give me some more time, and I'll be sure to track him down."

Dongfang Bai's eyes narrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he was just about to say something when his expression changed ever so slightly.

Right at this moment, a servant rushed into the palace, informing Dongfang Bai that some visitors had come to see him.

Dongfang Bai instructed them to come in, and the palace gates were opened, following which a thin, gray-haired elderly man and a black-robed man with a fearsome-looking blade on his back stepped inside.

The two of them made their way over to Tao Ji's side, then bowed in unison as they greeted, "We pay our respects to Palace Master Dongfang."

"No need for formalities. How did the investigation go?" Dongfang Bai asked.

The black-robed man and the elderly man exchanged a glance with each other, and the latter gestured for the former to deliver his report first.

Hence, the black-robed man reported, "Upon arriving at the Heavenly Pine Temple, I discovered that all signs of battle had already been intentionally destroyed, and the residual law power fluctuations in the area had also been erased."

"Does that mean you weren't able to find out anything, Hei Dao?" Dongfang Bai asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Even though all signs of battle had been erased, the same didn't apply to the residual souls of the Immortal Palace cultivators who had perished on that day. Hence I was able to use some ghostly secret techniques to harvest some soul fragments, and from their memory snippets, I was able to piece together the battle.

“What's particularly worthy of note is that he's an extremely accomplished bodily refinement cultivator, having already opened over nine hundred profound acupoints," Hei Dao replied.

"Over nine hundred profound acupoints... No wonder the Bipolar Yin Yang Array completely failed to contain him..." Tao Ji murmured to himself.

"You were the one who gathered everyone to hunt him down, were you not, Elder Tao? How did you not know about this in advance? Incompetent fool!" Dongfang Bai spat through gritted teeth.

"That was... indeed an oversight on my part," Tao Ji stammered.

He had underestimated Han LI from the very beginning, and by the time that he realized just how powerful Han Li was, he was too busy running for his life to make an assessment of Han Li's powers.

"Were you able to find out anything else?" Dongfang Bai asked.

"I also found out that he possesses at least three types of true spirit bloodlines, namely that of the Giant Mountain Ape, the True Dragon, and the Kun Peng. That's what granted him the power to overcome the Bipolar Yin Yang Array so easily. By my estimates, his physical prowess is on par with that of a Great Encompassment Profound Immortal," Hei Dao replied.

"Now that I think about it, I recall detecting the power of the Lightning Bird in his body while he was pursuing me. That must've been another true spirit bloodline," Tao Ji hurriedly said.

"Interesting. So he's a human with four true spirit bloodlines in his body, all of which belong to top-tier true spirits... How has he been able to avoid bloodline backlash?" Dongfang Bai mused with slightly furrowed brows.

While listening to Hei Dao's report, the gray-haired elderly man was constantly looking back and forth through a collection of around a dozen jade slips in his hands, seemingly trying to pick out something.

"He's also using a time-attribute cultivation art that can conjure up a golden wheel capable of slowing his targets down to a crawl. It was an extremely terrible feeling, like even my thoughts had slowed down," Tao Ji added.

"So he's essentially a Great Encompassment Stage Profound Immortal with a High Zenith Stage cultivation base, and he possesses multiple true spirit bloodlines and time law powers... How is it possible that a single person can possess all four of these traits? It's downright incredible!

“Such a man should've been vastly renowned across the entire immortal region, how is it possible that he's managed to keep such a low profile? Are you sure the information that you have on him is accurate?" Dongfang Bai asked.

If he really was in possession of that vial, then there was a chance that he could make such rapid progress in his cultivation base in such a short time, but there should've been no way for him to have become such a multi-faceted powerhouse!

Right at this moment, the gray-haired elderly man suddenly looked up from the jade slips in his hands.

"Do you have something to offer, Elder Lü Yun?" Dongfang Bai asked.

"I've found some interesting things during my travels over all these years. Perhaps they can help you gain a better understanding of this Han Li, Palace Master Dongfang," the elderly man replied, then respectfully offered up seven or eight jade slips that he had selected.

Chapter 1012: Culmination of Coincidences

Dongfang Bai's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of golden light, which captured all of the jade slips before carrying them to him.

As he examined the contents of the jade slip, a look of bewilderment appeared on his face, slowly becoming more and more pronounced.

Moments later, he set down the final jade slip as he asked with a grim expression, "Are you certain that all of these jade slips are describing the same person?"

"I've sent out all of my spies this past century, Palace Master Dongfang. They may not be the most capable fighters, but they can definitely be relied upon when it comes to gathering information.

“We began our investigation in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, and we discovered that Han Li had already appeared in their line of sight back when they were hunting down Baili Yan of the Blaze Dragon Dao. However, at the time, he was still going by the alias of Li Feiyu," Lü Yun reported.

"That was also when my son was killed by him," Tao Ji said with a pained expression.

"The Blaze Dragon Dao has the Mantra Axis Scripture, which is a time-attribute cultivation art, so that must be when he first began cultivating time law powers," Dongfang Bai mused.

"That's right. From that point onward, the name of Li Feiyu has sprung up several more times, but the information has been quite vague each time, indicating that he's been intentionally covering his own tracks. On top of that, a man by the name of Li Han has also made some appearances, and he possesses some traits that are identical to Han Li's, so it's very likely that Li Han was also an alias of his," Lü Yun replied with a nod.

"How is that possible? According to the information in these jade slips, Han Li has traveled across the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, the Black Mountain Immortal Region, the Black Soil Immortal Region, and now the Golden Origin Immortal Region within the short span of just a few thousand years, and on top of that, all of the major events that took place in those immortal regions during this time seem to have had something to do with him," Dongfang Bai mused with a perplexed expression.

"According to my investigation, there's some evidence to indicate that he played a role in a series of significant events, including the fall of the Blaze Dragon Dao, the emergence of the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, and the reappearance of the True Mantra Sect ruins. On top of that, he seems to have also played significant roles in the deaths of Gongshu Tian and Gongshu Jiu," Lü Yun reported.

A grim look appeared on Dongfang Bai's face upon hearing this, and he asked, "So where did he go after the True Mantra Sect ruins? Why has he suddenly appeared in our Golden Origin Immortal Region?"

"Please take a look at this first, Palace Master," Lü Yun replied as he offered up another jade slip.

"Isn't this a report from Dao Ancestor Feng Qingshui's trip to the Gray Realm?" Dongfang Bai asked with a perplexed expression.

"Many of the people that previously appeared in the True Mantra Sect ruins also appeared in the Gray Realm during the time that Dao Ancestor Feng Qingshui was there. Hence, my assumption is that Han Li most likely went there as well, then somehow ended up in the Devil Realm before returning to the Immortal Realm," Lü Yun speculated, and everyone in the palace fell into deep thought after hearing this.

"This man seems to have some ties with the Reincarnation Palace, and not only has been able to safely travel across multiple immortal regions, his cultivation base has been progressing rapidly during this time. What do you all think?" Dongfang Bai asked.

"The fact that he's been able to make such rapid strides in his cultivation base indicates that he's not just some average itinerant cultivator with no backing. His ties with both the Reincarnation Palace and the devil race serve as further confirmation of this," Hei Dao analyzed.

If Han Li were to hear this assessment of him, he would be left completely speechless. Somehow, these people had led themselves completely astray.

Does that mean that I've made an enemy out of someone that I can't afford to mess with?

With that in mind, a remorseful look appeared on Tao Ji's face.

After a long silence, Dongfang Bai stood up from his chair, then began slowly pacing from side to side with tightly furrowed brows as he contemplated how to proceed from here.

Some time later, he stopped in his tracks, then turned to Tao Ji's trio as he said, "Regardless of his cultivation base or status, we have to continue our investigation, given that that thing is concerned. Once you track him down, make sure not to make any rash moves. Just report back to me, and I'll plan out the next steps."

"What happens if a conflict arises?" Lü Yun asked.

"If that happens, then feel free to strike him down. Of course, do your best to capture him alive. Once we find out the whereabouts of that thing, we can take him back to the Nine Origins Temple before making a decision on what to do with him," Dongfang Bai replied.

Lü Yun's trio was rather hesitant upon hearing this, but they still gave a collective affirmative response.

"Remember to keep this matter a secret. If anyone leaks this information, and it reaches the ears of those immortal envoys from the Heavenly Court, there will be dire consequences to suffer," Dongfang Bai warned with a cold expression, and the trio hurriedly nodded in response.

Following their departure, Dongfang Bai continued to pace in the palace, feeling rather uneasy.

This was the first time that he had met someone as strange as Han Li, someone with such incredible powers and presumably an extremely powerful background, having played roles in so many significant events, but had somehow simultaneously managed to keep such a low profile.

On top of that, this was only the information that they currently had on Han Li, and there was a very good chance that it was only the tip of the iceberg.

What was truly terrifying to him was that such a person still wasn't under much scrutiny from the Heavenly Court.

......

In the Middle Earth Immortal Region.

There were a series of dark, crimson clouds hovering in the air within an unknown space.

There was a faint odor of blood emanating from the dark clouds, and a series of ominous-looking black buildings could be seen littered throughout the area.

The crimson clouds were hanging up in the sky in layers, and the higher one went, the denser the clouds they would encounter.

Standing below the crimson clouds was a white archway that was several thousand feet tall, upon which the words "Immortal Prison" were engraved in huge crimson characters.

Enshrouded within the crimson clouds not far away from the archway was a black palace with an octagonal bell roughly the size of a cow's head hanging from each corner of its roof, and the bells were swaying and chiming occasionally on their own, even though there was a complete absence of wind.

Whenever the bells chimed, a layer of faint golden light would ripple through the air, scattering some of the heavy bloody odor in the air.

Stationed at the entrance of the palace were two warriors clad in suits of black armor, both of which were extremely imposing and stood at over ten feet tall. One of them was wielding a giant ax, while the other was wielding a huge halberd, and their bloodshot eyes gave them a very fearsome appearance.

The gates of the palace were tightly shut, and hanging above its entrance was a giant black plaque that had the words "Judgment Hall" inscribed upon it in red characters.

There were two rows of red pillars standing alongside each other inside the palace, hanging upon which were a series of black metal tablets that laid out various different punishments for different crimes.

The interior of the palace was rather dimly lit, with a series of braziers with dark red flames burning inside them suspended up high.

Deep within the palace was a large, black, metal table, and standing in front of it with their back facing the palace gates was a tall figure that was rather strange in appearance. They possessed hands and feet that were far larger than that of the average person, and the figure currently had one hand resting on the table, while a jade slip was held in their other hand.

Their upper body was bared to reveal their fiery-red skin, and there were circles of strange patterns visible on their body.

On top of that, their hair was also bright red, with small flames occasionally springing out of it.

If Han Li were present, he would immediately be able to identify this man as one of the five disciples of Patriarch Miro, namely the traitor, Qi Mozi.

Qi Mozi slowly set down the jade slip in his hand, then sighed to himself, "How unfortunate that you had to suffer such a terrible fate, Hot Flame..."

Right at this moment, a fiery human face appeared within a nearby brazier, and it remarked, "It looks like he was always the disciple that you cared for the most."

"All I wanted was for him to stay far away from this mess, but he was ultimately still swept up in it in the end. I was never very fond of Chi Rong as a disciple, but he did enter the True Mantra Sect ruins for my sake. Who could've imagined that the two of them would both end up losing their lives in the Gray Realm?" Qi Mozi sighed.

"So what if they died? They still couldn't find the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, so their deaths were completely pointless," the face in the brazier sneered in an abrasive voice.

"That's not true, their deaths were not in vain. Prior to entering the Gray Realm, Chi Rong sent a message back to me, mentioning a very... strange individual. There's a very good chance that he was the biggest beneficiary to this venture into the True Mantra Sect ruins, and it's very likely that he's in possession of the complete Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra," Qi Mozi countered.

"Who is this person? Where is he right now?" the face in the brazier hurriedly asked.

"His name is Han Li, and he's recently been sighted in the Golden Origin Immortal Region," Qi Mozi replied.

"Looks like it's about time that I go out for some exercise. I must say, I'm really missing the air outside after staying in this Immortal Prison for so long. Let's make a deal: I capture this man for you, and you let me do whatever I want to an area of my choosing. I've already picked out an area, it's just an inconspicuous place in a lower realm, so it won't cause you any trouble," the face in the brazier proposed as it rose up into the air.

Chapter 1013: Qi Mozi’s Plan

Qi Mozi paid no heed to the fiery face as he continued to ponder the situation in silence, following which he made a casual grabbing motion toward the brazier, pulling out the fiery face along with a fiery figure.

After the figure was pulled out of the brazier, it gradually took on a substantial form, one that was identical in appearance to Qi Mozi.

A burst of fire emerged over Qi Mozi's hand, and the aura of the fiery figure beside him swelled drastically until it was almost on par with his own.

"I'm going in person this time, you stay behind to oversee the Immortal Prison for me," Qi Mozi instructed.

"What if someone..."

The fiery figure didn't get a chance to fully articulate his question before he was cut off by Qi Mozi.

"This is the Immortal Prison, no one's going to say anything here. I'll only be taking one person with me, and I'll return as quickly as possible."

"Who are you taking if you're not even taking me?" the fiery figure asked in a perplexed manner.

"An old acquaintance of mine," Qi Mozi replied with a faint smile, then made his way out of the palace.

All of a sudden, a burst of flames rose up over his entire body, and he sped toward a golden space neighboring the crimson clouds as a blazing fireball.

......

Sixty years flew by in the blink of an eye.

There was a peaceful courtyard in Azure Fox City.

The light of the morning sun was filtered through the branches of a tree, casting a series of fragmented shadows onto the ground.

A group of children were joyfully running back and forth along a little path, holding colorful paper windmills in their hands.

The sound of their playful laughter could be heard in the neighboring courtyard, and at his moment, Weeping Soul was seated on a stone chair inside the courtyard, resting her chin on one hand while listening to the sounds of the playing children outside.

Ever since she attained the ability to look directly into the hearts of others, she had become very fond of hearing the laughter of children. Their pure and simple joy never failed to put her in a good mood.

Right at this moment, she suddenly turned around as Han Li emerged from the room behind her, clearly in very high spirits.

"You've come out of seclusion so soon, Master. Have you already made a breakthrough?" Weeping Soul asked with a surprised expression.

"I did. Having already opened so many profound acupoints, I was able to progress very quickly in my cultivation of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra," Han Li replied with a smile.

At this point, it was only a matter of time before he reached the late-High Zenith Stage.

"Congratulations, Master!" Weeping Soul said with an elated expression.

"Have there been any abnormal occurrences in the Azure Fox Tribe during my seclusion?" Han Li asked.

"Nothing that I could see. After their chief made a full recovery, the morale of the entire tribe received a significant boost, and even the Golden Horse Sect hasn't dared to make any moves. I was worried that you would cause too much of a commotion during your breakthrough and attract a lot of attention, but even I didn't detect your breakthrough," Weeping Soul replied.

"There wasn't much of a bottleneck for me to overcome for this breakthrough. On top of that, I was cultivating in seclusion in the Flower Branch domain, and I set up an aura concealment array at the entrance of the domain, so that's why there wasn't any commotion. However, I won't be able to make my late-High Zenith Stage breakthrough in the Flower Branch domain, so I'll have to find some other place next time," Han Li said with a smile.

While Han Li and Weeping Soul were chatting with each other, there was a heated argument raging in the conference hall elsewhere in the city.

"I've always felt like that human cultivator was suspicious, Chief. Surely the Immortal Palace wouldn't be spreading false information. He's an evil cultivator who kills mortals in order to further his own cultivation! We cannot allow someone like him to continue to remain in our city!" Ye Qiu said in an urgent manner.

"Elder Qiu is right. Humans have always been very sly and cunning creatures, so we can't afford to take any chances here," another elder chimed in.

There were several people behind him who remained silent, but they were also nodding in agreement.

"There must be some misunderstanding here. Senior Han's aura is one of righteousness and tranquility, completely unlike the aura of an evil cultivator who would do something so heinous. He's definitely not the wanted fugitive that the Immortal Palace is looking for! If he really were such a terrible person, then he wouldn't have saved me and my mother!" Ye Susu protested vehemently.

It was true that Han Li had helped the Azure Fox Tribe, and conflicted looks appeared on the faces of all of the Azure Fox beings upon hearing this.

"You don't know just now cunning humans can be, Young Mistress. No one knows what his objectives are. Who knows if this isn't all just part of a long-term, sinister plan of his? Even if he bears no ill intent, we still can't afford to keep him. If we're caught harboring a wanted fugitive of the Immortal Palace, the consequences will be catastrophic!" Ye Qiu sighed.

"Indeed. If the Immortal Palace finds out that that human cultivator is staying here, our entire city would be razed to the ground," another elder sighed.

"We can't endanger the safety of our entire tribe for an outsider!"

"Please reconsider, Chief!"

"Everyone, Senior Han has done our tribe a great kindness, are we going to repay his kindness with ingratitude?" Ye Susu frantically yelled.

The entire hall immediately fell silent as guilty looks appeared on everyone's faces.

Right at this moment, a gentle voice suddenly rang out.

"I am aware of everyone's concerns."

Everyone immediately turned to the woman on the main chair in the conference hall upon hearing this, and it was none other than Ye Luo.

"Regardless of whether Senior Han has committed the crimes claimed by the Immortal Palace or not, it still doesn't change the fact that he has helped our Azure Fox Tribe in the past, so we cannot turn on him," Ye Luo said in a calm manner.

Ye Susu hurriedly nodded in agreement, but before she had a chance to say anything, Ye Luo continued, "However, now that Senior Han is a wanted fugitive of the Immortal Palace, we cannot allow him to continue staying in our city. Otherwise, it would be detrimental to both him and our tribe."

Ye Susu's face fell slightly upon hearing this.

Even though she was very grateful to Han Li, she knew that her mother was right, and she had simply been stubbornly denying the reality. Now that her mother had spoken, she had no choice but to accept this outcome.

Everyone nodded in relief and agreement upon hearing this.

"Susu, you were the one who brought Senior Han to our city, so you'll have to be the one to discuss this matter with him," Ye Luo said.

Ye Susu opened her mouth to say something, but ultimately remained silent and merely nodded in response.

"Let me go instead, I don't think it's safe to allow Young Mistress to go and see him," Ye Qiu hurriedly interjected.

"Senior Han is a benefactor of our Azure Fox Tribe, and the entwinement of his fate with our tribe started with Susu, so she should be the one to see things through to the end," Ye Luo said with a shake of her head.

"Leave it to me, Elder Qiu," Susu chimed in in agreement.

"Fine, you can go, but I'll come with you," Ye Qiu sighed.

Shortly thereafter, two streaks of light descended outside the peaceful courtyard that Han Li was staying in, and the children that were playing outside immediately gathered around Ye Susu, clamoring for her attention.

However, Ye Susu was in no mood to play with them, so she sent them away to play on their own before making her way over to the courtyard and knocking on its doors.

"Come in," Han Li called out from inside, and Ye Susu and Ye Qiu entered the courtyard to discover Han Li and Weeping Soul seated at the stone table, chatting with each other over some tea.

"Senior Han..." Ye Susu began, only for her voice to trail off into silence as she thought of her objective for this visit.

Ye Qiu stepped around Ye Susu to shield the latter behind her, following which she cast a wary gaze toward Han Li.

"Seeing as the two of you have come together, I'm assuming you haven't come to see me for private matters. Why don't you go ahead and state the purpose of your visit?" Han Li prompted as he took a glance at Ye Susu, paying no heed to Ye Qiu in the process.

Ye Qiu's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and she was just about to say something when Ye Susu raised a hand to stop her.

"Please pardon my abrupt visit, Senior Han. I've come here today..."

With that, Ye Susu informed Han Li of his current status as a wanted fugitive of the Immortal Palace, but made no mention of asking him to leave Azure Fox City.

After hearing what she had to say, an amused look appeared on Han Li's face as he mused, "I'm not sure if I should feel flattered that the Immortal Palace thinks so highly of me that they've fabricated these crimes just to justify my capture."

Weeping Soul also shook her head with a wry smile.

Ye Susu was very relieved to hear this, and a bright smile appeared on her face as she said, "I knew you weren't that type of person, Senior Han!"

Chapter 1014: Active Report

Ye Qiu's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and she decided that she had to speak up.

In her eyes, Ye Susu was still too naive, and she was far too trusting of Han Li. Seeing as Ye Susu hadn't asked them to leave, she would just have to do so in her stead.

"Seeing as the warrant for my capture has already reached Golden Rhinoceros City, it'll only be a matter of time before your Azure Fox Tribe is investigated. If I were to continue to stay here, that would only bring disaster upon your tribe, so I'm going to pack my things and leave right away," Han Li said in a serious manner.

Ye Qiu's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and she was at a loss for words. She was clearly not expecting such a response from Han Li, and a guilty look appeared on Ye Susu's face as she said, "I know in my heart that you're a good person, Senior Han, but..."

"There's no need to feel any guilt toward me. I've already stayed for quite some time in Azure Fox City, and it's about time that I left. Weeping Soul, go and pack our things, and we'll leave after you're done," Han Li said with a smile.

Weeping Soul gave an affirmative response before entering the room.

There weren't many things that had to be packed, but the restrictions that Han Li had set up had to be disassembled and recovered.

"Please forgive us, Senior Han. Our Azure Fox Tribe is but a small tribe that's completely powerless to resist the Immortal Palace, so we have no choice but to ask you to leave. Rest assured, we will be sure to keep your visit a secret," Ye Susu said as she extended a respectful curtsey.

"No. Go to Golden Rhinoceros City tomorrow morning and inform the Immortal Palace cultivators there of our stay in Azure Fox City. Make sure to report the precise time frame of our stay, and do not omit any information from them," Han Li said.

"What? What do you mean, Senior Han?" Ye Susu asked in an incredulous manner, hardly able to believe her own ears.

Ye Qiu's expression also changed slightly upon hearing this, and the enmity in her eyes slowly faded away.

"I'm saying that you need to report me to the Immortal Palace," Han Li explained.

"Are you saying that we should point them in the wrong direction?" Ye Susu asked.

"Once I leave Azure Fox City, I'll be continuing northward deeper into the Golden Origin Mountain Range. Make sure to tell them exactly that. Otherwise, a calamity will befall the Azure Fox Tribe," Han Li replied.

"I... I don't understand, Senior Han," Ye Susu said in a perplexed manner.

"Young Mistress, regardless of whether we report Senior Han or not, the Immortal Palace will definitely find out that he's been to our city. As opposed to waiting for them to come to us, Senior Han is instructing us to go and actively report to them. He's doing this in order to protect our Azure Fox Tribe," Ye Qiu explained.

"Once you report me to the Immortal Palace, they'll be sure to send people to investigate, and they'll only let your Azure Fox Tribe off the hook if you can offer them some accurate and useful information," Han Li said.

Only then did Ye Susu come to understand Han Li's intentions, and she was at a temporary loss for words.

"You are a noble man, Senior Han. Not only did you save our chief, you're also thinking in the best interests of our tribe. I feel ashamed to have thought so badly of you," Ye Qiu said as she extended a respectful bow.

"There's no need to be ashamed for anything, Elder Qiu. I've been able to enjoy a rare window of peace in Azure Fox City, so I should be the one thanking you," Han Li said.

Right at this moment, Weeping Soul returned to the courtyard before giving Han Li a slight nod.

On the cusp of parting ways, tears began to well up in Ye Susu's eyes as she asked, "Will we meet again, Senior Han?"

"Trouble follows me wherever I go, so it's best for us not to meet again," Han Li replied.

With that, he and Weeping Soul bade farewell to Ye Susu and Ye Qiu before flying away as two streaks of light, instantly vanishing out of sight, while Ye Susu stared off into the distance with a look of melancholy in her eyes.

"It's alright, Young Mistress, you'll meet again if fate deems it to be so," Ye Qiu consoled, and Ye Susu nodded in response as a faint smile appeared on her face.

......

The two streaks of light only flew northward for several thousand kilometers before descending onto a mountain to reveal Han Li and Weeping Soul.

"Aren't we stopping a little too close to Azure Fox City, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"Once the Azure Fox Tribe makes its report, the Immortal Palace will definitely send people to investigate. If they don't detect any traces of us nearby, then that'll still bring trouble to the Azure Fox Tribe," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"How thoughtful of you, Master," Weeping Soul praised with a smile.

"The Azure Fox Tribe may only be a small tribe, but its members are very kind and pure of heart, completely different from the fox beings that I've met in the past," Han Li said as a reminiscent look appeared in his eyes.

He couldn't help but wonder how Liu Le'er was currently doing in the primordial land.

"If you're so fond of the Azure Fox Tribe, then why didn't you help them out a little? At the very least, we can ensure that they won't be bothered by the likes of the Golden Horse Sect," Weeping Soul said.

"Right now, we are wanted fugitives of the Immortal Palace, so we can't establish any close ties with the Azure Fox Tribe. No matter what we leave behind, it could spell destruction for the tribe. I'll just have to come back at a later date when I'm no longer weighed down by such inhibitions," Han Li sighed.

The two of them lingered on the mountain until noon before Han Li summoned a green jade flying carriage, and the two of them continued flying toward the north atop the carriage.

......

Two days later.

Several dozen giant, golden battleships were hovering in the air above Azure Fox City, thousands of armored soldiers could be seen standing on the decks of the battleships.

Close to half of the city was shrouded under the shadows cast by the battleships, striking fear into the hearts of all of the Azure Fox beings.

At this moment, there were eight or nine figures in a peaceful courtyard in the city.

One of them was a white-robed, middle-aged man who was seated beside a stone table in the courtyard, staring absentmindedly at a vibrant flower with a contemplative look on his face.

Standing behind him were none other than Tao Ji and Hei Dao, and the former's brows were tightly furrowed as he asked, "Is this the courtyard that he was staying in?"

The Azure Fox beings standing behind them all nodded in response.

Ye Luo stepped forward before extending a slight curtsey, then said, "He was cultivating in seclusion for the entire duration of his stay, but for some reason, he suddenly departed unannounced two days ago. We only received word of the warrant for his capture from Golden Rhinoceros City yesterday, and we immediately reported the matter."

Meanwhile, Ye Susu was standing beside Ye Qiu with her lips tightly pursed.

"You were the one who brought that scoundrel back to your Azure Fox City, is that right?" Tao Ji asked as he turned a cold gaze toward Ye Susu.

Ye Susu shuddered slightly internally, but her expression remained unchanged as she calmly replied, "That's right. He saved my life, so I invited him to stay in our city. Never could I have imagined that he would be a wanted fugitive of the Immortal Palace..."

"If he left two days ago, then why did you only report him yesterday? Were you intentionally buying time for him to escape?" Tao Ji interrogated.

"Of course not, esteemed immortal envoy! We really did only receive word of this from Golden Rhinoceros City yesterday, and we immediately reported him without delay as soon as we found out about his status as a wanted fugitive," Ye Luo hurriedly replied in a fearful manner as she extended a deep bow, as did Ye Qiu and the others.

Ye Susu was also bowing down to Tao Ji, but internally, her heart was full of disdain. In her eyes, these Immortal Palace cultivators were extremely pretentious, as opposed to Han Li, who appeared a little cold and unapproachable, but was actually a very kind and thoughtful man.

"We'll see about that! Elder Lü should be back soon. If he doesn't discover any signs of Han Li traveling northward, then you'll be punished as his accomplices!" Tao Ji sneered.

Ye Qiu and the others were very anxious to hear this.

After all, the other Azure Fox beings didn't have as much trust in Han Li as Ye Susu did, and they were worried that Han Li hadn't actually traveled northward as he proclaimed, or that perhaps he hadn't left any tracks behind. If either of those proved to be true, then the Azure Fox Tribe would be in grave danger.

Right at this moment, Dongfang Bai suddenly turned to look directly at Ye Susu as he asked, "If he saved your life, then why did you report him? Are you not repaying his kindness with ingratitude?"

"Esteemed immortal envoy... I... We..."

An inexplicable sense of horror suddenly welled up in Ye Susu's heart in the face of his scrutiny, and she wasn't even able to muster up a complete sentence.

Right at this moment, a delicate hand reached out to grab onto hers.

Ye Susu knew that the hand belonged to her mother, and it instilled within her a sense of reassurance.

She had already thought of a response to this question, so after taking a moment to compose herself, she said, "While it's true that he was a benefactor of our Azure Fox Tribe, he's already been staying in our city for over a century, and we've unknowingly broken the laws of the immortal region by harboring him, so I think we've already more than repaid him for his kindness.

“If we refused to report him even after finding out that he's a wanted fugitive, then that would be an act of active defiance against the Immortal Palace, and we certainly wouldn't dare to do such a thing."

Dongfang Bai's expression remained unchanged after hearing this response, and he continued to scrutinize Ye Susu intently, trying to see any unnatural changes in her expression.

Chapter 1015: Genocide

At this point, Ye Susu had already composed herself, and she was meeting Dongfang Bai's gaze with a calm one of her own.

At the same time, she was recollecting everything that Han Li had told her prior to his departure, and her heart was filled with admiration. It seemed like he had predicted everything that would happen on this day, and all they had to do was follow his instructions.

Right at this moment, a streak of light descended into the courtyard, then faded to reveal Lü Yun.

"How did it go, Elder Lü?" Dongfang Bai asked.

"I detected some of Han Li's residual aura on a mountain several thousand kilometers north of here. It seems that he stopped there for a while, then got onto a flying carriage before continuing northward. From there, I also managed to detect more of his residual aura in other places, but it was all very faint, indicating that he employed some measures to conceal his own aura. I was in a hurry to get back here, so I only left some markings behind and didn't continue my search," Lü Yun replied as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute.

"Well done," Dongfang Bai said with a nod.

"In that case, it looks like they weren't lying," Tao Ji murmured with tightly furrowed brows.

Dongfang Bai took one final glance at Ye Susu, then said, "Let's go."

Immediately thereafter, he vanished from the spot, and Tao Ji and the others hurriedly departed as well.

In the blink of an eye, all that remained in the courtyard was the group of Azure Fox beings, and all of them were looking at each other in silence.

Ye Susu's palms were drenched in sweat, and she took a glance at her own mother before looking up at the enormous battleships in the sky, wondering exactly who Han Li was to have warranted the deployment of such a formidable army.

Tao Ji and the others appeared one after another on the deck of a battleship high up in the sky, and they discovered Dongfang Bai standing at the railing, looking down at Azure Fox City below.

As they approached him, he suddenly ordered, "Kill them all."

"What?" Tao Ji asked in a stunned voice, clearly not expecting such a cruel order.

From Dongfang Bai's perspective, it didn't matter whether the Azure Fox Tribe had allowed Han Li to escape or not. What was important to him was that information on Han Li's whereabouts had to be kept secret. Otherwise, if widespread attention was drawn to this matter, he wouldn't be able to claim the sole merit of recovering the Heaven Controlling Vial for himself.

"Yes, Palace Master!" Hei Dao replied as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Make sure to destroy everything. Otherwise, it could spell trouble for us if the Immortal Prison launches an investigation," Dongfang Bai added.

Hei Dao gave another affirmative response before departing.

"Elder Tao, Elder Lü, it would be too slow to go after him with the entire army, so the three of us will pursue him on our own," Dongfang Bai instructed.

Lü Yun accepted this arrangement without any hesitation, while Tao Ji was silent for a moment before ultimately also giving an affirmative response.

He had personally witnessed Han Li's terrifying powers, so he was hoping to bring along more people for the hunt. Of course, with Dongfang Bai getting personally involved, Tao Ji most likely wouldn't have to play any role in the hunt anyway, and even if he couldn't kill Han Li himself, witnessing Han Li's death in person would be the next best thing.

With a casual sweep of his sleeve, Dongfang Bai summoned a white flying boat that was around a hundred feet in length, one that was clearly a graded immortal treasure.

He rose up into the air before descending onto the flying boat, and Tao Ji and Lü Yun hurriedly followed suit.

After Lü Yun pointed out the direction for them to travel in, the flying boat sped away as a streak of white light, vanishing into the distance in a flash.

Meanwhile, the golden battleships above Azure Fox City began to glow radiantly, and all of the runes on their surfaces lit up as they descended upon the city.

At the same time, all of the offensive arrays on the ships were activated, releasing an all-encompassing destructive aura.

According to later reports, Azure Fox City was burned to the ground on this day during the course of a calamitous natural disaster.

......

Over half a year flew by in a flash.

There were three large rivers in the northern part of the Golden Origin Immortal Region named the Dragon River, the Yuan River, and the Water Ripple River. These three rivers converged at the foot of Comb Grate Mountain to form the Three River Lake, which was several thousand kilometers in size.

It was said that there were once several hundred mountains where the Three River Lake currently stood. Those mountains were connected to Comb Grate Mountain, and they were all part of the same mountain range, with quite a large immortal sect constructed upon it.

However, countless years ago, that immortal sect was completely destroyed during a large-scale battle, and most of the mountains here were also razed to the ground.

Over time, the three aforementioned rivers converged to this place, submerging all of the remnants of the mountains that once stood here.

Even though the sect was already long gone, there were still many buildings left behind by the sect, most of which were taken over by the Comb Flow Sect, which had only been established here for several hundred thousand years. After some renovations, the buildings were made to look new again.

It was said that there were some destroyed immortal abodes beneath the Three River Lake, and they were all still protected by arrays, so there was a chance that there were undiscovered treasures on the lakebed.

Following its establishment, the Comb Flow Sect took over the Three River Lake, incorporating it as part of the sect's territory. However, the sect wasn't a particularly powerful one, so it didn't dare to seal the river and claim sole ownership of it. Instead, they renovated some of the ruined immortal abodes on the lakebed into underwater abodes for cultivators to rent.

Cultivators of advanced cultivation bases naturally didn't find the residual world's origin qi in these water abodes appealing, but many True Immortals, particularly those using water-attribute cultivation arts, or cultivators cultivating water law powers were very fond of staying here.

The rent on these water abodes wasn't a huge source of revenue, but it was very steady and had supported the Comb Flow Sect over the course of many years.

On this day, a tall male cultivator with a rather unremarkable appearance arrived on Comb Grate Mountain, expressing a desire to rent a water abode to cultivate in.

The man was naturally none other than Han Li, and he was greeted by a benevolent-looking elderly administrator.

The elderly man didn't openly display any disdain toward Han Li, but he certainly wasn't impressed by Han Li's unremarkable appearance and aura.

"Are you looking to rent a water abode, esteemed guest? You certainly came right in the nick of time! Right now, there are only three vacant water abodes left in the entire Three River Lake. I'll fetch a map for you and point them out right away," the elderly man said with a smile.

"There's no need for that. I heard that there are around a dozen water abodes that are still yet to be opened in the lake, and I would like to choose one of them," Han Li said.

There were many water abodes in the Three River Lake, but most of them had already been developed, and only around a dozen of them remained sealed by powerful immortal restrictions, making them inaccessible to the Comb Flow Sect.

However, the Comb Flow Sect didn't hire any powerful cultivators to break these restrictions. Instead, anyone could rent those unopened water abodes for the same price required to stay in the other water abodes, but as for whether one could actually enter the water abode, that would be up to them.

On top of that, the one who opened the water abode would be able to claim everything within it, so long as what they were taking didn't compromise the structural integrity of the abode.

In the beginning, there were often cultivators who would come to rent these unopened water abodes, but the vast majority of them failed to access said water abodes. Among those who were able to enter the abodes, many of them perished inside, so only very few people were able to successfully open a water abode before successfully re-emerging with the treasures inside.

Even then, many of them were hunted down by itinerant cultivators who received word of their exploits, and they were killed for the treasures that they had obtained.

Generally speaking, those who left the territory of the Comb Flow Sect were left to fend for themselves, with the sect claiming no responsibility for their safety.

Of course, even if one were to fail to enter an unopened water abode, the rent that they had paid wouldn't be refunded to them. Hence, for a very long time, the Comb Flow Sect actually earned far more revenue from these unopened water abodes than from renting out opened water abodes.

After all, there was never a shortage of people in the cultivation world willing to take significant risks for potentially exorbitant rewards.

However, as time passed, most cultivators began to realize that this was not a wise endeavor, and it had already been a very long time since this administrator had encountered a risk-taker like Han Li.

"Certainly! Please wait here for a moment while I fetch you a map of all of our unopened water abodes," the elderly man said before turning to depart.

However, he then stopped in his tracks and asked, "By the way, may I ask your name, esteemed guest?"

"Han Li," Han Li casually replied.

"It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, Fellow Daoist Han," the elderly man replied with a nod before departing.

Shortly thereafter, he returned with an underwater map of the Three River Lake and spread it out onto the table before giving Han Li a brief rundown of the layout of all of the water abodes.

Chapter 1016: I'll be Back Soon

All of a sudden, Han Li pointed at a certain spot on the map as he asked, "This should be an unopened water abode, right?"

"That's right, but I should advise you not to attempt to access this water abode," the elderly man replied with a smile.

"Why is that?" Han Li asked.

"Pardon me for being frank, but you're most likely not going to have much luck with that water abode. There have been many cultivators of cultivation bases as lofty as the late-Golden Immortal Stage that have tried to access this water abode, but just the restriction on its gates alone was enough to keep out all of them.

“There were two of them who attempted to breach the restriction by force, only to incur backlash from the restriction, and one of them was severely wounded, while the other was killed on the spot," the elderly man sighed.

"I see. Thank you for looking out for me, but I have a decent understanding of restrictions and arrays, so even if I can't open the water abode, I think I'll be able to at least ensure self-preservation," Han Li replied.

The elderly man could see that Han Li had made up his mind, so he said, "In that case, I wish you the best of luck. Once you issue the payment, I'll send someone to take you there."

From his perspective, he had completed his obligation by issuing that warning to Han Li, and if he were to say anything further, then that would only rouse suspicions.

After the payment was issued, the elderly man called over a red-robed young woman, then issued her some instructions before sending her to take Han Li to the lake.

The young woman wasn't particularly beautiful, but there were a couple of dimples on her round face, making it appear as if she were constantly smiling, so she was certainly very pleasant to look at.

The woman led Han Li and Weeping Soul down Comb Grate Mountain, then made her way down a small path toward the lake.

The young woman seemed to have a very bubbly personality, and she couldn't help but ask, "Why did you pick out Ill Omen Manor, esteemed guest? You don't seem like a foolish person."

"Ill Omen Manor? Why do you call it that?" Han Li asked.

"Ever since this water abode was made public, no one has been able to access it, and many people have died trying, so it's essentially one big ill omen! That's why we named it Ill Omen Manor in private. That's not its official name, so if you can open it, you can give it a more festive and lucky name," the young woman explained.

"Ill Omen Manor isn't bad, I'll call it exactly that," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"I don't mean to rain on your parade, esteemed guest, but you only get to name the water abode if you can open it. If the restriction proves to be too much for you, then come back up to the surface right away. It's not worth losing your life over something like this," the young woman sighed.

"What's your name?" Han Li suddenly asked with a smile.

The young woman faltered slightly upon hearing this. All of the guests that she had attended to over the years had only treated her as a servant, and she had never been asked her name by any of them.

"My name is Hu Xiaocheng," the young woman replied in a slightly embarrassed manner.

"That's a fine name," Han Li replied with a contemplative nod, and at the same time, he couldn't help but think of Ye Susu, who this young woman very much reminded him of.

Last month, he had learned through certain avenues that a natural disaster had befallen Azure Fox City half a year ago, burning the entire city to the ground, and there wasn't even a single survivor.

That was right after he left, so he immediately realized that this had to have been a hoax to cover the Immortal Palace's tracks, and that was why he had come to this Three River Lake.

Hu Xiaocheng could see that Han Li was absorbed in his own thoughts, so she continued to lead the way in silence.

The three of them soon arrived on a plaza beside the Three River Lake, and there was a cool breeze blowing over the lake. It was a very pleasant day, and Hu Xiaocheng couldn't help but stretch lazily as she took a deep breath.

Looking at the rippling surface of the lake, Han Li was also feeling a bit more relaxed, and the dark emotions that had been recently weighing on him abated slightly.

"We've arrived, esteemed guest. Enter the lake from here, and you'll reach Ill Omen Manor after descending for about ten thousand feet," Hu Xiaocheng declared.

"Alright, I'll be back soon," Han Li replied with a nod, then plunged straight into the water before Hu Xiaocheng had a chance to reply.

"Be care..."

Hu Xiaocheng wasn't even able to fully articulate two words before Han Li vanished out of sight.

A resigned pout appeared on her face as she grumbled under her breath, "I didn't even get a chance to tell him about the layout of the lakebed in this area..."

In her eyes, there was no way that Han Li would be successful in this endeavor. After all, this was the notorious Ill Omen Manor that had kept out even many a Golden Immortal, so how could this unremarkable-looking guest succeed where countless others had failed?

"I hope he returns safely, at least," Hu Xiaocheng murmured to herself, and as soon as her voice trailed off, a figure flew out of the lake before landing beside her.

Hu Xiaocheng was stunned to discover that it was none other than Han Li, and she exclaimed, "You're back already? I thought you'd at least be down there for a few hours before you give up. I suppose it's a good thing that you know your limits."

Han Li was rather amused to hear this, and he tapped her on the forehead as he said, "Go and fetch that administrator. Tell him that I've opened this water abode."

Hu Xiaocheng's eyes immediately widened in incredulity upon hearing this.

"What? You're saying you've already..."

"Go on," Han Li prompted with a smile, and Hu Xiaocheng was still in a state of disbelief, but she did as she was told, flying straight back to Comb Grate Mountain.

Shortly thereafter, she returned with the bewildered elderly administrator from before.

The administrator descended down to the lakebed to take a look for himself, and only then did he finally believe Han Li's claim. He was stunned beyond belief, and he emerged from the lake with an ecstatic expression as he said, "You can stay in this water abode for the next three years, Fellow Daoist Han. As per what I said earlier, you can claim all of the treasures in the abode as long as it doesn't impact the abode's structural integrity."

"You have my thanks," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

"Also, please give the water abode a name," the elderly man said.

Han Li took a glance at Hu Xiaocheng, then said, "I'll call it Ill Omen Manor."

The elderly man faltered slightly upon hearing this, but then merely nodded in response before departing.

Prior to his departure, he instructed, "Stay with Fellow Daoist Han for now. If he needs anything, come to the sect to inform me right away."

Hu Xiaocheng hurriedly gave an affirmative response.

Following the elderly man's departure, Han Li turned to Hu Xiaocheng and asked, "Do you want to come down and take a look around in the manor?"

Hu Xiaocheng nodded eagerly in response.

Han Li laid a hand onto her shoulder, and a layer of azure light appeared over both of their bodies as they descended into the depths together.

The deeper they went, the darker the environment became.

Hu Xiaocheng had guided guests to other water palaces before, but she had never been this deep in the Three River Lake, and she was eagerly looking around with a curious expression.

The lakebed was riddled with broken mountains, some of which were still somewhat intact, while others displayed varying degrees of destruction.

There were light barriers of different colors spread over these mountains, encompassed within which were individual water abodes that had already been opened.

Most of these water abodes were extremely far away, giving them the appearance of stars in the night sky.

Han Li led Han Li all the way to the lakebed, arriving before a small hill that was only several hundred feet tall.

Hu Xiaocheng could see a light barrier on the summit of the hill, within which was a long courtyard.

Han Li led her by the arm as he rose up through the water before entering the light barrier, and upon arriving on a plaza in front of the courtyard, Han Li immediately withdrew the azure light barrier around them.

"Ancestral hall... This is the sect's ancestral hall?" Hu Xiaocheng exclaimed at the sight of a plaque hanging above the entrance of the courtyard up ahead.

"Why else do you think no one has been able to break through the restriction here even after so many years?" Han Li chuckled.

"If that's the case, then how were you able to break the restriction?" Hu Xiaocheng asked.

"I've read a lot of books," Han Li replied with a smile.

It was actually true that he had seen the protective array here in an ancient scripture, and with his powers and extensive knowledge in arrays and restrictions, it was an easy task for him to open the water abode.

"You're so lucky! I've heard that the ancestral hall is usually where a sect's best scriptures and treasures are kept, so you're going to make a massive haul!" Hu Xiaocheng said with an envious expression.

Chapter 1017: Waiting for Someone

"Perhaps there will be some scriptures, but I doubt that there will be any powerful treasures left. If the sect has already met its demise, then surely its most powerful treasures will have been taken out of the ancestral hall to ward off the enemy," Han Li said in a casual manner as he strode over to the water abode before pushing open its doors.

"Oh, that's a real pity then," Hu Xiaocheng said in a disappointed manner.

However, her expression then quickly lit up again as she continued, "Even so, scriptures can be just as valuable as treasures. If you can find a few top-tier cultivation arts here, then that'll still be a great haul."

The doors swung open with a loud creak, having been opened for the first time in countless years, revealing a long open-air area, and there was nothing in the courtyard aside from a rusty copper vat.

Han Li approached the vat to discover that there were some antiquated runes engraved onto its surface. The vat was half-filled with water, floating on top of which was a dark green lotus flower that was giving off strong water law power fluctuations.

"Wow, there's so much water-attribute spiritual qi here!" Hu Xiaocheng exclaimed.

She was only at the Nascent Soul Stage, so she wasn't very sensitive to law powers.

"Looks like there are still good things left here," Han Li remarked with a smile, and he casually swept a sleeve through the air, upon which the copper vat vanished into his Flower Branch domain.

On either side of the open-air area were two wide corridors that led to a large hall that appeared to be a conference hall, and the only things inside were some cushions that had already decomposed countless years ago.

Beyond this hall was a small courtyard that was much larger than the open-air area from before. The entire courtyard was paved with white stone blocks, giving it the appearance of a drill ground.

Beyond the drill ground was the final and most important building in the entire ancestral hall.

Han Li looked up to discover a plaque hanging above the entrance of the building, upon which were inscribed the words "a long history and a bright future".

Upon entering the hall, Han Li was greeted by the sight of a nine-tiered offering table.

Placed upon the offering table were numerous rectangular wooden placards that were extremely ornately crafted. As opposed to memorial tablets used to commemorate the dead, these were long-life tablets meant for the living.

There were a total of over eighty of these placards, all of which presumably carried the names of the leader and the elders of the sect.

On the bottom tier of the offering table were two thick books with a layer of flowing golden light over their surfaces.

Han Li approached the pair of books to discover that they were still sealed under restrictions, but due to the passage of time, the restrictions had already become very feeble.

He casually broke the restriction, then briefly read through the books to find that neither of them were cultivation arts.

One of them was a record of all of the significant events in the sect's history prior to its demise, while the other book contained the genealogical records of the sect, encompassing the names of all of the sect's members, from its founding father to all of its disciples.

"So this sect is called the Tranquility Sect. How unfortunate that it met such a terrible fate after standing for so long," Hu Xiaocheng sighed.

Han Li was reminded of the True Mantra Sect and the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor upon hearing this. Both had also suffered abrupt demises after extensive histories.

He cast his gaze toward the top tier of the offering table, and he suddenly noticed that there was a long-life tablet with the name "Chang Qingliu" inscribed upon it that looked a little strange.

He drew the tablet into his grasp, and after examining it briefly with his Infernal Devilish Eyes, a faint smile appeared on his face as he began tapping a finger over the tablet.

Moments later, a burst of azure light emerged over the tablet, following which a hidden jade slip flew out from within.

Han Li grabbed the jade slip, then returned the long-life tablet to its original spot.

"What's this?" Hu Xiaocheng asked with her eyes with intrigue.

"This is a cultivation art of the Tranquility Sect called the Formless Journal," Han Li replied after briefly inspecting the contents of the jade slip with his spiritual sense.

"I was worried that you had gone to the effort of opening this water abode for nothing, but now that you've found this cultivation art, it looks like your efforts weren't in vain," Hu Xiaocheng said with an elated expression, and it seemed that she was genuinely happy for Han Li.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, and a faint smile appeared on his face.

He searched through the entire ancestral hall with Hu Xiaocheng, but didn't find anything else, and Hu Xiaocheng was a little disappointed for him.

However, Han Li was very pleased with what he had found. The Formless Journal was a cultivation art that allowed one to cultivate water law powers, and it wasn't very useful to him, but it was perfect for his Earthly Deity Avatar in the Black Wind Sea.

On top of that, the copper vat and the dark green lotus flower that he had stowed away into his Flower Branch domain earlier were also both very remarkable items.

Due to the fact that the entire ancestral hall was situated on the lakebed, the environment was very cool despite the absence of wind.

Han Li and Hu Xiaocheng sat down together on the doorstep at the entrance of the ancestral hall, and both of them were looking up at the light barrier above in silence.

"That administrator instructed you to keep an eye on me and report everything I do to him, right?" Han Li suddenly asked.

"How did you know?" Hu Xiaocheng exclaimed, then immediately scratched her own head in a sheepish manner.

"You're not the only one, all of the guests who stay here get assigned a servant. Of course, it's not forced upon them, but generally, no one would refuse those beautiful big sisters. I don't know what Elder Lu was thinking this time, sending me to accompany you."

"He sent you to come with me because he didn't think very highly of me and didn't think that I could open this water abode," Han Li revealed.

"So that's why..." Hu Xiaocheng said as a look of realization appeared on her face.

"Other people can look down on you, but never look down on yourself. I can see that you possess decent cultivation aptitude, so a lack of resources must be why you're still stuck at the late-Nascent Soul Stage, right?" Han Li asked.

Hu Xiaocheng nodded in response in an uncertain matter, wondering why Han Li was bringing up this subject.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a small, red vial before handing it to her.

"I don't have any pills fit for consumption for low-tier cultivators. The pills in this vial will have to wait until you reach at least the Body Integration Stage."

Hu Xiaocheng was rooted to the spot upon hearing this, and she didn't dare to accept the vial.

Han Li thrust the vial into her grasp, and at the same time, he tapped a finger against her glabella.

Hu Xiaocheng immediately felt her own consciousness shudder slightly, and by the time she returned to her senses, she discovered that Han Li had already withdrawn his hand.

At the same time, she realized that a passage of text had appeared in her mind, and it was the full Formless Journal cultivation art.

Hu Xiaocheng immediately sprang to her feet, and she was so stunned that she didn't know what to say.

"The entire Three River Lake is about to be upturned soon," Han Li said in a serious manner as he also stood up from the doorstep.

"Have you rented this water abode to do something important, Senior?" Hu Xiaocheng.

"Not really, I'm just here to wait for someone," Han Li replied in an indifferent manner.

"A friend?" Hu Xiaocheng asked.

"A sworn enemy."

"Is there anything I can do for you?" Hu Xiaocheng asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"I've already removed the mark that the Comb Flow Sect planted in your body. Leave this place right away and get as far away as you can. Focus on your cultivation, and don't ever return to this place," Han Li said.

"Why are you doing all of this for me, Senior?" Hu Xiaocheng asked with a puzzled expression.

Han Li took a glance at her, then sighed, "I suppose it's to make up for the guilt that I harbor toward someone that you remind me of..."

Looking at the melancholy in Han Li's eyes, a hint of sorrow welled up in Hu Xiaocheng's heart as well.

"In that case, I'll come back to repay you once I've made some strides in my cultivation, Senior," Hu Xiaocheng said as she extended a deep bow toward Han Li.

"Go now," Han Li said with a smile.

Hu Xiaocheng extended another respectful bow before departing, and following her departure, Weeping Soul appeared beside Han Li amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

"Are you not worried that she's going to report you to Comb Grate Mountain?" she asked.

"Since when have I been such a terrible judge of character?" Han Li chuckled.

Weeping Soul also smiled as she fell silent.

"Even if she really does disappoint me, it doesn't matter. I'm staying here precisely so that the Immortal Palace can find me," Han Li said as a cold look flashed through his eyes.

"We'll make them pay for all of their past crimes," Weeping Soul said with a nod.

"Alright, we have guests to welcome soon, so let's arrange an appropriate welcome. We wouldn't want to be rude now, would we?" Han Li mused as he clapped his hands together, then made his way into the ancestral hall.

......

Half a month later.

A white flying boat that was around a hundred feet in length arrived in the sky above Comb Grate Mountain.

Standing on the flying boat were none other than Dongfang Bai and the three Immortal Palace elders.

Standing on the mountain below them was a handsome, azure-robed young man and a round-faced elderly man. The former was the current leader of the Comb Flow Sect, while the latter was the administrator that had attended to Han Li.

At this moment, both of them had fawning smiles on their faces as they looked up at Dongfang Bai's group.

"Have you told anyone that Han Li is staying here? Dongfang Bai asked.

Chapter 1018: Unwelcome Visitor

"I felt like this was a very important matter, so I've kept it a secret from everyone else. Right now, Elder Lu and I are the only ones in our entire sect who know about this, and we haven't informed the cultivators staying in the other water abodes of this matter," the Comb Flow Sect Leader hurriedly replied.

"Good. In that case, I won't have to destroy the entire sect," Dongfang Bai mused with a contemplative nod.

The young man and the round-faced elderly man exchanged a bewildered glance with each other upon hearing this, wondering if they had misheard.

However, before they had a chance to ponder this remark any further, they suddenly discovered that they weren't able to move.

All they could still move were their eyeballs, and they looked down to discover that a layer of slick, green moss had appeared over their bodies, on top of which a vibrant flower was blooming.

The azure-robed young man let loose an agonized roar as the flower took on a bright red color, and droplets of dew had even appeared on its surface, giving it a particularly alluring appearance.

In contrast, the two men were completely parched, and it was as if all of the life force had been sucked out of their bodies, reducing them to a pair of dried and withered corpses in just a few seconds.

Dongfang Bai took an expressionless glance at the two sets of withered remains, then asked, "Is his aura still here, Elder Lü?"

"It is," Lü Yun replied.

"Good," Dongfang Bai replied with a nod.

Meanwhile, Tao Ji was looking at the Three River Lake with a hesitant look on his face, and for some reason, he was feeling a little uneasy.

Dongfang Bai could see the uncertainty in his eyes, and he said, "Tao Ji, if you have something to say, then spit it out."

"Judging from his past track record, Han Li is definitely not a careless person, so I think that it's very suspicious that he left behind such clear tracks for us to trace to this point," Tao Ji said.

"Why are you being so cautious, Elder Tao? Could it be that you've lost your wits after your physical body was destroyed by him last time? How could he possibly put up any resistance against Palace Master Dongfang?" Hei Dao sneered.

However, Dongfang Bai agreed with Tao Ji on this occasion.

"Elder Tao's concerns are not unwarranted. Let's proceed with caution from here."

Tao Ji hurriedly extended a respectful bow upon hearing this, while the flying boat flew into the air above the Three River Lake at Dongfang Bai's behest.

"He's down there," Lü Yun said as he pointed at a section of the lake.

"Palace Master, please wait a moment while I split open the surface of the lake and force that scoundrel to come out," Hei Dao said as he removed the fearsome blade from his back.

"There's no need for that. It would be rude of us to barge in so barbarically," Dongfang Bai said with a faint smile, following which he extended a finger forward, and a burst of azure light shot out of his fingertip before plunging into the lake in a flash.

As soon as the burst of azure light entered the water, it immediately began to descend toward Han Li's water abode like a formidable flood dragon.

The still and calm lake was instantly stirred up into a frenzy, with a massive whirlpool appearing on its surface, leading all the way down to Ill Omen Manor.

At the same time, an azure spirit domain spread through the surrounding area, encapsulating all of the churning water to contain all of the energy fluctuations within the spirit domain.

Everything remained placid and tranquil outside the spirit domain, and even if curious bystanders were to try to look in, they wouldn't be able to see into the spirit domain.

The burst of azure light crashed headfirst into a white light barrier with an earth-shattering boom, and the light barrier was instantly shattered, revealing the hill that was home to the Tranquility Sect's ancestral hall.

At this moment, Han Li was seated at a stone table with Weeping Soul in the courtyard, and the cup in his hand shuddered slightly, but none of the wine spilled out from within.

"Looks like you were right, Palace Master Dongfang has come after us in person," Han Li said with a smile, following which he downed the contents of his cup in three sips, then stowed the cup away before standing up on his stone chair.

The surrounding water in the lake seemed to have been restricted by some type of strange power, and a swirling vortex had appeared around the hill.

Dongfang Bai's group was hovering in mid-air above the courtyard, looking down upon Han Li and Weeping Soul.

"I've heard much about you, Fellow Daoist Han. It's an honor to make your acquaintance," Dongfang Bai said with a faint smile.

"The honor is all mine, Palace Master Dongfang. To think that I had a mighty palace master chasing after me like a pathetic dog for so long. To what do I owe this great honor?" Han Li chuckled.

"Insolence!" Hei Dao roared in a furious voice upon hearing this.

"Oh? Was that too rude for your liking? In that case, how do you think I should speak to a piece of scum who kills innocents without any remorse?" Han Li asked in a cold voice.

A cold look flashed through Hei Dao's eyes, and he was just about to charge at Han Li, but a stern glance from Dongfang Bai kept him in check.

Han Li's gaze then fell upon the handsome young boy beside Dongfang Bai, and a surprised look appeared on his face as he said, "I didn't think we'd meet again, Elder Tao. You've been given a second chance at life, shouldn't you cherish it a little more?"

Tao Ji's mouth immediately ran dry at the sight of Han Li's scrutiny, and he glowered intently at Han Li to disguise the fear in his heart.

"What do the lives of those ants matter to cultivators of our status, Fellow Daoist Han? I'm willing to extend an offering of peace to you. As long as you're willing to hand over that thing, I can consider letting you off the hook and even putting in a recommendation for you to join the Nine Origins Temple. What do you say?" Dongfang Bai proposed with a smile.

As soon as Han Li heard mention of the words "Nine Origins Temple", he immediately understood what "that thing" that Dongfang Bai was referring to was.

His pupils contracted slightly upon hearing this, but he made no effort to deny that the Heaven Controlling Vial was in his possession. In any case, he had no intention of letting any of these four get away. Otherwise, if word were to spread of this, then there would be no end to the trouble that he would have to deal with.

In the past, he didn't want to engage in direct conflicts with the immortal palaces, but that didn't mean that he feared them. Now that they had provoked him on multiple occasions, it was time for him to give them some comeuppance.

"I advise you not to oppose the Heavenly Court, Fellow Daoist Han. If you so wish, you could easily cultivate in peace from here onward. Given your aptitude, as long as you have access to sufficient resources, it'll only be a matter of time before you reach the Great Encompassment Stage, and..."

"Looks like not only do you like to follow me around like a dog, you like to bark like one as well. I don't know what you want from me, and I don't care to find out. The Heavenly Court may be too powerful for me to oppose, but I can certainly stomp you into the ground," Han Li interjected in a lazy voice, cutting Dongfang Bai off mid-sentence.

"It seems like you're intent on opposing the Heavenly Court. What a pity. The Heavenly Court could've certainly used a man of your talents," Dongfang Bai sighed in a forlorn manner.

As soon as his voice trailed off, Hei Dao immediately swooped down from above, leaving a trail of afterimages in his wake as he swung his mighty blade down upon the ancestral hall, conjuring up a vast expanse of dark clouds.

A blade projection that was over ten thousand feet in length erupted out of his blade, slicing through the heavens as it crashed down from above.

The dark clouds descended alongside the blade projection, and a series of giant, fearsome-looking ghostly creatures emerged from within, all of which converged toward Han Li and Weeping Soul with intense bloodlust in their eyes.

Han Li paid no heed to Hei Dao's almighty attack, instead turning to Weeping Soul with a hint of amusement in his eyes.

"My tummy has been feeling rather empty ever since I awakened, I wasn't expecting the Immortal Palace to deliver a ghostly cultivator of this caliber right to my doorstep. This is going to be a massive feast," Weeping Soul said as she eagerly licked her lips.

"Make sure to take your time and don't eat too fast," Han Li replied with a smile.

Weeping Soul nodded in response, then sprang up into the like lightning, plunging directly into the dark clouds, upon which she instantly vanished out of sight.

Dongfang Bai turned to Hei Dao with a perplexed look upon seeing this, and Hei Dao was also rooted to the spot. He had never seen someone so eagerly rush to their death before.

However, right at this moment, a horrified look suddenly appeared on his face, and Dongfang Bai also cast his gaze toward the dark clouds, sensing that something was amiss.

As it turned out, all of the fearsome ghostly creatures within the dark clouds had suddenly begun fleeing for their lives, but they weren't able to get anywhere as they were bound to Hei Dao's blade.

Immediately thereafter, a pair of strange horns emerged from the dark clouds, followed by an enormous, ape-like head with a third, bright red, demonic eye on its glabella. The creature also had three black bone spikes protruding out of its back, and its body was covered in a layer of steel-needle-like black fur, giving it an even more fearsome appearance than the ghostly creatures around it.

"That's a Xing Beast!" Dongfang Bai exclaimed, and Hei Dao had also arrived at the same realization.

Never had he anticipated that he would encounter such a natural bane to his ghostly powers, and he hurriedly attempted to return his blade to its scabbard, but Weeping Soul naturally wasn't going to give him that opportunity.

A beam of crimson light erupted out of the vertical eye on her glabella, forming a giant crimson chain that swept toward the surrounding ghostly creatures.

Chapter 1019: Lured Into an Array

Xing Beasts had always been the bane of all ghostly creatures of the world, and after suffering her near-death ordeal, Weeping Soul had become far more powerful than before.

The crimson chain protruding out of her glabella resembled a giant steel whip, easily piercing through the chests of all of the ghostly creatures that it struck before stringing them together like accessories on a necklace.

Arcs of crimson lightning erupted out of the chains, instantly eradicating all of the thousands of ghostly creatures in the dark clouds to reduce them to plumes of black mist.

In the next instant, a burst of black light erupted out of the Xing Beast's mouth, and all of the ghostly creatures were sucked into its belly.

Meanwhile, Hei Dao had only managed to withdraw his blade halfway into its scabbard before the crimson chain wrapped itself around it like a spirit snake.

Countless arcs of crimson lightning erupted out of the chain, and Hei Dao's entire body instantly began to spasm uncontrollably as he howled in pain.

Right at this moment, a burst of dark green light suddenly appeared on his arm, and a series of green vines emerged from within, extending along his blade-wielding arm all the way to the blade itself.

The vines possessed some type of law powers that allowed them to rapidly regenerate after being struck by the arcs of crimson lightning, and they pried their way into the gaps between the chains and the blade to slowly extricate the latter bit by bit.

Hei Dao hurriedly took advantage of this opportunity to fully return his blade to its scabbard, but at this point, the majority of the dark clouds that he had unleashed had already disappeared.

Even though this was an extremely severe loss, he knew that he was very fortunate to have survived, and he hurriedly turned to extend his gratitude toward Dongfang Bai.

"Thank you, Palace Master..."

However, before he had a chance to finish his sentence, he suddenly felt a gust of fierce wind blowing at him from behind.

As it turned out, Han Li had abruptly vanished from the spot, only to reappear behind Hei Dao in a wraith-like manner, grabbing him by the back of his neck before he even had a chance to react.

Hei Dao's eyes widened in shock and horror, and before he even had a chance to beg for his life, Han Li tightened his grip and snapped his neck like a twig.

Dongfang Bai was furious to see this, and he thrust a palm toward Han Li.

Countless wisps of the world's origin qi converged toward him, instantly forming countless azure wooden rods that shot forth toward Han Li in a fearsome barrage.

At this point, Han Li had already released Hei Dao's lifeless body, and he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability to dart right past Tao Ji.

However, he chose not to harm Tao Ji as he descended toward the plaza in front of the ancestral hall.

Hei Dao's body fell out of the sky, and his nascent soul had only just flown out of his head before it was caught by the Xing Beast before being tossed into its cavernous mouth.

Tao Ji's initial shock and horror were even further magnified upon seeing this, and he began to descend out of the sky in a blind panic.

Meanwhile, Lü Yun rushed over to Dongfang Bai's side, staring intently at Han Li as he released a gray spirit domain to defend himself from potential sneak attacks from Han Li.

Dongfang Bai was naturally furious to have lost an important subordinate so early in the battle, and at the same time, he was stunned by Han Li's power.

He made a grabbing motion with one hand, and all of the wooden rods in the air before him converged to form a wooden dragon that was several thousand feet in length before pouncing at Han Li.

"You're attacking me with a toy made out of wood?" Han Li sneered as he clenched a hand into a tight fist, injecting all of his fist intent and starpower into the fist.

A resounding boom rang out as Han Li lashed out, and a burst of radiant starpower erupted out of his fist.

The wooden dragon crashed headfirst into the white starlight, and a string of resounding thumps rang out as the wooden rods that its body was comprised of were shattered one after another.

Scraps of wood filled the entire sky, and Dongfang Bai suddenly emerged from within, approaching Han Li before casually extending a finger in his direction.

A burst of azure light emerged from his fingertip, transforming into a dark green wooden spear that pierced directly at Han Li's chest.

There was a draconic projection coiled around the wooden spear, and the surrounding space warped and twisted violently as it shot forth through the air.

Han Li made no attempt to take any evasive measures as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword to oppose the wooden spear.

The two clashed violently against each other, and a burst of golden lightning instantly shot out of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

Lightning had always been the bane of wood, and the wooden spear instantly exploded upon being struck by the golden lightning.

"Is that all you've got? How disappointing. I would've expected more from a palace master," Han Li sneered.

A furious look flashed through Dongfang Bai's eyes upon hearing this, but he quickly composed himself again as he descended onto the plaza in front of the ancestral.

"I know what you've been up to. You've been verbally provoking me this entire time to lure me onto this plaza and into the array that you set up in advance, right? In that case, here I am. Let's see what you're going to do to me," Dongfang Bai said with a faint smile.

"You don't possess power befitting a palace master, but you're certainly as arrogant as one. Now that you're here, you're not getting away!" Han Li roared as he made a hand seal, and the entire hill shuddered violently as four mountainous devilish projections slowly rose up from the ground, each wielding an umbrella, an immortal sword, a mirror, and a python.

The four projections each surrounded Dongfang Bai from one direction, and the umbrella-wielding raised its umbrella high up into the sky, where it released countless rays of light to form a dome-shaped light barrier to encompass the entire hill, and the flow of the world's origin qi within the light barrier instantly stagnated.

Standing within the light barrier, Dongfang Bai could sense that the surrounding world's origin qi was no longer accessible to him, but this didn't faze him at all.

Those who cultivated wood law powers had innate worlds within their bodies, supplying them with limitless immortal spiritual power, so there was nothing for him to fear.

However, right at this moment, he spotted a beam of light sweeping toward him from the side, and he immediately darted away in evasion.

As he turned around, he discovered that the beam of light was shining down upon the spot where he had been standing just a moment ago, and a huge hole that was over thirty feet in size had appeared in the ground there.

The beam of light was coming from the mirror held by one of the four devilish projections, and all of the space in the wake of the beam of light was warping and twisting violently.

If he had been struck by that beam of light earlier, his body would've definitely been torn apart.

Before he had a chance to think about anything else, the sword-wielding and python-wielding projections lashed out in unison.

Balls of five-colored flames erupted out of the sword before raining down like a meteor shower, while the python swooped down from above with lightning flashing within its cavernous mouth.

The beam of light released by the mirror could still be avoided, but there was no way to evade the storm of lightning and fire.

Dongfang Bai gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, then began chanting an incantation while thrusting his palms up toward the heavens.

Azure light burst out of his body like a volcanic eruption, forming a gargantuan ancient tree projection that kept all of the lightning and fire at bay.

Even though the tree was only a projection, it still erupted into flames upon being struck by the lightning and fire.

However, its canopy was constantly regenerating at a rate faster than it was being incinerated, and even the beam of white light released by the mirror was unable to break through the projection's defenses.

"Is this your trump card, Fellow Daoist Han? If so, then this is truly disappointing," Dongfang Bai scoffed.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a beam of translucent light suddenly appeared in front of him, and before he even had a chance to catch a clear glimpse of it, it had already transformed into a miniature sword and pierced into his glabella.

He immediately felt a sharp pain in his head, and his consciousness began churning violently. He couldn't help but shudder from the intense agony, and the azure light erupting out of his body quickly faded away.

The giant tree projection also dissipated, and the ferocious barrage of lightning and fire rained down upon him to inundate him in the blink of an eye.

A string of resounding booms rang out as the entire plaza was illuminated by the explosions of fire and lightning.

Lü Yun and Tao Ji were locked in battle against Weeping Soul, and Tao Ji turned to Dongfang Bai with an alarmed expression upon seeing this.

"Don't worry about the palace master, Elder Tao, just focus on the task at hand," Lü Yun said as he swept his sleeves through the air, controlling eighteen crimson metal flags that were revolving around Weeping Soul.

Chapter 1020: Turning the Tables

As soon as Lü Yun's voice trailed off, the lightning and fire on the plaza faded away to reveal Dongfang Bai again.

However, he was no longer looking anywhere near as composed as before, and his entire body was charred black, giving him the appearance of a smoldering, charred stump.

There were also tiny crimson flames all over his body, but there was also a ball of flickering green light on his chest, releasing thin lines that spread out across his entire body like blood vessels.

The green lines were delivering life force to all parts of what appeared to be a lifeless body, and as a result, he was gradually beginning to recover.

Right at this moment, Han Li swooped onto the scene before sweeping a hand horizontally through the air.

Dongfang Bai's charred head immediately fell to the ground before being stomped into powdered coal beneath Han Li's foot.

At the same time, an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword pierced through Dongfang Bai's chest before releasing a burst of golden lightning that eradicated the ball of green light with ease.

However, instead of displaying any relief or triumph, Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he swept a perplexed gaze over his surroundings.

At this moment, there was a frail blade of grass growing nearby, and it was swaying gently in the wind.

All of a sudden, it began to rapidly grow amid an eruption of green light, transforming into a second Dongfang Bai in the blink of an eye.

"How remarkable," Han Li mused with a smile.

"Playtime's over, Fellow Daoist Han," Dongfang Bai said in a cold voice, and as soon as his voice trailed off, he rubbed his hands together, upon which countless specks of azure light appeared within his azure spirit domain, giving off a burst of tremendous wood law power fluctuations.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and he reflexively began to fly back in retreat.

Right at this moment, countless thick vines began to sprout within the azure spirit domain before rapidly spreading through the air, uprooting all of the giant trees in the area and instantly demolishing the entire ancestral hall.

In the blink of an eye, the lakebed was transformed into a lush forest.

The vines crawled rapidly over the four devilish projections stationed around the plaza, quickly inundating them and severing their connection with Han Li.

Meanwhile, Weeping Soul was ensnared by a series of special vines that were riddled with golden patterns, instantly rooting her to the spot.

Even though Han Li had reacted in a very timely fashion and already sprung back several thousand feet, the vines were still able to latch onto his feet, rooting him firmly to the ground.

Han Li took a glance at Weeping Soul to find that even though she had been trapped, she was in no danger for now, and that came as quite a relief.

"I've seen quite a few Creation Tier spirit domains before, but none quite as spectacular as this one."

"If Palace Master Dongfang hadn't spent so much time and effort cultivating his spirit domain, there's no way he would still only be at the peak-High Zenith Stage. No one in the entire Golden Origin Immortal Region dares to actually regard him as anything below a Great Encompassment cultivator," Lü Yun said with a confident smile, while Tao Ji turned to Dongfang Bai with a look of awe and veneration in his eyes.

"It doesn't actually make any difference whether you hand over that thing or not, Fellow Daoist Han," Dongfang Bai said as he slowly approached Han Li.

"I'm well aware of that," Han Li replied, and he channeled his own immortal spiritual power as he spoke, only for the immortal spiritual power that he had mustered up to instantly be sucked away by the vines clinging to his body.

He then channeled his starpower, and he discovered that it would also be absorbed by the vines, but at a far slower rate.

"Don't bother. Everything trapped in my spirit domain belongs to me. Once all of your immortal spiritual power has been sucked away, this powerful body of yours will be reduced to sustenance for my spirit domain, and your nascent soul will be forced to serve as my slave for all of eternity," Dongfang Bai said with a cold smile.

He could see that there was a string around Han Li's neck, and he extended a hand to reach down the front of Han Li's robe, but right at this moment, Han Li suddenly harrumphed coldly, "Don't touch what belongs to me!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, instantly transforming into a devilish deity with three heads and six arms.

Dongfang Bai's heart jolted slightly upon sensing the strange aura emanating from Han Li's body, and he hurriedly rushed back in retreat while directing all of the countless vines in his spirit domain to swarm toward Han Li at once.

However, Han Li was able to wade directly through the vines, tearing right through them with ease.

Dongfang Bai swept both sleeves through the air upon seeing this, and his spirit domain shuddered violently as a series of massive trees emerged before transforming into eighteen wooden giants that were over a thousand feet tall.

Each wooden giant was wielding a massive wooden spear as they charged at Han Li, and as they thrust their spears through the air, vortexes of azure light emerged from their tips, warping and tearing the space around them.

Han Li displayed no fear at all as he retaliated with his six arms, destroying the eighteen wooden giants in the span of no more than twenty seconds before leaping up into the air and plummeting down upon Dongfang Bai.

However, at this point, Dongfang Bai had already steadied himself, and countless vines had wrapped themselves around his body, transforming him into a wooden giant that was over a hundred feet tall.

These vines were riddled with golden patterns, harboring tremendous wood law powers and life energy.

As Han Li came crashing down from above, Dongfang Bai raised his left hand, sending a vine whip sweeping through the air before wrapping itself around Han Li's waist. He then tugged violently on the whip to accelerate Han Li's descent while thrusting the wooden spear in his other hand directly at Han Li's chest.

At the same time, the vine whip around Han Li's waist was rapidly absorbing his bloodline power, and if it weren't for his astonishingly formidable physical constitution, this would've already been too much for him to bear.

He reached out with one hand to grab the wooden spear, only for a powerful eruption of azure light from the tip of the spear to knock his hand away, following which the tip of the spear struck him on the chest.

A burst of tremendous immortal spiritual power surged through the entire spear, culminating in a ball of radiant azure and golden light at the tip of the spear that exploded violently, sending such formidable shockwaves sweeping in all directions that the entire spirit domain began to tremble and sway violently.

Lü Yun and Tao Ji were astonished as they witnessed this from afar.

Meanwhile, most of the immortal spiritual power in Weeping Soul's body had already been sucked away by the vines around her, forcing her to revert back to her human form, and she was watching Han Li's battle from afar with a concerned look in her eyes.

However, once the dust settled, it was revealed that Han Li was standing completely still on the spot, and the wooden spear hadn't managed to pierce even a single inch into his chest.

"Impossible!" Dongfang Bai exclaimed upon seeing this.

"I've heard that you possess power far beyond your cultivation base, but so what if you possess power on par with a Great Encompassment cultivator?" one of Han Li's heads sneered.

The combination of his true spirit bloodlines and Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts enhanced his physical constitution to the point that it was far beyond that of the average Great Encompassment cultivator, so Dongfang Bai's attacks never posed any true threat to him.

Han Li leaned down as he spoke, causing the wooden spear to bend like a bow, and he grabbed onto the vine whip around his waist before tugging on it to drag Dongfang Bai toward himself.

Immediately thereafter, he began unleashing a torrential barrage of punches upon Dongfang Bai with his six giant fists.

A string of deafening booms rang out as the entire azure spirit domain trembled violently.

The wooden vines around Dongfang Bai's body were only able to resist Han Li's punches for a short while before they were completely smashed to bits.

Lü Yun and Tao Ji exchanged a glance upon seeing this, and each of them could see their own horror mirrored in one another's eyes.

They possessed nowhere near enough power to play any role in this battle. In fact, just a single one of those punches that Han Li was unleashing would be enough to kill them on the spot.

Before long, Dongfang Bai was revealed amid a mass of shattered vines before being grabbed by Han Li.

"You shouldn't have done what you did to Azure Fox City. The Azure Fox Tribe was just a small tribe that would've never been able to pose any threat to you, why weren't you willing to spare them?" Han Li interrogated with all three of his heads, and his voice rumbled like thunder.

"Why do you care so much for those ants? They..."

Before Dongfang Bai had a chance to finish his sentence, Han Li clenched his fist tightly, crushing his body into a pulp.

However, no nascent soul flew out of the mangled body.

Han Li tossed the body aside, and he reverted back to his human form before turning to Tao Ji and Lü Yun with tightly furrowed brows.

A small vine beside them gradually swelled in size before transforming into yet another Dongfang Bai.

As for the body that Han Li had just discarded, it had already been devoured by the masses of surrounding azure vines.

"Looks like you've gotten the best of me here, Fellow Daoist Han. We'll meet again," Dongfang Bai said with a dark expression.

"You're not getting away!" Han Li harrumphed coldly, and as soon as his voice trailed off, a radiant golden spirit domain appeared within the surrounding azure spirit domain.

Chapter 1021: Report

An alarmed look appeared on Dongfang Bai's face upon seeing this, and in the next instant, he withdrew his azure spirit domain without any hesitation, then grabbed onto Tao Ji and Lü Yun before launching himself up into the sky.

In the absence of his spirit domain, the water in the lake instantly gushed back in to fill the vortex.

A layer of radiant, azure light appeared around Dongfang Bai's trio, warding off the majority of the time law powers in Han Li's golden spirit domain as Dongfang Bai sped away into the distance.

"None of you are getting away today!" Han Li roared as he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, appearing above the trio in the blink of an eye.

A look of resolve appeared in Dongfang Bai's eyes upon seeing this, and he thrust his palms into Tao Ji and Lü Yun's backs, sending one of them flying toward Han Li, while the other was launched at Weeping Soul down below.

Only then did Tao Ji and Lü Yun discover, much to their shock and horror, that they were completely immobilized, and they couldn't even open their mouths to speak.

Han Li thrust a palm at the oncoming Tao Ji, but right at this moment, the latter's lower abdomen suddenly began to swell rapidly. Immediately thereafter, a tiny seedling emerged from his belly button.

Before Han Li was able to reach him, his stomach swelled up like a balloon, following which his entire body exploded violently.

His nascent soul had been detonated within his dantian, generating such tremendous power that even Han Li was sent flying back by the explosion, while his outstretched hand had also been severely mutilated.

However, he had no time to attend to his own injuries as Lü Yun was currently hurtling toward Weeping Soul.

He simultaneously channeled his Reversal True Axis ability and his Lightning Bird bloodline before plunging into the lake to swoop up Weeping Soul, and a resounding explosion rang out behind him before he had a chance to get away.

The explosion was so powerful that all of the water abodes on the lakebed were destroyed, and enormous waves that were over ten thousand feet tall erupted out of the lake before crashing toward the neighboring Comb Grate Mountain.

A few moments later, Han Li and Weeping Soul shot out of the lake before hovering in the sky above.

"That Dongfang Bai is truly a terrible man, Master! He sacrificed his own companions just so he could get away!" Weeping Soul spat through gritted teeth.

"The fact that a man like him is serving as the palace master of such an important immortal region is a clear indication that the Heavenly Court is already rotten to the core. No matter, he can run for now, but he can't run forever. His past crimes will eventually catch up to him," Han Li said.

"What should we do now, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"You take some time to rest, I'll devise a plan for what we do from here onward," Han Li replied, then conjured up an entrance to the Flower Branch domain for Weeping Soul.

Once she had entered the Flower Branch domain, Han Li flew away as a streak of light, instantly vanishing into the distance.

......

There was a cluster of palaces situated somewhere in the western region of the Golden Origin Mountain Range. The palaces stretched as far as the eyes could see, and some were situated in cols, some were built on mountains, and some were even hovering in mid-air.

The palaces were connected by bridges of rainbow light, giving the entire place the appearance of an immortal paradise, and this was none other than the Golden Origin Immortal Palace.

Right at this moment, a streak of green light appeared in the distant sky, flying through the air at an astonishing speed before fading to reveal Dongfang Bai.

The look on his face was as dark as the clouds on a stormy day, and the Immortal Palace personnel that he passed by all bowed in silence, not daring to say anything for fear of incurring his very apparent wrath.

Before long, Dongfang Bai arrived deep in the Immortal Palace. He entered a palace with a golden communication array inside, and he flipped a hand over to produce a purple badge before placing it onto the communication array.

The badge began to glow with radiant purple light, illuminating the surrounding golden array a purple color as well.

Moments later, a projection of a green-haired woman appeared in the array.

The woman was very youthful in appearance, seemingly only around sixteen to seventeen years of age, and her complexion was a little pale, but there was a look of unmatched regal authority in her eyes.

"Dongfang Bai, why have you used your Nine Origin Badge to contact me? If those people from the Immortal Prison find out about this, it'll spell trouble for both of us," the green-haired woman said.

"Please forgive me, Immortal Lord Miao Fa. I just received a piece of information pertaining to Creation Crystals, and I wanted to report it to you right away," Dongfang Bai replied in a respectful manner.

"What? You've found leads on Creation Crystals? Elaborate!" Immortal Lord Miao Fa urged as a burst of tremendous pressure was exerted upon Dongfang Bai through the array, causing his robes to flap audibly around him.

Dongfang Bai didn't dare to waste any time, and he hurriedly informed Immortal Lord Miao Fa of the situation regarding Han Li and the Heaven Controlling Vial, making sure to embellish the story as he told it.

For his version of the story, he proclaimed that Tao Ji and Tao Yu had discovered Han Li first, only to withhold the information from him. From there, he became suspicious of Tao Ji and decided to look into the matter, thereby leading to his discovery of Han Li and the Heaven Controlling Vial. In any case, both Tao Ji and Tao Yu were already dead, so there was no one to disprove his story.

"That does sound like there's a very good chance that those crystals are indeed Creation Crystals! Finally, the Heaven Controlling Vial has reappeared in the True Immortal Realm!" Immortal Lord Miao Fa exclaimed with an ecstatic expression.

However, a cold look then appeared in her eyes as she asked, "If you've already found out about this matter, then why didn't you report it to me earlier?"

"Please forgive me! I was too greedy and wanted to capture Han Li and the Heaven Controlling Vial myself before offering them up to you in the hope that I would be granted a handsome reward.

“However, he was too powerful for me to defeat, so I had no choice but to turn to you," Dongfang Bai said as he fell to his knees, and there was a panicked look on his face, but if one were to look closely into his eyes, they would discover that he was actually very calm and collected.

There was no hiding what had happened with Han Li, so as opposed to lying and inevitably being caught later, it was better for him to admit to his own faults from the get-go.

From there, he spoke about the blatant disregard that Han Li had displayed toward the Heavenly Court, much to the fury of Immortal Lord Miao Fa.

Han Li was still in the Golden Origin Immortal Region at the moment, so Dongfang Bai knew that Immortal Lord Miao Fa would have to rely on him for Han Li's capture. Hence, he was confident that he wouldn't be punished too severely for his transgressions.

Sure enough, Immortal Lord Miao Fa's expression eased slightly as she asked, "Where is he right now?"

Dongfang Bai was very relieved to see this, and he hurriedly replied, "I've sent out some people to search for him, but the search hasn't yielded any results yet. However, I've already issued orders for all of the teleportation arrays in the Golden Origin Immortal Region to be shut down, so I'm certain he must still be near the Golden Origin Mountain Range."

"You did well. You may have made a significant contribution in uncovering these leads on the Creation Crystals, but you also made a grave transgression in your inappropriate handling of the matter. For now, your contributions and transgressions cancel each other out, so whether you're going to be punished or rewarded will depend on what you do from here onward.

“If you can capture Han Li and secure the Heaven Controlling Vial, I'll let your past transgressions slide and even personally request a reward for you from our temple master. However, if you let him escape from the Golden Origin Immortal Region, I'm sure I don't need to tell you what's going to become of you, right?" Immortal Lord Miao Fa asked in a threatening tone.

"I'll do everything in my power to capture Han Li. However, I'm afraid that my Golden Origin Immortal Palace simply doesn't possess the power required to accomplish such a feat," Dongfang Bai replied in a hesitant manner.

"Rest assured, I'll send the Lan siblings of the Vast Golden Immortal Palace to help you. Keep searching for Han Li's whereabouts, but make sure to be careful and don't scare him into hiding," Immortal Lord Miao Fa warned.

"Yes, I understand!" Dongfang Bai replied in an ecstatic manner.

The Lan siblings of the Vast Golden Immortal Palace were a vastly renowned brother-and-sister duo. Even though both of them were only at the late-High Zenith Stage, they had a secret technique that allowed them to temporarily combine their cultivation bases to reach the Great Encompassment Stage.

The two of them had made a name for themselves after fighting a Great Encompassment cultivator of the Reincarnation Palace for three days and three nights without suffering a defeat.

With the Lan siblings on his side, Han Li would essentially have to face two Great Encompassment cultivators at once, and there was no way he could overcome such fearsome opposition.

With that in mind, Dongfang Bai was feeling much more reassured.

Immortal Lord Miao Fa issued a few more instructions to him, then cut off their communication, and Dongfang Bai heaved a long sigh of relief as he retrieved the purple badge from within the communication array.

......

In a certain pink palace somewhere in the Heavenly Court.

The entire palace was filled with a soft, pink glow, as well as a delicate, feminine aroma.

Deep within the palace was an ornate bed surrounded by a pink veil canopy. There was a young woman seated on the bed, and it was none other than Immortal Lord Miao Fa.

At this moment, there was a yellow toad that was far larger than the bed resting beside it. Its earthy yellow skin was riddled with hard lumps, and what was most peculiar about the creature was that there were six large eyes on its face, giving it a rather unsettling sight to behold.

Even though the yellow toad was merely resting beside the bed, it was giving off an enormous aura that wasn't inferior to Immortal Lord Miao Fa's by much, and its cavernous mouth perked up slightly at the corners as if it were smiling as it said, "Congratulations, Mistress. If you can secure the Heaven Controlling Vial, the temple master will be sure to reward you handsomely. The post of deputy temple master has always been vacant, and it'll be yours for the taking."

"I don't really care for that. All I'm hoping is that in exchange for my efforts, the temple master will provide me with some guidance in how to sever my second corpse soul," Immortal Lord Miao Fa replied.

"Indeed, power is always paramount," the yellow toad chimed in in agreement.

"She Chan, relay my orders to the Vast Golden Immortal Palace. Also, make a trip to the Golden Origin Immortal Region," Immortal Lord Miao Fa instructed after a brief silence.

Chapter 1022: Storming the Immortal Palace

"Surely the Lan siblings will already suffice. No matter how powerful that Han Li is, he's still just a High Zenith cultivator, so there should be no need for me to go," She Chan scoffed.

"I've heard that Han Li has made some significant inroads in the cultivation of time law powers, so he's not to be looked down on. I don't trust the Lan siblings to get the job done on their own. Make sure to keep yourself hidden from everyone and remain in the shadows at all times. Only strike when you're absolutely certain that you can land the decisive blow," Immortal Lord Miao Fa said.

She Chan's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but a hint of discontentment flashed through its six eyes.

Not only was its master making it go after a mere High Zenith cultivator, she was also instructing it to lurk in the shadows and sneak attack like a coward, and it was feeling rather slighted.

"This is a matter of the utmost importance. If anything goes wrong, you'll be held accountable!" Immortal Lord Miao Fa said in a cold voice.

"I understand, I'll go relay your orders right away, Mistress," She Chan replied as it transformed into a hideous yellow-skinned woman in the blink of an eye before vanishing into the ground.

......

Inside the Golden Immortal Stage, Dongfang Bai emerged from the communication palace, feeling much more relaxed than before.

Once the people from the Vast Golden Immortal Palace arrived, Han Li's capture would be all but assured, and he would be able to do as he pleased to Han Li.

He had already thought of dozens of vicious torture methods that he wanted to use on Han Li, and just the thought of that was filling him with sadistic joy.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he clapped his hands together twice, and a streak of light flew onto the scene from afar, then faded to reveal a young man with a pair of sharp and piercing eyes.

"What can I do for you, Palace Master?"

"Hei Dao and Lü Yun have perished during this outing with me, so from this day forth, you will be the leader of Dark Sword. Send out all of the Dark Sword spies and contact all of the spies of our Immortal Palace across the entire immortal region. Make sure to find out Han Li's whereabouts at all costs," Dongfang Bai instructed.

A hint of elation flashed through the young man's eyes upon hearing this, and he gave an affirmative response as he extended a respectful bow.

Right at this moment, a burst of dull rumbling rang out in the distance, and the entire surrounding area trembled violently.

"What's going on?" Dongfang Bai asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I'll go take a look," the young man volunteered, yet before he had a chance to leave, a streak of light shot forth from afar, then descended to reveal a golden-robed guard that was covered in blood.

"Palace Master Dongfang, someone has stormed into the Immortal Palace!" the man reported in a horrified manner.

"Who dares to challenge the authority of our Golden Origin Immortal Palace?"

A furious look flashed through Dongfang Bai's eyes, and he was just about to fly away into the distance when a thought suddenly occurred to him.

He released his spiritual sense toward the entrance of the Immortal Palace, upon which his expression instantly changed slightly.

......

The formerly opulent and majestic entrance of the Immortal Palace had already been completely razed to the ground, and there were currently over a hundred Immortal Palace cultivators hovering in mid-air, arranged in a crescent-shaped formation behind five black-robed elderly men.

The five men were almost indistinguishable from one another, indicating that they were identical quintuplets.

All of the Immortal Palace cultivators present ranged from the late-True Immortal Stage to the late-Golden Immortal Stage, while the five black-robed elderly men were all at the High Zenith Stage.

All types of immortal treasures and formidable attacks were being launched through the air, and the target was only a single person.

It was an azure-robed young man with dozens of golden flying swords circling around him, forming a wall of golden sword projections that easily destroyed all of the oncoming attacks.

At the same time, the young man swept a sleeve through the air, releasing around a dozen more golden flying swords that flew through the air with astonishing power.

Bursts of thunderous rumbling rang out from the flying sword as they sliced through the air, leaving long, white spatial rifts in their wake.

The five High Zenith Stage elderly men's expressions changed drastically as they immediately arranged themselves into a cross formation, following which each of them released a black flag with a sinister-looking black dragon emblazoned onto its surface.

The black flags quickly swelled to several times their original size before releasing a vast expanse of viscous black mist, forming an enormous black cloud that swept toward the oncoming flying sword, corroding the very space in its wake.

All of the other Immortal Palace cultivators immediately rushed away to avoid the black cloud, but Han Li remained completely unfazed as thick arcs of golden lightning erupted out of his golden flying swords at his behest.

As soon as the flying swords plunged into the black cloud, the latter immediately began churning violently before rapidly dissipating into countless plumes of black mist.

The golden flying swords were barely impeded at all as they tore through the black cloud before hurtling toward the five black-robed High Zenith cultivators, all of whom were very alarmed to see this.

All of a sudden, all five of them shrank down significantly to only around three feet in height before darting away to the side at an incredible speed, allowing them to just barely evade the golden flying swords.

Instead of pursuing them, the flying swords flew right past them before tearing into the Immortal Palace cultivators behind them.

A string of bloodcurdling howls rang out as the flying swords raked through the crowd, slaying all of the True Immortals in the blink of an eye while also cutting down as many as a third of the Golden Immortals present. All of the remaining Golden Immortals immediately fled for their lives, and their crescent-shaped formation instantly disintegrated.

Meanwhile, the five High Zenith Stage elderly men reverted back to their original heights, and furious looks appeared on their faces upon seeing this.

These Golden Immortals were the foundation of the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, and a third of them had just been slain in the blink of an eye!

"Who are you? The Heavenly Court is not going to let you get away with this!" one of the five elderly men yelled in a furious voice.

Han Li paid no heed to the elderly as he swept his sleeve through the air once again, and the dozen or so golden flying swords immediately set off after the remaining Golden Immortals, slaying several more of them in a flash.

The five High Zenith Stage elderly men were even more infuriated, and they collectively turned to the center of the Immortal Palace, seemingly waiting for something, but nothing happened.

In the blink of an eye, two more Golden Immortals were cut down, and the five elderly men were just about to storm at Han Li again when around a dozen streaks of radiant green light descended from the heavens before transforming into a series of huge, green snakes.

These snakes were extraordinarily fast and agile, and each of them wrapped itself around one of the golden flying swords.

Tendrils of green mist surged out of their bodies to ensnare the golden swords, only to be instantly destroyed, but more and more of those tendrils of green mist continued to emerged from the bodies of the green snakes, and it didn't take long before the golden flying swords were exhausted of much of their power.

Countless tendrils of green mist wrapped themselves tightly around the swords, forming a giant cocoon around each of them.

Han Li made a hand seal upon seeing this, and the dozen or so golden flying swords pierced their way out of the green cocoons around them before returning to his side.

Immediately thereafter, Dongfang Bai descended out of the sky, and all of the green snakes flew back to him before quickly shrinking down into a series of green rings that hovered around him.

All of the Immortal Palace cultivators were ecstatic to see Dongfang Bai.

"The palace master is here!"

"You're dead now, you scoundrel!"

"Palace Master, don't let him leave this place alive!"

All of the Immortal Palace cultivators gathered behind Dongfang Bai as they glowered at Han Li with resentful expressions.

Dongfang Bai paid no heed to them as he cast his gaze toward Han Li.

"I'll admit that you're a very powerful man, Han Li, but you've bitten off more than you can chew here!"

"You've saved me the trouble of having to pluck you out, Dongfang Bai. You killed all 57,300 members of the Azure Fox Tribe for no just cause, and today is the day that you get your comeuppance!" Han Li declared in a cold voice.

Many of the Immortal Palace cultivators turned to Dongfang Bai with stunned expressions upon seeing this.

It was strictly forbidden for cultivators of the Heavenly Court to kill for no just cause, particularly on such a large-scale basis, and the punishments for such a transgression were very severe.

"They deserved to die for harboring a wanted fugitive on the Immortal Slaying List and attacking the cultivators of our Immortal Palace!" Dongfang Bai countered.

Han Li had no intention of bickering with him on this matter, and he harrumphed coldly, "Regardless of what you say, today is the day that you die!"

Immediately thereafter, all of the dozens of Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that were revolving around him shot forth toward Dongfang Bai in unison.

In response, Dongfang Bai made a hand seal, and the green rings around him reverted back into around a dozen giant, green pythons, releasing countless tendrils of green mist toward the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Chapter 1023: Rats Fleeing a Sinking Ship

"All of you, get back!" Dongfang Bai yelled, and the five black-robed elderly men immediately led all of the other Immortal Palace cultivators on a retreat.

Han Li paid no heed to the others as countless streaks of golden sword qi erupted out of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at his behest, causing the entire sky to tremble violently.

The green pythons stood no chance against this formidable barrage of sword qi, and they were quickly torn to shreds.

Dongfang Bai's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and he abruptly made a hand seal while letting loose a loud roar.

The shredded remains of the green pythons swelled rapidly before exploding violently, sending powerful shockwaves sweeping through the air in all directions, and all of the streaks of golden sword qi were also scattered as a result.

Taking advantage of this opportunity, Dongfang Bai turned and fled deeper into the Immortal Palace with a gust of fierce green wind swirling around his body.

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this, and he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability.

All of a sudden, he vanished from the spot, only to reappear in front of Dongfang Bai an instant later, displaying astonishing speed akin to instantaneous teleportation.

Before Dongfang Bai had a chance to do anything, countless golden ripples erupted out of the Mantra Treasured Axis in Han Li's body, sweeping over Dongfang Bai in the blink of an eye.

All of a sudden, Dongfang Bai was completely immobilized, much like a fly caught in a block of amber.

Fierce killing intent flashed through Han Li's eyes as he pointed a finger forward, and a streak of golden light shot out of his fingertip before punching a large hole straight through Dongfang Bai's lower abdomen.

However, a layer of white light that instantly emerged over Dongfang Bai's body, and it rapidly transformed into a white puppet.

The puppet appeared to have been crafted from some type of white beast bone, and it was riddled with talismans and white patterns.

This is a substitution puppet!

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this.

He had read about this white puppet in a scripture from Daoist Xie's collection. It was said that this puppet had been created by a powerful master in the Heavenly Court, and one could inject their own immortal spiritual power and law powers into it to manifest an avatar that was completely identical to themselves, both in terms of appearance and aura.

Daoist Xie had always been interested in securing such a puppet for research purposes, but he was never able to succeed, and Han Li certainly wasn't expecting to see one here.

Right at this moment, countless specks of green light appeared in the surrounding area, forming a green spirit domain around Han Li.

Countless disembodied vines appeared within the spirit domain before wrapping themselves around him to rapidly devour his immortal spiritual power.

At the same time, an enormous golden mountain appeared above Han Li without any warning. The mountain was riddled with massive runes, and it seemed to be an immortal treasure, one that was crashing down upon him with unstoppable might.

At this moment, Dongfang Bai, the five black-robed elderly men, and all of the Immortal Palace Golden Immortals were seated atop the mountain with their legs crossed, collectively injecting their power into the mountain.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the golden mountain crashed down onto the ground, sending violent tremors running through the ground in a radius of tens of thousands of kilometers, while the entire Golden Origin Immortal Palace and the nearby mountains sank down by three feet in unison.

A pleased smile appeared on Dongfang Bai's face upon seeing this.

It had taken him countless years and an investment of an unfathomable amount of resources to refine this Xumi Golden Mountain using the Golden Origin Stones in the Golden Origin Mountain Range, and he was more aware of its power than anyone.

Unfortunately, the mountain was too heavy for him to use with his own immortal spiritual power alone, and he could only use it with the help of the arrays in the Golden Origin Immortal Palace. Otherwise, if he had been able to use it during his previous battle against Han Li, then he was certain that he would've emerged victorious.

All of the Immortal Palace cultivators heaved a collective sigh of relief, and they were also looking very excited.

After all, it was a very rare honor to be able to work together with their palace master to slay such a powerful enemy.

However, in the next instant, Dongfang Bai's smile abruptly stiffened.

At the same time, looks of shock and horror appeared on everyone's faces as they looked down in unison.

The golden mountain beneath them was beginning to tremble unsteadily as it gradually rose up from the ground, as if it were being lifted from below.

As it turned out, Han Li had once again adopted his devilish deity form with three heads and six arms, and he was only using two of his arms to lift the golden mountain, as if he were lifting nothing more than an ordinary rock.

"Impossible!" Dongfang Bai exclaimed.

Right at this moment, Han Li's Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree appeared before him, and it began to radiate dazzling golden light.

As soon as the plants in the surrounding spirit domain came into contact with this golden light, they were immediately reduced to bursts of energy that surged into the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree before being transmitted into Han Li's body, instantly replenishing the immortal spiritual power that had been sucked out of his body.

At the same time, the green spirit domain was rapidly shrinking.

"This is impossible! Nothing can devour my Wood God Spirit Domain!" Dongfang Bai exclaimed in shock and horror, and before he had a chance to do anything else, Han Li swung his remaining four fists upward with devastating power, sending them crashing into the underside of the golden mountain.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the golden mountain was sent flying through the air, toppling close to twenty mountains before drawing to a halt.

Most of the cultivators on the mountain had already been knocked off in the process, and the few that managed to remain on the mountain were all stunned beyond words.

Cold sweat was running down Dongfang Bai's forehead as he hurriedly withdrew his spirit domain before fleeing deeper into the Immortal Palace as a streak of green light.

"Get back here!" Han Li roared as he set off in pursuit.

Right at this moment, a vast black cloud suddenly swept toward him from the side before blocking his path, and the five High Zenith Stage elderly men could be seen within it.

The five of them were wielding the same black flags from before, waving them frantically through the air to expand the black cloud further. Immediately thereafter, eight giant black dragon claws shot out of the black cloud before grabbing at Han Li in unison.

The eight dragon claws were giving off an almighty aura, and it seemed that they were capable of tearing holes into the very heavens.

Even though the five elderly men had banded together to oppose Han Li, they were far from glad to do so.

At this point, it had already become abundantly clear that Han Li was far too powerful for them to oppose, but as elders of the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, if they were to abandon their post, then that would be seen as a crime of treason against the Heavenly Court.

Hence, they could only hope to keep Han Li occupied for now and devise other strategies as the situation unfolded.

"Get out of my way!" Han Li harrumphed coldly as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing all seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which clashed against the black dragon claws while giving off incredibly fearsome lightning law power fluctuations.

The flying swords easily sliced through the black dragon claws like hot knives through butter, and some small gashes immediately appeared on the black flags in the hands of the five elderly men.

The five of them hurriedly attempted to rush back in retreat upon seeing this, but the seventy-two flying swords were astonishingly fast, catching up to the retreating black cloud in the blink of an eye.

The five elderly men roared in unison as they summoned their protective immortal treasures, but the black cloud instantly dissipated upon contact with the golden lightning released by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, while the protective treasures that they had summoned were also destroyed in an instant.

It was finally confirmed to them beyond a doubt that they stood no chance against Han Li, and they were just about to flee for their lives when a burst of sharp sword intent descended upon each of them, causing their immortal spiritual power circulation to stagnate and plunging them into the depths of despair.

Many of the surrounding Golden Immortals had already fled following Dongfang Bai's escape, and all that remained were the direct subordinates of the five elderly men.

They were just about to pounce at Han Li, but all of them stopped in their tracks with horrified expressions upon seeing this.

Immediately thereafter, someone fled for their life, and everyone immediately followed suit, much like a nest of rats fleeing a sinking ship.

Chapter 1024: Slaying the Five Scourges

"You're the Five Heavenly Yin Disciples, right? Tell me your names," Han Li demanded in a cold voice.

The five elderly men exchanged a few glances with one another, following which the leftmost one put on a fawning smile as he said, "My name is Yin Tianhu. Please spare us, Fellow Daoist Han, we know nothing about your differences with Palace Master Dongfang."

The five of them were each wearing a black jade storage ring with the characters for tiger, deer, bear, ape, and eagle inscribed upon them, and the one who had just spoken was wearing the tiger ring. [1]

"My name is Yin Tianlu," the elderly man next to the first one said, and he was clearly also submitting to Han Li through his body language.

"I am Yin Tianxiong," the third elderly man said in a neutral manner.

"My name is Yin Tianyuan. If you're going to kill me, then hurry up and stop wasting my time!" the fourth elderly man harrumphed coldly with an arrogant expression.

"Don't spout such nonsense, Tianyuan!" Yin Tianhu scolded in a frantic manner.

Right at his moment, the final elderly man abruptly shrank down to only around half of his original height, allowing him to avoid the flying sword that had been resting against his throat before flying away at an incredible speed.

However, the golden flying sword immediately set off in pursuit at a far superior speed, catching up to him in the blink of an eye before slicing through his body with ease.

"Tianying!"

"Please spare him, Fellow Daoist Han!"

The other four elderly men all called out in alarm, but it was already too late.

Right at this moment, Weeping Soul appeared behind him amid a flash of silver light, and she made a grabbing motion with both hands, releasing a burst of crimson light that sucked the nascent soul out of Yin Tianying's remains.

Drawn to her alongside his nascent soul was his storage ring, one that was inscribed with the character for eagle.

The other four siblings reflexively wanted to flee, but with the example set by Yin Tianying, they knew not to pursue such a foolish course of action.

"All of us cultivators have killed many people in the past, but I sorely detest those who senselessly slaughter those weaker than them. I've heard about what the five of you have done, and I asked you to tell me your names so I can tell you your crimes before I kill you!" Han Li declared in a cold voice.

The four elderly men were very alarmed to hear this, and they contemplated fleeing once again, but didn't dare to do so.

"That one just now was Yin Tianying, right? He sacrificed over a hundred mortal cities to refine an immortal treasure, killing countless people in the process. For that, he deserves to die a thousand times over!" Han Li declared.

The four elderly men were stunned to hear this. Yin Tianying had been very secretive about this matter, so they were stunned that Han Li was aware of his secret.

"Yin Tianhu, you once cultivated for many years in the Vast Cloud Mountain Range, and in order to claim a place that was abundant with yin qi for your cultivation, you slaughtered all of the over two thousand cultivators of the Golden Peak Sect in the Vast Cloud Mountain Range, isn't that right?" Han Li asked.

"There must be some misunderstanding! I..." Yin Tianhu stuttered as his face turned deathly pale.

"Yin Tianlu, in order to refine an evil treasure of yours, you sent out your subordinates to capture countless women over six months into their pregnancies before sacrificing them, is that correct?" Han Li interrogated.

A look of despair appeared on Yin Tianlu's face, and he began to tremble uncontrollably.

"Yin Tianxiong, don't act like you're better than your brothers. You're using a dual cultivation art that enhances your cultivation base at the expense of female partners. During your time in the Immortal Palace, you've secretly abducted hundreds of female disciples at or above the Grand Ascension Stage from different sects across the Golden Origin Immortal Region for your own nefarious cultivation," Han Li said in a cold voice, and Yin Tianxiong's complexion also instantly turned deathly pale.

"And you, Yin Tianyuan. You're not like your brothers in that you don't kill for your own selfish desires, but you're a loyal lapdog to Dongfang Bai. Over the years, you've decimated countless tribes and sects under Dongfang Bai's orders," Han Li said.

"You've really done your homework, haven't you? That's right, I've eradicated more than my fair share of tribes and sects! If you're going to kill me for that, then go ahead!" Yin Tianyuan provoked with no fear in his eyes whatsoever.

Right as Han Li was about to slay the four men, Yin Tianyuan's skin suddenly took on a crimson complexion, and he began to cackle in a high-pitched voice, much like the cries of an ape.

His cackling was imbued with some type of peculiar law powers that struck Han Li with a burst of sharp pain in his eardrums, despite his incredible physical constitution.

Yin Tianhu, Yin Tianlu, and Yin Tianxiong immediately pounced on this opportunity to dart back in retreat away from the flying swords resting against their throats.

In contrast, Yin Tianyuan pounced directly at Han Li instead of retreating with his brothers.

"Run! I'll keep him here while you three get away!" Yin Tianyuan yelled as he crashed toward Han Li, while his body began to swell up like a balloon.

"Tianyuan!" Yin Tianxiong yelled as he turned around to rush back to Yin Tianyuan, only to be stopped by Yin Tianhu.

"Tianyuan has already used the Red Lotus Destruction Arts, so he's beyond saving. Don't let his sacrifice be in vain!" Yin Tianhu yelled as he dragged Yin Tianxiong away.

Right at this moment, a dull thump rang out as a ball of radiant crimson light erupted forth in all directions.

Han Li remained completely unfazed as he conjured up his True Extreme Film to easily keep out the oncoming crimson light.

Yin Tianhu's trio was shocked and horrified to see this, and they hurriedly fled for their lives in different directions.

A layer of black flames emerged over Yin Tianhu's body as he sped away into the distance as a massive, black fireball.

Meanwhile, Yin Tianlu devoured an azure pill, and a giant, azure deer projection instantly appeared around him before galloping away as a streak of azure light.

As for Yin Tianxiong, a layer of rippling black light had appeared over his body, and he abruptly vanished into the ground.

In response, Han Li lashed out with his left fist while making a hand seal with his right hand, and at the same time, a blurry sword projection shot out of his glabella before vanishing into thin air.

Immediately thereafter, a golden fist projection the size of a house appeared behind Yin Tianhu amid a burst of spatial fluctuations before crashing into him, instantly snuffing out the black flame around him before smashing his body into smithereens.

At the same time, a golden flying sword appeared in front of Yin Tianlu, catching him completely off guard, and his body was sliced into two before he had a chance to take any evasive measures.

Deep underground, Yin Tianxiong was fleeing as quickly as he could when a translucent sword projection suddenly appeared beside him before plunging into his head.

A bloodcurdling howl rang out from underground before immediately fading into silence, while Weeping Soul reached out to make a grabbing motion with her hands, and three nascent souls flew into her grasp from different directions.

At this moment, there were four nascent souls hovering above her hands, and they were struggling with all their might to break free, but it was a completely futile endeavor.

"Make sure to examine their memories before you devour their souls," Han Li said.

He had stormed into the Golden Origin Immortal Palace on this occasion not just to kill Dongfang Bai and the others, but also because there was an interregion teleportation array in the Golden Origin Immortal Palace that could take him straight to other immortal regions.

Now that he had already completely exposed himself, continuing to stay in the Golden Origin Immortal Region was no longer an option, so he wanted to leave this place as soon as possible.

"I'm not going to devour their filthy souls," Weeping Soul harrumphed coldly. "After I've searched their souls, I'm going to refine them into soul tools to torture them for ten thousand years!"

As soon as her voice trailed off, she began to chant an incantation, unleashing a soul search technique.

Meanwhile, a burst of golden lightning erupted out of Han Li's body to encompass Weeping Soul, following which he set off in pursuit of Dongfang Bai.

It hadn't taken him very long at all to slay the Five Heavenly Yin Disciples, and Dongfang Bai was still within his spiritual sensory range.

After tracking down Dongfang Bai with his spiritual sense, he set off at an astonishing speed, and it didn't take long before the distance between them was whittled down to no more than several hundred kilometers.

Han Li harrumphed coldly as he swept a sleeve through the air, and his seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly combined as one, forming a thick bolt of lightning that caught up to Dongfang Bai in the blink of an eye before crashing down upon him with almighty power.

[1]. In Chinese, tiger is pronounced as "hu", so Yin Tianhu's name ends in tiger, and the names of his siblings all follow the same formula, with the prefix of Yin Tian, followed by their respective animal, ie. deer (lu), bear (xiong), ape (yuan), and eagle (ying).

[Back]

Chapter 1025: Job Done

In response, Dongfang Bai turned around and opened his mouth to release a large azure flag, and countless peculiar green flowers emerged from the flag, forming a floral bouquet to oppose the oncoming bolt of lightning.

A rich aroma that was imbued with a type of special law powers wafted through the air, and the power of the bolt of lightning was greatly diminished by this strange fragrance.

As a result, it was only able to pierce through a large chunk of the floral bouquet before being stopped in its tracks.

Right at this moment, Dongfang Bai swooped down toward a particularly massive golden palace down below before vanishing into it in a flash.

A resounding thunderclap rang out as Han Li appeared in the sky above before also descending toward the palace, and at the same time, the bolt of golden lightning exploded to completely eradicate what little remained of the floral bouquet.

The azure flag re-emerged, having already been torn to shreds, while the bolt of golden lightning flew up Han Li's sleeve in a flash.

Han Li appeared in front of the palace in an instant, and he was just about to fly in when the gates of the palace swung shut amid a burst of loud rumbling.

The gates were over a hundred feet tall, and they were giving off an indestructible black gleam.

The gates were also riddled with antiquated golden patterns that formed numerous swords of different sizes, and it was clearly an extremely formidable restriction.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he stopped cold in his tracks, and after taking a moment to inspect his surroundings, he asked, "Have you finished searching their souls, Weeping Soul? What is this place?"

"Hold on a second, Master," Weeping Soul replied as she continued carrying out her soul search.

All of a sudden, an alarmed look appeared on her face as she exclaimed, "This is the teleportation palace of the Golden Origin Immortal Palace! The interregion teleportation array is in there!"

"So he's trying to get away, is he?" Han Li harrumphed coldly as he instantly transformed into a devilish deity with three heads and six arms, and over nine hundred profound acupoints lit up over his body, glowing as radiantly as stars in the night sky.

Three bursts of true spirit bloodline powers rose up within his body, releasing a devastating aura of destruction.

Han Li let loose a thunderous roar as he lashed out at the palace gates with all six fists, but Weeping Soul hurriedly called out, "That won't work, Master! These gates were crafted using Idol Stones, one of the hardest materials under the heavens. On top of that, the restrictions on these gates are also extremely powerful and not to be dealt with through brute force. I've already found the way to deactivate the restriction, so allow me to..."

However, Han Li's fists had already struck the palace gates before she had a chance to finish.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the entire palace trembled violently, and countless cracks instantly appeared over the palace gates.

Close to ten thousand streaks of golden swordlight erupted out of the gates, forming a giant sword array that converged toward Han Li.

This sword array was even more formidable than what Han Li was able to unleash with his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, but all he did was open his mouth to release a burst of green light, which spread out in all directions to sweep up all of the streaks of golden sword light.

Immediately thereafter, the burst of green light vanished alongside all of the streaks of golden swordlight, and it was as if they had never existed at all.

After the green light faded away, Han Li slammed his six giant fists into the palace gates once again, completely shattering them and reducing them to rubble.

Only then did he recall that Weeping Soul seemed to have been trying to communicate something urgently to him, and he turned to her as he asked, "What did you just say?"

"N-nothing..." Weeping Soul stammered as she stared blankly at the wreckage of the palace gates, while Han Li rushed straight into the palace.

The palace was circular in shape, and it had a diameter of several thousand feet. There were dozens of white stone pillars in the palace, supporting the roof above, and at the center of the palace was a golden array that was riddled with countless profound runes and around five hundred to six hundred feet in diameter.

There were twelve silver stone pillars around the array, engraved upon each of which was a relief of a majestic silver dragon.

At this moment, Dongfang Bai was busy at work inside the array, quickly placing silver crystals into the slots on the twelve silver stone pillars.

The slots on half of the stone pillars had already been filled, and they were glowing with radiant silver light that converged toward the center of the array.

Han Li crashed down into the palace, stomping a pair of enormous craters into the ground and causing the entire palace to tremble violently.

"This is impossible! How could you have made it in here so quickly?!" Dongfang Bai roared in an incredulous manner.

"This is the end of the road for you, Dongfang Bai."

Han Li slowly emerged from the cloud of dust that had been raised by his landing, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

Dongfang Bai's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly abandoned the array to flee for his life.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face as countless golden ripples erupted out of his Mantra Treasured Axis, instantly filling the entire hall.

Dongfang Bai abruptly reappeared near the entrance of the palace amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, having been completely immobilized by Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis.

Han Li reverted back to his human form, then flicked a finger through the air, releasing a golden sword projection that pierced straight through Dongfang Bai's dantian.

The nascent soul inside was destroyed in the process, confirming that this was undoubtedly Dongfang Bai's true body.

A look of relief appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and his Mantra Treasured Axis faded away at his behest, but immediately thereafter, a ball of green light flew out of Dongfang Bai's body before shooting out of the palace.

"Weeping Soul!" Han Li called out, and she immediately appeared in front of the fleeing soul in a wraith-like manner before trapping it in her grasp.

The ball of green light was struggling with all its might, and it was clearly significantly more powerful than the souls of the Five Heavenly Yin Disciples, but it was still unable to break free.

Dongfang Bai's face appeared within the ball of green light, and he hurriedly said in a frantic manner, "My sincerest apologies for my past transgressions against you, fellow daoists. Please spare my life, and I'm willing to hand over all of the wealth that the Golden Origin Immortal Palace and I have accumulated over the years.

“The Golden Origin Immortal Region is a very fertile immortal region with countless riches to be harvested, so I'm sure you won't be disappointed with what I have to offer."

Han Li merely smiled and offered no response.

As for Weeping Soul, she had been very close with Ye Susu, so she had zero intention of letting Dongfang Bai off the hook, and she was glowering resentfully at his soul.

Dongfang Bai's heart sank slightly at the sight of Weeping Soul's hateful expression, and he turned to Han Li as he continued, "Fellow Daoist Han, I can serve you for the rest of my existence as a ghostly slave. With my current cultivation base, even after I'm converted into a ghostly slave, my powers won't diminish much, so I'll definitely be of help to you.

“The Nine Origins Temple has already sent powerful cultivators to come and capture you, and you'll only be able to escape from them with my help. Otherwise, even if you kill me, you'll fall into the hands of the Nine Origins Temple!"

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

"Master, we can't let him go after what he did to the Azure Fox Tribe! If you want to know anything from him, then I can just search his soul and tell you!" Weeping Soul hurriedly said.

It had become very clear that Han Li was the decision-maker here, so Dongfang Bai felt no need to respect Weeping Soul, and he harrumphed coldly, "I've cultivated a soul locking secret technique that makes my soul impossible to search. If you try to use a soul search technique on me, you'll only be able to destroy my soul at most!"

"Please trust me, Master! My law powers specifically target souls, so I'm sure that I can search his soul even if others can't!" Weeping Soul urged in a frantic manner.

"Rest assured, Weeping Soul, I never had any intention of sparing him. Go ahead and search his soul. Even if you end up destroying his soul in the process, it hardly matters to me," Han Li said.

"Thank you, Master!" Weeping Soul said in an ecstatic manner, then immediately sprang into action before Dongfang Bai had a chance to say anything.

Countless crimson runes surged out of her hands before infiltrating Dongfang Bai's soul, and a bloodcurdling howl rang out, but the soul didn't explode.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this. It seemed that Weeping Soul's law powers really did trump Dongfang Bai's soul locking secret technique.

With that in mind, he strode over to Dongfang Bai's body, then removed a storage ring from one of its fingers before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

Moments later, a pleased look appeared on his face as he swept a sleeve through the air to produce a small pile of the silver crystals that Dongfang Bai had been using just now.

He wasted no time, picking up the crystals before placing them into the vacant slots on the silver pillars.

Even though he wasn't able to find any information on this teleportation array in Dongfang Bai's storage ring, it was only going to be a matter of time before Weeping Soul dug this information out of Dongfang Bai's memories.

All he had to do was ready the array, and once Weeping Soul found out how to operate it, they would be able to leave this place right away.

Chapter 1026: More Trouble

Before long, all of the remaining slots on the silver pillars in the palace had been filled, and after looking around to ensure that nothing was amiss, Han Li made a hand seal, upon which the entire array began to glow with bright silver light.

At the same time, an elated look appeared on Weeping Soul's face as the black light over her hands quickly faded away, revealing Dongfang Bai's soul again.

At this point, the soul was already extremely frail, and there was also a dull and dazed look in its eyes, indicating that all of its intelligence had been erased during the course of Weeping Soul's soul search.

"Master, this teleportation array is connected to four places, the Vast Golden Immortal Palace, the Middle Earth Immortal Palace, the..."

Right at this moment, a thick pillar of silver light erupted out of the array, illuminating the entire palace a bright silver color.

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he immediately rushed toward one of the silver pillars before reaching out to pluck out the silver crystals on it, but right at this moment, a translucent, spherical light barrier appeared around the array, encompassing the entire array and the twelve surrounding stone pillars within it.

Han Li crashed headfirst into the array before immediately being sent flying back, as if he had run into a soft and bouncy wall.

At the same time, two figures appeared within the pillar of silver light, one of whom had fiery red skin and disproportionately large hands and feet, presenting a bizarre sight to behold.

He was accompanied by a young man who was dressed in immortal envoy attire, and Han Li's expression changed drastically at the sight of the two figures as he grabbed onto Weeping Soul before flying outside.

He was able to identify the red-skinned man as none other than Patriarch Miro's traitorous disciple, Qi Mozi, and his tremendous aura indicated that he was a Great Encompassment cultivator.

As for the golden-robed young man with him, he was only at the late-Golden Immortal Stage.

If this were a normal Great Encompassment cultivator, then Han Li would be confident in his own ability to at least put up a fight, but Qi Mozi was also cultivating the laws of time, so directly engaging him in battle would clearly not be a wise option.

A hint of surprise appeared on Qi Mozi's face at the sight of the situation in the palace, following which his brows furrowed slightly as he caught sight of the fleeing Han Li.

He then turned to the golden-robed young man beside him, and the latter immediately confirmed, "That's him!"

An elated look appeared in Qi Mozi's eyes upon hearing this, and he immediately attempted to fly out of the array, but the spherical light barrier around the array was extremely resilient, and he was unable to break through, even with his Great Encompassment Stage powers.

At this point, Han Li had already flown out of the palace with Weeping Soul, and he turned around to take a glance at the two people in the teleportation array before sweeping a sleeve through the air, releasing a flurry of golden lightning that encompassed both himself and Weeping Soul, following which the two of them vanished from the spot.

Qi Mozi harrumphed coldly as a golden torch appeared in front of him, and it was none other than the Time Severing Torch.

Compared with Han Li Time Severing Torch, Qi Mozi's was around twice the size, and aside from the golden flame on top of it, the rest of the torch also had a substantial form, unlike Han Li's, which had a more illusory and intangible appearance.

There were over two thousand Time Dao Runes flashing on Qi Mozi's Time Severing Torch, and it was giving off time law power fluctuations far more formidable than those of Han Li's Time Severing Torch.

The flame on the torch swelled up at Qi Mozi's behest, releasing waves of fiery spiritual light that instantly spread over the entire surrounding area in a radius of around a thousand feet.

The surrounding spherical light barrier was instantly enveloped within the fiery spiritual light, and the spiritual power circulation in the light barrier was instantly brought to a complete standstill. It was a similar effect to that of Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis, but even more potent.

The golden-robed young man had also been completely immobilized by the fiery spiritual light, but Qi Mozi remained unaffected as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of golden light that struck the spherical light barrier.

The burst of golden light wasn't giving off any formidable aura, but it was able to shatter the spherical light barrier with ease, immediately following which the Time Severing Torch and the surrounding, fiery spiritual light faded in unison, and everything returned to normal.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and the golden-robed young man had a chance to react, Qi Mozi had already flown out of the palace.

Countless golden shadows flew out of his body before racing away in all directions, following which his eyes lit up slightly as he made a hand seal, and countless flame-shaped runes surged out of his body as well, forming a radiant, golden array around him in the blink of an eye.

Bursts of golden flames erupted out of the array to envelop his entire body, and in the next instant, he abruptly vanished from the spot.

The golden-robed young man hurriedly flew out of the palace as well, but at this point, Han Li and Qi Mozi were already nowhere to be seen.

The young man heaved a forlorn sigh upon seeing this, then flew away in another direction as a ball of golden light.

Meanwhile, Han Li and Weeping Soul reappeared amid a flash of golden lightning above a mountain that was close to a hundred thousand kilometers away from the Golden Origin Immortal Palace.

"Who was that man just now?" Weeping Soul asked.

"He's from the Heavenly Court's Immortal Prison, perhaps even the chief warden of the Immortal Prison," Han Li replied.

"The chief warden of the Immortal Prison!" Weeping Soul exclaimed.

"Now's not the time to talk. We're still not safe yet, so we have to leave this place right away," Han Li said as he made a hand seal, and countless arcs of golden lightning sprang out of his body, quickly forming a golden lightning array that was several dozen feet in size.

Right at this moment, a ball of dazzling golden light appeared in the distance, giving off bursts of spatial fluctuations.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which he and Weeping Soul vanished from within the golden lightning array.

Meanwhile, the ball of golden light unfurled to form a fiery golden array with Qi Mozi within it, and a cold sneer appeared on his face at the sight of the lightning array, which was still yet to fully dissipate.

After taking a moment to detect which direction Han Li had gone in, he conjured up another fiery golden array around himself before vanishing from the spot.

Han Li and Weeping Soul reappeared somewhere within the Golden Origin Mountain Range amid a flash of golden lightning, and a concerned look appeared on Weeping Soul's face as she asked, "What do we do, Master? That Qi Mozi is also adept in spatial teleportation!"

A grim look had appeared on Han Li's face as well, and as soon as he steadied himself, he immediately conjured up another lightning array.

However, before he had a chance to activate the array, another ball of golden flames appeared in the distance, and this one was traveling even faster than before.

Han Li immediately activated his lightning teleportation array to teleport himself and Weeping Soul away, only for Qi Mozi to instantly appear before conjuring up another spatial teleportation array as well.

With that, a game of cat and mouse ensued, and before long, the three of them were already countless kilometers away from the Golden Origin Immortal Palace.

Even though Han Li was the one leading Qi Mozi on a chase, the latter was gradually becoming more and more familiar with Han Li's lightning array, and the gap between them was constantly dwindling.

Han Li and Weeping Soul reappeared once again amid a flash of golden lightning, this time above a cliff in the Golden Origin Mountain Range.

It wasn't that Han Li didn't want to send Weeping Soul into the Flower Branch domain. Instead, the problem was that Weeping Soul was a living being, so in order to enter the Flower Branch domain, a spatial door had to be opened first, and there was simply no time for Han Li to do this with Qi Mozi so hot on his heels.

As soon as the two of them reappeared, Han Li immediately made a hand seal to conjure up another lightning array.

"He's getting closer and closer, Master. At this rate, he'll catch up to us soon. Do you have any way to lose him?" Weeping Soul asked.

"The teleportation technique that he's using combines the powers of fire and space, and it's fundamentally very similar to my lightning teleportation array. If I can teleport a massive distance away in one go, that should be enough to shake him off," Han Li replied.

Before the lightning array had a chance to fully take shape, Qi Mozi suddenly appeared nearby amid a flash of golden fire, and he sneered, "You'll have to almost teleport yourself entirely out of the Golden Origin Mountain Range in one go if you want to get away from me!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, a long, black ribbon of light that was over a thousand feet in length erupted out of the golden fire, and it was traveling at an astonishing speed, striking the lightning array in the blink of an eye.

The lightning array didn't have much defensive properties to begin with, and it was instantly destroyed upon contact.

Han Li hurriedly darted back in retreat with Weeping Soul, only just barely managing to evade the black ribbon, which continued to pursue them.

While flying back in retreat, Han Li channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and lashed out with his fist, releasing a golden fist projection to clash against the black ribbon.

The golden fist projection was instantly sliced into two, while the black ribbon drew to a momentary halt before continuing to fly through the air.

Han Li's expressions changed slightly upon seeing this, and he yelled for Weeping Soul to hold tightly onto him before unleashing a rapid flurry of punches, sending a torrential barrage of golden fist projections crashing into the black ribbon.

A string of earth-shattering booms rang out as the black ribbon gradually faded over time, and after slicing through countless fist projections, it finally vanished entirely.

At this point, Han Li was already slightly out of breath.

His physical body had already been severely taxed during his battle against Dongfang Bai, and he had just thrown thousands of punches in the blink of an eye, which was certainly not helping his condition.

Chapter 1027: Stubborn Pursuit

Weeping Soul's eyes had been shut while she clung to Han Li, and upon opening her eyes, she immediately asked in a concerned voice, "Are you alright, Master?"

"I'm fine. He's coming again," Han Li said in a grim manner as he cast his gaze toward a certain direction.

"It looks like you do have some tricks up your sleeve. No wonder you were able to kill Dongfang Bai," Qi Mozi remarked with a smile as he flew out of a ball of golden fire in the distance.

At this moment, he was holding a glowing, black hatchet, and it seemed that the ribbon of black light had been unleashed by this hatchet.

For some reason, Han Li felt as if his entire body were being laid bare under Qi Mozi's scrutiny, and only after channeling his time law powers was he able to just barely ward off this sensation.

"Who are you? I don't recall ever meeting you before this."

Even though Han Li was well aware of who Qi Mozi was, he still decided to try and employ some stalling tactics.

"Did neither of my two disciples show you an image of me? I am Qi Mozi. I'm sure you've already heard of that name. I don't want to waste any more time here, hand over the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and I'll spare you your life," Qi Mozi said as he began to approach Han Li.

Han Li's heart jolted slightly upon hearing this, but his expression remained completely unchanged as he asked, "The Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra? What's that? A cultivation art?"

"You really are just as sly and uncooperative as Chi Rong told me you were! It doesn't matter whether you admit it or not, I'll just have to use a soul search technique on you," Qi Mozi sneered as he launched himself at Han Li, who hurriedly flew back in retreat.

"Leave me behind, Master. Focus on dealing with him, I can look after myself," Weeping Soul said, but Han Li paid no heed to her.

"What a chivalrous gentleman you are! Rest assured, I never kill women. All I want is your soul!" Qi Mozi chortled as he swung his hatchet through the air, releasing a ribbon of black light that was several times brighter and wider than before, and it was also almost twice as fast as the previous one, reaching Han Li in the blink of an eye.

The space around the ribbon of black light was shattered like a mirror, forming countless spatial rifts that converged toward the center from all sides.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face as he hurriedly released his Mantra Treasured Axis, sending countless golden ripples surging through the air to encompass the ribbon of black light.

The black ribbon was instantly stopped in its tracks, but the golden ripples also shuddered violently, seemingly struggling to hold themselves together.

"Oh? How remarkable that you've managed to cultivate the Mantra Axis Scripture to this extent," Qi Mozi mused with a surprised expression, but he remained unfazed as he raised his hatchet once again.

Right at this moment, a golden spirit domain erupted out of Han Li's body, encompassing the entire surrounding area within a radius of several kilometers.

Enshrouded within the spirit domain, Qi Mozi's movements were instantly slowed down to a crawl.

Simultaneously using both his Mantra Treasured Axis and his time spirit domain was extremely taxing on Han Li's immortal spiritual power, but he paid no heed to this as he swept both sleeves through the air, releasing around a dozen lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood, which immediately formed a circle around him.

Radiant golden lightning erupted out of the lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood before converging around Han Li.

Qi Mozi could see what Han Li was attempting to do, and he immediately released his own fiery spirit domain, encompassing an area that was several dozen kilometers in radius.

Han Li's movements were immediately slowed down significantly under the effects of Qi Mozi's spirit domain, but he was still doing his best to activate the Lightning Restraining Wood Array.

Right as the array was about to be completed, Qi Mozi let loose a loud roar as he conjured up his Time Severing Torch.

Waves of fiery spiritual light erupted out of the torch, bringing everything around it to a complete standstill, and the spiritual light was spreading extremely quickly, almost instantly reaching Han Li and Weeping Soul.

Han Li and the surrounding lightning array were instantly immobilized, as was the Mantra Treasured Axis, having been completely dominated by Qi Mozi's Time Severing Torch.

Qi Mozi's expression eased slightly as he swung his hatchet through the air, unleashing another ribbon of black light that struck the golden ripples around Han Li, instantly shattering them with ease.

The black ribbon then continued sweeping toward Han Li, but right at this moment, a golden jade vial suddenly appeared on Han Li's left, while a golden hourglass appeared on his right.

A golden torch then emerged in front of him, while a small, golden tree sprouted behind him.

The five time-attribute law treasures seemed to be able to resonate with one another, and all of the Time Dao Runes on their surfaces lit up, releasing a burst of incredibly formidable time law power fluctuations.

Fifty time law threads shot out of the five time-attribute law treasures, then connected together to form a golden ring that released a burst of powerful suction force.

Qi Mozi's spirit domain began to shudder violently, and bursts of fiery spiritual light were sucked into the golden ring, much to his astonishment.

At the same time, the time-slowing effect on Han Li and the lightning array around him was undone, and he immediately made a hand seal, instantly completing the array.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of radiant golden lightning erupted out of the array to encompass both Han Li and Weeping Soul, and extremely formidable spatial fluctuations were surging out of the golden lightning in all directions.

A furious look appeared on Qi Mozi's face upon seeing this, and the black hatchet in his hand instantly swelled to around ten times its original size, transforming into an enormous black ax.

A burst of incredibly violent law power fluctuations erupted out of the ax, and the nearby space was already beginning to collapse.

Qi Mozi grabbed onto the ax with both hands before swinging it viciously down upon the lightning array, unleashing a giant ribbon of black light that was around half a kilometer wide and several kilometers in length.

All of the space in its wake was completely shattered, creating countless spatial vortexes in the surrounding area.

The sky instantly turned pitch-black as dark clouds converged up above, but it was already too late.

A rumbling thunderclap rang out as Han Li and Weeping Soul vanished from the spot, immediately following which the black ribbon descended, tearing the lightning array apart while also destroying the lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood.

A dark look appeared on Qi Mozi's face as he stowed his black hatchet away, following which he closed his eyes to try and track Han Li.

Around fifteen minutes later, he reopened his eyes, and his expression had darkened even further.

However, a fervent look then appeared in his eyes as he chuckled to himself, "So you really are in possession of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra. This cultivation art allows the user to absorb all other time law powers. As expected of the most powerful time-attribute cultivation art of them all!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he flew back in the direction of the Golden Origin Immortal Palace as a streak of golden light.

......

Deep within the Golden Origin Mountain Range, countless kilometers away from the Golden Origin Immortal Palace.

There was a stone chamber that was several dozen feet in size dug out inside an enormous golden mountain.

The walls of the stone chamber were riddled with spirit patterns that were giving off lights of different colors, and there was a golden lightning array arranged on the ground.

Around a dozen lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood were standing around the array, and all of them were flashing with golden lightning.

All of a sudden, the golden lightning array lit up as an enormous pillar of golden light erupted into the heavens.

All of the spirit patterns in the stone chamber instantly lit up, conjuring up several layers of light barriers that contained all of the law power fluctuations and pillars of golden light released by the array.

The pillar of golden light only lingered for a few seconds before fading away to reveal Han Li and Weeping Soul, the latter of which was looking around with an intrigued expression.

"As a safety precaution, I set up this Lightning Restraining Wood Array here prior to going to the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, and I'm glad I made that decision. This place is extremely far away from the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, so Qi Mozi won't be able to track us here," Han Li said as he withdrew the five time-attribute law treasures around him.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swayed unsteadily before falling to one knee, and blood began to trickle down from the corner of his lips.

"Master, are you injured?" Weeping Soul exclaimed as she hurriedly grabbed onto Han Li to support him.

"While I was activating the lightning array, I sustained some internal injuries from the law power fluctuations released by Qi Mozi's ax projection," Han Li explained as he summoned a green pill before devouring it.

"Thank heavens you prepared this lightning array in advance. Otherwise, we would've been in major trouble. Should we stay here for a while so that you can rest and recover?" Weeping Soul asked.

"The Lightning Restraining Wood Array caused a massive commotion just now, and even with the restrictions I set up, there's no guarantee that it wouldn't have attracted any attention, so let's leave this place first," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light that disassembled the lightning array on the ground, while a series of array flags also flew out of the surrounding stone chamber before falling into his grasp.

After stowing these items away, Han Li conjured up another golden lightning array, and the two of them vanished amid a flash of golden lightning.

Chapter 1028: Strange Spring

Somewhere in the Golden Origin Mountain Range, there was a secluded mountain.

A rumbling thunderclap rang out as a golden lightning array appeared above the mountain before vanishing in a flash, following which two figures plummeted out of the sky, crashing down into a dense forest on the mountain summit.

A string of loud thumps rang out as several giant trees were felled before the two figures finally collapsed beside a giant rock.

The two figures were none other than Han Li and Weeping Soul, and the latter called out in an urgent voice, "Master!"

She then hurriedly helped Han Li up into a seated position.

At this moment, Han Li's robes were in tatters, and there was a wry smile on his face as he said, "I'm fine, it's just that I've completely exhausted my immortal spiritual power reserves."

"That Qi Mozi really is a despicable man! He swooped in right as you were in a vulnerable condition after your battle against Dongfang Bai," Weeping Soul complained.

Han Li took a deep breath, then said, "He really did appear at the worst possible time for us. We're still not safe yet, so we have to keep going after I take a short rest."

Weeping Soul nodded in response, and Han Li devoured a pill before sitting down with his legs crossed to meditate.

Some time later, he opened his eyes, looking in slightly better condition than before, and as he rose to his feet, Weeping Soul hurriedly did the same before arriving by his side.

"Master, I'm afraid Qi Mozi most likely isn't going to be the only one coming after us. Before we arrived at the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, Dongfang Bai contacted a Great Encompassment cultivator of the Nine Origins Temple, who told him that she would send the Lan siblings after us," Weeping Soul said in an urgent manner.

"The Lan siblings..." Han Li murmured to himself.

"They seem to be quite powerful. Dongfang Bai doesn't have many memories of them, but I can tell that he has a lot of trust in them," Weeping Soul added.

"We've already killed Dongfang Bai, so there's no need to entangle ourselves with these people any further. The Golden Origin Immortal Palace's territory is mainly focused in the western region of the Golden Origin Mountain Range, while the central and eastern regions are under the control of countless immortal sects and clans.

“Given how complex the situation in those regions is, they should make for good hiding spots for us, so let's leave this place right away," Han Li said, and Weeping Soul nodded in response.

"In order to prevent being tracked, I'm going to be temporarily sealing away my own immortal spiritual power and traveling solely using my physical powers. During this time, I'll get you to stay in the Flower Branch domain to rest and recover," Han LI said as he conjured up a door of silver light, and Weeping Soul readily obliged, stepping through the door of light and into the bamboo pavilion.l

After closing the door of light, Han Li took a glance up at the sky, then sprang up into the clouds.

......

Two years flew by in a flash.

There was a long mountain range in the central region of the Golden Origin Mountain Range, within which was a small and unremarkable col by the name of the Azure Silk Col.

Inside the col was a village called the Spare Food Village that was completely isolated from the rest of the world, and the village had several hundred residents.

One night, the Spare Food Village was brightly lit, and not a single villager had retired to their beds. Instead, all of them had changed into clothes woven using bamboo fibers, and they were holding torches and banging on gongs and drums as they carried several bamboo sedan chairs toward the foot of the mountain behind the village.

The sedan chairs were all occupied by elderly men with heads of white hair, and they looked as if they were not long for this world.

Amid all of the villagers was a tall, azure-robed man who stuck out like a sore thumb in the crowd.

He was walking alongside a young man who was leading the way, and he asked, "Where are we going, Chief?"

The man that was being referred to as chief was quite youthful in appearance, but he possessed a pair of eyes that seemed to have seen far more than his age would suggest.

"We're going to White Head Valley, Doctor Han," the village chief replied.

This Doctor Han was none other than Han Li.

Half a month ago, he just so happened to arrive in the village, which was suffering from a plague, and he decided to help them to do a good deed. As a result, he became revered as a miracle-working doctor, and the villagers insisted that he stay and enjoy some hospitality.

Han Li initially had no intention of staying in the village for long, but after spending two days in the village, he discovered some very abnormal things. For example, this village chief appeared to be no more than forty years of age, but in reality, he had already lived for over five hundred years.

Mortals in the Immortal Realm enjoyed longer lifespans than those in other realms, but even so, their lifespans were usually capped at around two hundred fifty years. None of these villagers were cultivators, so it didn't make sense for them to be able to live this long.

"Why are we going there?" Han Li asked.

A hesitant look appeared on the village chief's face, following which he replied, "You saved our village, so I'm not going to keep this a secret from you any longer, Doctor Han. How old do you think those people on the sedan chairs are?"

"They look to be around a hundred and fifty years old to me," Han Li replied.

"That's right, all of them are indeed roughly that age. However, they are actually juniors of mine as I'm currently five hundred and thirteen years old," the village chief revealed.

"What?" Han Li exclaimed as he feigned a stunned expression.

The village chief smiled at the sight of Han Li's stunned expression, then patted him on the shoulder as he said, "There's no need to be so surprised, Doctor Han. Truth be told, there are people in this village who are even older than me."

"How is that possible? Could it be that you've all obtained some type of miraculous medicine?" Han Li asked.

"It's all thanks to a spring in the White Head Valley," the village chief explained.

"A spring? What kind of springwater could possibly extend one's lifespan to such an extent?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know what to tell you. It's a very strange spring that only appears once every over a hundred years, and whenever it appears, we'll carry those in our village who are about to die of old age into the valley. There, they'll soak in the spring for a day and a night before we return to collect them," the villager replied.

"Could it be that bathing in the spring can restore one's youth?" Han Li asked.

"It's kind of like that, but it's not that simple. The spring only works some of the time. Sometimes, the people bathing in it end up dead, while other times, their youth is restored. It's all down to luck," the village chief explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a contemplative nod.

"You're still in your prime at the moment, so don't try to bathe in the spring, Doctor Han. The spring can restore one's youth, but it can't cure ailments, so we can still die from illness. I'm telling you this because I would like you to stay and live in our village. That way, far fewer of us will die from illness, and in return, you'll hopefully be able to live a long life thanks to this spring," the village chief said.

"I'm but a traveling doctor, so I'm truly honored that you think so highly of me, Chief. Having said that, this is quite a significant decision for me to make, so would I be able to think about it before getting back to you?" Han Li asked.

"Of course," the village chief replied with a smile.

The two of them continued onward, and their conversation gradually shifted to more mundane small talk. The village chief was still very keen to convince Han Li to stay, and he asked Han Li if he had a wife.

He then offered to introduce to Han Li a woman in the village, one that was already around a hundred years of age, but still had the appearance of a young woman, leaving Han Li both amused and exasperated.

Due to the fact that they were traveling on foot at a mortal pace, it was already past midnight by the time arrived in the White Head Valley.

The valley was completely silent, but the jagged rocks on the mountain faces on either side of the valley appeared to be rather sinister under the dim light of the moon.

Upon entering the valley, the atmosphere became very solemn, and looks of awe and veneration had appeared in the eyes of all of the villagers.

Deep within the valley were two enormous rocks that were leaning against each other to form a triangular archway, beneath which was a spring that was no more than a hundred feet in size.

The water in the spring was extremely clear, and even under the dim light of the moon, it was possible to see the mud and leaves at the bottom of the spring.

Upon arriving by the spring, everyone joined their palms and closed their eyes in prayer, while the village chief began reciting a verbal prayer.

While no one was paying attention, Han Li drew a ball of water out of the spring and into his grasp, and after examining it for a moment, his brows furrowed slightly with intrigue.

Standing beside the spring, he could sense some barely detectable time law power fluctuations, but this ball of water from the spring was no different from any normal springwater.

Meanwhile, the village chief had already ordered for the elderly men to be carried down from their sedan chairs before being lowered into the spring.

The men sat down with their legs crossed, and the springwater reached all the way up to their chests.

After that, all of the villagers extended respectful bows toward the spring before leaving the valley, preparing to return a day and a night later.

On the way back, everyone was looking much more relaxed, and they quickly returned to the village.

Han Li bade farewell to the village chief before returning to his own thatch hut, but no more than a few minutes later, he snuck out of the hut again before quickly vanishing into the distance.

Chapter 1029: Investigation

Shortly thereafter, Han Li returned to the White Head Valley.

After hearing what the village chief had to say earlier, Han Li had determined that faint time law powers within the spring were able to alter the bodies of the villagers bathing inside, either restoring their youth or accelerating their deaths.

If he were to cultivate his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra here, then there was a very good chance that he would be able to make a breakthrough in a shorter time, thereby making him better equipped to deal with the likes of Qi Mozi.

However, the time law powers in the spring seemed to be rather inconsistent, and according to the village chief, it only appeared for short windows once every over a hundred years, so if he wanted to make use of it, he would have to find the root of the time law powers first.

Upon entering the valley, Han Li began to examine the jagged rocks on either side of it instead of immediately venturing deeper into the valley.

It didn't take long for him to notice that there were many golden seal text runes engraved onto the surrounding rocks.

Some of the runes were still relatively intact, while others were far less so, but all of them had already lost their original spiritual nature.

No wonder I detected some time law power fluctuations earlier, but I can't detect them now that I'm in here. It's quite remarkable that these runes have such a strong concealment effect even in their current state, Han Li thought to himself as he stroked one of the runes on a nearby giant rock.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him. If the concealment effect in this place was so potent, then why didn't he make this his new hiding place?

Over the past two years, even though he hadn't been caught by his Immortal Palace pursuers, they were constantly hot on his tail, keeping him constantly on edge. Every once in a while, he would release a puppet that bore a hint of his aura to try and confound his pursuers, but even so, he was still unable to truly shake them off.

With that in mind, Han Li began to carefully examine the White Head Valley while occasionally extending a finger to trace the runes engraved onto the rocks around him.

Only as the sun began to rise did he finally sit down onto a large rock, feeling thoroughly exhausted at this point.

After an entire night of work, Han Li manually restored most of the incomplete runes and also moved around many of the large rocks in the valley to restore the array inside as much as possible.

In the instant that his work was done, a cloud of mist instantly began to rise up, concealing the entire valley within it.

Han Li flew up into the air, then examined the valley with his spiritual sense for a moment to discover that he was no longer able to detect even the slightest bit of time law power fluctuations.

If even he couldn't detect anything with his spiritual sense, then it was extremely unlikely that anyone else would be able to.

After descending back into the valley, Han Li began to make his way toward the spring.

Upon arriving at the triangular archway, Han Li discovered that there was currently a layer of white mist over the spring as well. However, all of the mist was condensed under the two giant rocks, and none of it seeped out into the surrounding area.

Han Li swept his spiritual sense across the valley, upon which his expression changed ever so slightly, and he hurriedly flew over to the spring, where he spotted the elderly men that had been placed in the spring the night before.

All of them were looking extremely wizened and atrophied, clearly having already perished long ago.

Furthermore, the clothes on their bodies began to rapidly decay right before Han Li's eyes, following which their flesh also disintegrated, revealing the skeletons underneath.

"Looks like they weren't so lucky this time," Han Li sighed, then reached a hand into the spring before giving the water a gentle stir.

The water was cool to the touch, and it didn't appear to be remarkable in any way.

A perplexed look appeared on Han Li's face, but right at this moment, he suddenly felt a faint burst of warmth coming from somewhere deep within the spring. This warmer water was wrapping itself around his hand, and it was clearly smoother than the other water around it.

As soon as this burst of water came into contact with Han Li's hand, he immediately detected a burst of time law power fluctuations, following which the fine hairs on the back of his hand began to rapidly grow before falling away, and the cycle was repeated over and over again.

So the water here is capable of accelerating the flow of time. It looks like there really is some type of treasure hidden here.

With that in mind, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to pick up the skeletons before setting them down beside the spring, then waded into the spring himself.

Upon arriving at the source of the burst of warmer water in the spring, Han Li bent down to discover a small hole at the bottom of the spring.

He cleared away all of the small rocks around the hole to fully reveal it, but it didn't appear to be remarkable in any way.

How strange. Even my spiritual sense isn't able to detect anything out of the ordinary here...

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he looked up at the two giant rocks above, and in doing so, he discovered a ring-shaped rune inscribed onto each rock, but the two runes weren't giving off any spiritual power fluctuations.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes, and the runes immediately displayed a change in his eyes.

Deep within the giant rocks where the two runes had been engraved were two rings of golden light that were revolving incessantly in opposite directions.

An intrigued look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he rose up into the air before pressing his hands against the two ring-shaped runes.

At the same time, he channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and two bursts of golden light flowed out of his hands before injecting themselves into the ring-shaped runes.

The two runes instantly lit up as they began to revolve several times faster than before, and they each released a burst of golden light that came together to form a golden light barrier, which completely encompassed the space underneath the stone archway.

At this point, Han Li had already preemptively backed out of the stone archway, and he was observing the door of golden light before him with a wary expression.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he conjured up his True Extreme Film before flying into the light barrier.

The golden light barrier instantly vanished, and shortly thereafter, the water in the spring slowly seeped into the ground.

The entire spring gradually dried up, leaving only the skeletal remains of the elderly men laying on the loose rocks nearby.

......

There was a lone mountain standing on the border between the western and central regions of the Golden Origin Mountain Range.

At this moment, Qi Mozi was standing on the mountain summit with a broken puppet beneath his feet, looking into the distance.

"This is already the 136th puppet. Even though he left his blood essence on this puppet, he also planted a blood incinerating mark on it, so his blood essence would immediately be incinerated into nothingness as soon as we caught this puppet, leaving no trace behind for us. You were right, Xiong Shan, he really is a very cunning man," Qi Mozi mused.

At this moment, there was a young man standing behind Qi Mozi, and it was none other than Xiong Shan in his new body.

"I've had first-hand experience with Han Li's cunning and resourcefulness, and I paid a heavy price for my lack of preparedness. Even so, never did I think that he would develop so quickly, to the point that he's now posing a threat to the Heavenly Court," Xiong Shan said in a grim voice.

"I was originally planning to take him down in secret, but he stormed into the Golden Origin Immortal Palace and even killed Dongfang Bai, so there's no way the Heavenly Court will remain oblivious to him. Having said that, I suppose this also benefits me as I can now openly pursue him on behalf of the Immortal Prison," Qi Mozi mused.

"Judging from the route that he's taken, he appears to have traveled into the central area of the Golden Origin Immortal Region. The situation is very complex there, so we may not have the easiest of times pursuing him," Xiong Shan said in a hesitant manner.

"The Heavenly Court has already been discontent with the central area of the immortal region for a very long time, so if any sect dares to oppose us at this juncture, then it'll be a perfect opportunity to set an example. Rest assured, the leaders of all of the powerful sects and clans in this area are sly old foxes who would know that it's wise to stay out of our way.

“In fact, they'll most likely do everything to prevent Han Li from sneaking into their territory just to avoid getting caught up in this mess," Qi Mozi harrumphed coldly.

"That's true. Han Li always likes to act alone, so he most likely won't go into hiding in any sect or clan. Hence, I think we should focus the majority of our efforts on searching the areas that aren't overseen by any prominent powers," Xiong Shan said, and Qi Mozi nodded in agreement with this sentiment.

"Let's go. I detected his aura earlier, and he should be heading southeastward. Let's see how long he can keep running for!" Qi Mozi said as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a red flying boat with crimson flames burning around it.

The two of them leaped onto the boat, which then immediately flew away into the distance, quickly vanishing out of sight.

Chapter 1030: Metal Beast

In the instant that Han Li passed through the golden light barrier, he was immediately bound by countless golden threads that contained formidable law powers, suspending him in mid-air in an immobilized manner.

He looked down to discover a lush forest that was around several hundred kilometers in size below, and the forest was bordered by dense, gray mist. It was clear from this layout that this was a small secret area.

A series of small bluestone paths could be seen through the lush greenery, leading to a golden courtyard deep in the forest.

There's so much time law powers here! Han Li thought to himself as he took a glance at the golden threads around his own body.

This was a feeling akin to being restricted by the Mantra Treasured Axis, but his thoughts weren't affected. Even with his tremendous physical constitution, the incredibly sharp golden threads were slicing into his body, causing him great pain.

All of a sudden, his expression changed slightly as he spotted a cloud of dust rising up from the forest in the distance, and there were two giant, golden figures rushing toward him, destroying all of the greenery in their paths.

It was a pair of massive, golden tigers with wings growing out of their ribs, but the wings were disproportionately small compared to their bodies, so they couldn't use those wings to take flight.

As they continued rushing forward while flapping their wings, they began to rise up from the ground bit by bit en route to Han Li.

Are these metal beasts?

Even though these two creatures were beastly in form, their bodies were entirely comprised of extremely pure metal-attribute spiritual qi, allowing them to thrive in the environment of the Golden Origin Mountain Range.

As these thoughts ran through Han Li's mind, he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, and time law power fluctuations erupted out of his body, attempting to reach some type of balance with the golden threads around him.

As these time law power fluctuations surged out of his body, the golden threads began to unravel on their own, but at a rather slow rate.

After around twenty seconds, his body was still bound by several hundred golden threads, but at this point, the two giant metal beasts were already upon him, and both of them opened their cavernous mouths, with one of them biting down upon his head, while the other was chomping at his waist.

Burst of golden light that were imbued with extremely sharp metal-attribute spiritual qi could be seen gleaming over their sharp fangs, and even Han Li was struck by a sense of foreboding at the sight of them.

Right as their mouths were about to close around Han Li, a silver fire raven abruptly flew out of his body, then swelled drastically in size as it flapped its fiery wings and crashed directly into the pair of metal beasts.

Two resounding explosions rang out as specks of silver fire erupted in all directions, and the two metal beasts were forced back down to the ground by the Essence Fire Raven.

The two beasts let loose thunderous roars as they chomped down onto the Essence Fire Raven's wings, and even though the Essence Fire Raven had already flown back up into the sky, two large chunks were still torn off its fiery wings.

The metal beasts were completely unfazed by the scorching, silver flames, chewing a few times before directly devouring them, and a surprised look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

He knew better than anyone else just how formidable the Essence Fire Raven's flames were, so it was truly surprising to him that these two metal beasts were able to devour such flames.

All the while, more and more of the golden threads around his body continued to unravel in the face of his time law powers.

The Essence Fire Raven seemed to have been infuriated to have had parts of its wings torn away, and it swooped down from above like a fiery asteroid, transforming into a swirling tornado of silver flames that encompassed both of the metal beasts.

The silver tornado rose up into the heavens, and the fierce wind swept up by its revolution drastically elevated the temperatures of the flames. Situated within the fiery tornado, wisps of faint golden mist began to rise up from the bodies of the two metal beasts.

The bodies of these metal beasts were primarily comprised of metal-attribute spiritual qi, so that was most likely what this golden mist was.

Right at this moment, two thunderous roars rang out as the two metal beasts suddenly crashed headfirst into each other with a resounding boom.

A burst of blinding golden light instantly erupted out of their foreheads before sweeping through the air in all directions, slicing through the surrounding silver flames to allow the pair of metal beasts to escape from the fiery tornado.

The Essence Fire Raven's body had been split into two, and the two bursts of silver flames rose up into the air before attempting to fuse back together, but they were prevented from doing so by a layer of golden light between them.

As for the metal beast, they paid no further heed to the Essence Fire Raven as they charged directly at Han Li once again.

However, at this point, Han Li had already struggled free from the binding golden threads, and he took a step forward in mid-air, then channeled his Titan Vajra Arts as he lashed out with both fists.

A burst of radiant starlight emerged over his arms, and his fists struck the two metal beasts squarely on their foreheads amid a pair of resounding clangs.

Two bursts of powerful shockwaves erupted forth in all directions, and the two metal beasts were sent plummeting out of the sky before crashing down onto the ground, causing the earth to tremble violently.

Han Li took a glance at the Essence Fire Raven, which was still struggling to fuse itself back together, then continued pursuing the pair of metal beasts, raining down more punches upon them before they had a chance to crawl out of the crater in the ground.

Han Li's fists fell like rain, and after unleashing over a hundred punches, the entire surrounding area within a radius of several dozen kilometers had already been severely ravaged.

He was worried that if he were to keep this up, then the foundation of this entire secret area would be destroyed, so he stopped what he was doing, but as soon as he did so, his brows instantly became tightly furrowed.

As it turned out, the two metal beasts were already nowhere to be seen.

Han Li flew down to the bottom of the crater, and only then did he discover that the two metal beasts had already fled through an underground tunnel that they had dug.

"Let's go after those two first, then find a way to eradicate that golden light so you can return to your normal form," Han Li communicated to the Essence Fire Raven.

The two bursts of silver flames immediately stopped trying to fuse back together, and they transformed into a pair of identical silver fire ravens instead before landing on Han Li's shoulders.

Han Li took a glance at the entrance of the underground tunnel, then flew directly into it.

Due to the fact that the tunnel had only just been dug out, it was very hot and humid inside, and the entire tunnel was filled with the odor of mold and soil.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he advanced onward for close to ten kilometers, upon which he arrived at a crossroads.

The crossroads consisted of the tunnel that Han Li was currently traveling through, intersected by another wider tunnel with smooth and dry walls, indicating that it had been dug out long ago.

Furthermore, there were some air currents flowing through the other tunnel, and the air currents were very hot to the touch.

After sweeping his spiritual sense through the area, a faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he chuckled to the pair of fire ravens on his shoulders, "You're in luck..."

He then flew into the crossroads before taking the tunnel to his left, and after traveling for close to another ten kilometers, he arrived in a spacious underground area.

As soon as he arrived in this underground area, he spotted a five-colored fire pit that was over a thousand feet in size. The pit was filled with crimson, yellow, green, azure, and blue flames, and it was giving off waves of sweltering heat.

At this moment, the two metal beasts were laying beside the fiery pit, gnawing on a giant piece of golden ore, and with each bite that they took a small amount of metal-attribute spiritual qi would enter their bodies.

The two metal beasts immediately stood up at the sight of Han Li, and they bared their fangs at him in a menacing manner, but didn't dare to attack him again.

They've been constantly residing near this fire pit and feeding on ore that's tinged with the power of the five-colored flames, so it's No wonder they were able to devour my Flames of Essence.

At this point, the pair of fire ravens on Han Li's shoulders had also realized just how remarkable this five-colored fire pit was, and they were both jumping up and down in excitement.

"Go on," Han Li said with a smile, and the two fire ravens immediately flew toward the five-colored fire pit in unison.

The two metal beasts instantly sprang up into the air to try and stop the fire ravens, but in the blink of an eye, Han Li appeared beneath them in a wraith-like manner, then grabbed onto their tails before tugging them downard.

The two metal beasts were sent crashing heavily down onto the ground, then immediately scrambled to their paws before pouncing at Han Li.

Han Li channeled his Giant Mountain Ape bloodline, and tufts of golden fur appeared over his skin as he instantly transformed into a giant golden ape that was over a hundred feet tall, then pressed his hand down onto the two metal beasts' heads, forcing them firmly into the ground.

The two metal beasts struggled with all their might, and their tails were swinging around frantically like a pair of whips, but they were no match for Han Li's tremendous strength.

Chapter 1031: Diverse Interests

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he looked down at the pair of metal beasts beneath his hands.

If he wanted to kill these two metal beasts, then he was naturally perfectly capable of doing so, but he was feeling a little hesitant as he was thinking that it would not be a bad idea to send them into the Flower Branch domain to serve as a pair of guardian beasts.

Right at this moment, the tail of the two metal beasts suddenly wound themselves together, and a burst of radiant golden light appeared as the bodies of the two metal beasts suddenly liquefied, following which they fused as one to form a single giant golden tiger.

The combined golden tiger's wings were several times larger than before, but they were still rather disproportionate compared with the rest of its body.

So they can even fuse together! As expected of metal beasts formed by such pure metal-attribute spiritual qi.

The combined metal beast possessed a far superior aura to before, and it let loose a thunderous roar as it pounced at Han Li.

Right at this moment, the five-colored fire pit suddenly churned violently, and an enormous fiery bird flew out from within, then pecked down with its enormous silver beak.

Before Han Li had a chance to stop it, the fiery bird's beak had already pecked down onto the giant golden tiger, following which the creature was devoured whole.

What a pity.

Han Li heaved a forlorn internal sigh upon seeing this, while the fiery bird cocked its head to the side slightly, wondering why Han Li was looking so disappointed.

"It's fine. You've already eaten them, so it can't be helped. I'll just have to get Xiao Bai to look after the Flower Branch domain once we're reunited," Han Li said, and he promptly reverted back to his human form.

The enormous fiery bird also shrank down drastically in size before arriving at the edge of the fire pit.

Han Li strode over to it to discover that it was carrying four longan-sized beads on one of its wings. The beads were yellow, green, azure, and blue in color, corresponding with the colors of the flames in the pit.

The four beads were glowing radiantly while giving off bursts of stifling heat, and a look of surprise appeared on Han Li's face as he exclaimed, "You found this many beads of Rainbow Fire Pill Sand?"

The fiery bird's beak opened and closed a few times, and even though it uttered no sounds, Han Li was able to understand what it was trying to communicate.

"You're saying that there was also a crimson one, but you already ate it?"

The fiery bird nodded joyfully in response, causing the flames in the fire pit to ripple violently.

"I'm glad to hear it. If you can absorb all of these beads of Rainbow Fire Pill Sand, then your powers will be even further enhanced," Han Li said with a pleased smile.

The fiery bird was extremely excited, and it fell back into the fire pit before gliding gracefully through it on its back, as if it were performing a backstroke.

"Stay here and refine these pieces of Rainbow Fire Pill Sand, I'll go and see if there's anything else worthy of note here. If anything happens, notify me through our spiritual connection right away, and I'll come and find you," Han Li said.

The fire raven rose up out of the fire pit before swooping back down again, indicating that Han Li that it had understood his instructions.

Han Li briefly examined the area around the fire pit, and only after he was certain that nothing was amiss did he depart.

After passing through a gradually rising underground tunnel that was several thousand feet in length, Han Li emerged into a golden hall.

The hall was completely empty with the exception of three round, white jade cushions, upon which were engraved circles of complex patterns that resembled mazes.

After observing these patterns for a short while, Han Li was struck by a sense of dizziness, and he hurriedly steadied himself as an intrigued look appeared on his face.

He strode over to the cushions for a closer examination, and only then did he discover that the cushions were connected to the ground, making them impossible to move.

However, there didn't appear to be anything else special about them, and they displayed no changes in the face of injections of spiritual sense and immortal spiritual power.

After examining the cushions for a while longer, he lost interest and made his way out of the hall.

Only upon arriving outside the hall did he discover that he had already reached the cluster of golden buildings that he had previously seen from afar.

Outside the hall was a white stone plaza, which was also completely empty with the exception of a stone sundial at its center.

On the other side of the plaza was the entrance to this cluster of buildings.

After looking around momentarily, Han Li decided to make his way down a path beside the hall, and he passed through a small, circular archway to arrive in a floral garden.

There were all types of spirit flower and spirit trees planted in the garden, all of which were giving off immense world's oriqin qi.

Upon setting foot in the garden, Han Li's expression instantly changed slightly. Just like back at the spring before, he had once again detected a faint hint of time law powers.

However, the time law powers were quite scattered, and he was unable to determine its source. Instead, it seemed that the time law powers were spread throughout every single spirit flower in the entire garden.

Han Li casually plucked down a purple, nine-petaled night-blooming cereus before conducting a close examination, only to discover that it didn't contain any time law powers.

"How strange," Han Li murmured to himself as he made his way deeper into the garden.

Beyond the garden was a separate courtyard that had a total of three rooms.

Han Li entered the room on the left first to discover that it was also very sparsely furnished, with only a few bookshelves that were laden with books placed flush against the walls.

He picked out one of the books at random, and after flipping through it briefly, he discovered that it was only a poem anthology, as opposed to any profound scripture.

Han Li was rather perplexed as he picked out another book, and after briefly flipping through it, his expression became even more peculiar. This book wasn't a cultivation art or a poem anthology. Instead, it was an erotic novel.

Looks like the owner of this place has some very diverse interests!

After lingering in this room for a while, Han Li departed and made his way into the room on the right side of the courtyard.

This room contained a lot of antiques, including things like cultural artifacts, precious jewels, and chinaware, but there wasn't even a single spirit or immortal treasure inside.

Han Li couldn't help but feel a little exasperated by the tastes of this manor's former owner. Everything in his collection was tacky and ostentatious, giving them the impression of a man who possessed vast wealth, but no refined taste to speak of.

As Han Li entered the final room in the courtyard, he had already abandoned all hope of finding anything useful, but he discovered that it was a pill refinement chamber.

At the center of the chamber was a cauldron that was around half the height of an average human adult, and placed on either side of it was a wooden shelf, both of which were laden with containers of different sizes and colors.

The flame in the cauldron had already burned out, but there were many vials of pills on the wooden shelves. The pills of the highest caliber here were Spirit Sea Pills fit for consumption for High Zenith cultivators, while even the worst pills present were Dragon Forest Pills for Golden Immortals.

Finally, something useful!

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly as he stowed all of the pills away, and right as he was about to depart, his gaze suddenly fell upon the cauldron in the room.

He had just detected some faint spiritual power fluctuations from it.

He strode over the cauldron before lifting its lid, and as soon as he did so, a burst of golden light that contained extremely potent time law power fluctuations erupted out of the cauldron.

A surprised look appeared on his face as he peered into the cauldron to discover ten longan-sized pills sitting inside.

He drew one of the pills into his grasp, and after examining it closely for a moment, his brows furrowed ever so slightly.

These pills are on the verge of completion, so why didn't whoever was here see the refinement process through to the end?

After a brief hesitation, he placed the pill back into the cauldron, then replaced its lid as well.

He then reflexively attempted to summon his Essence Fire Raven to help him refine the pills, only to recall that it was currently refining the beads of Rainbow Fire Pill Sand, so he could only ignite the cauldron with his own nascent flame.

Forty-nine days flew by in a flash.

On this day, golden light was flashing incessantly within the pill refinement chamber, and there was a cloud of lingzhi-shaped golden mist above the cauldron that refused to dissipate.

So these pills were refined using the Flowing Fire Lingzhi as the primary ingredient. No wonder they contain such abundant time law powers even though they've already been left here in this incomplete state for countless years.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the nascent soul beneath the cauldron surged back into his body.

With another sweep of his sleeve, the cloud of golden mist dissipated, and the lid of the cauldron was lifted.

Han Li looked into the cauldron to discover that three of the ten pills inside were riddled with cracks, having been ruined during the final refinement process, but the remaining seven were all glowing brightly, and each of them had four dao patterns on their surface!

With these pills at his disposal, he would be able to make far faster progress in his cultivation of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

Chapter 1032: Seclusion

Han Li was ecstatic as he made a beckoning motion, and the seven pills flew out of the cauldron in a line before being drawn into a palm-sized jade vial.

After stowing the vial away, Han Li exhaled as he made his way out of the room.

From there, he took a glance at his surroundings, then conjured up a door of silver light, and Weeping Soul emerged from within.

"Where are we right now, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"We are currently in an unknown secret area that appears to be quite safe for now. I plan to go into seclusion here for some time. If I can make some strides in my cultivation base here, then we'll be better equipped to deal with the Immortal Palace cultivators on our tails," Han Li replied.

"After what we did at the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, I'm sure the Heavenly Court will be sending some very powerful cultivators after us, so it would indeed be a good idea to stay here for now. I'll keep a look out for you, go ahead and go into seclusion, Master," Weeping Soul said with a nod.

"The entrance of this secret area is over there," Han Li said as he pointed up at a barely visible rift in the sky. "The rest of the secret area is sealed in all directions, so that's the only place that you need to keep an eye on."

"Alright, in that case, I'll cultivate while keeping a lookout on the plaza over there," Weeping Soul replied.

All of a sudden, Han Li noticed a change in Weeping Soul's aura, and his expression changed slightly as he remarked, "It seems like your aura has become quite a bit more powerful as well."

"Indeed, Master. Ever since my awakening, I've felt a burst of law powers that's been constantly recovering and growing stronger within my body. At the same time, I've been feeling an insatiable hunger," Weeping Soul replied with a smile.

"What is this hunger that you speak of?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know how to describe it, it just always feels like my stomach is empty. I felt a little better after devouring all those ghostly creatures last time, so perhaps that's the key. I'll test out that theory the next time we encounter a powerful ghostly cultivator," Weeping Soul replied.

"Alright, I'll be leaving everything here to you then. I'm going to go into seclusion in that hall up ahead," Han Li said with a smile, and with that, the two of them parted ways, with Weeping Soul making her way onto the plaza, while Han Li entered the hall from before.

He sat down with his legs crossed onto the jade futon in the center, then flipped a hand over to produce that jade vial, tipping out a golden pill that he promptly devoured.

As soon as the pill entered his belly, a burst of formidable time law powers instantly spread through his dantian before flowing into the rest of his body.

Han Li hurriedly closed his eyes as he channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, guiding the burst of time law powers toward the designated acupoints in his body.

Moments later, his brows furrowed slightly as his eyes sprang open, and a hint of surprise had appeared on his face.

As it turned out, waves of rippling golden light had appeared over the jade cushion beneath him, immediately following which the same golden light emerged over the other two unoccupied cushions as well.

All of a sudden, it was as if a layer of golden liquid had been spilled over the entire interior of the hall.

Han Li could feel a burst of peculiar time law power fluctuations all around him, placing him in a profound and indescribable state.

An ecstatic look appeared on his face as he hurriedly began channeling the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra again.

As he did so, five balls of golden light appeared around him, revolving incessantly around his body, and they contained his five time-attribute law treasures.

Collectively, there were over one thousand six hundred Time Dao Runes on the five law treasures, and they were all glowing radiantly while giving off extremely formidable time law power fluctuations.

With the emergence of these time-attribute law treasures, all of the golden light within the entire hall began to unfurl like flower petals, forming a giant golden flower bud around Han Li.

Han Li was ecstatic to sense the time law powers surging into his body, and he knew that there had to be other secrets waiting to be discovered in this secret area, but at the moment, cultivation was his top priority, and everything would just have to wait until after he came out of seclusion.

......

Over two hundred years passed by in the blink of an eye.

On this day, Weeping Soul was seated beside the sundial on the white stone plaza, looking up at the spatial rift in the sky with a contemplative look in her eyes.

Seated with its legs crossed on her shoulder was a miniature silver figure that was close to five inches in height. The figure's entire body was enshrouded in silver flame, but there were seven vertical lines of fire of different colors above its head, making it appear as if it had a head of rainbow hair.

After completely refining the five beads of Rainbow Fire Pill Sand, the Essence Fire Raven's human form had become a lot taller than before, and it had also gained those extremely distinctive lines of rainbow fire above its head.

As opposed to Weeping Soul, the silver figure was looking at the golden hall while swinging its little legs back and forth with an unhappy look on its face.

"You're also hoping that Master will come out of seclusion soon, right?" Weeping Soul asked with a smile.

The silver figure nodded in response, and the lines of rainbow fire on its head suddenly pulsed a few times.

Weeping Soul knew that it was very keen for Han Li to see its newfound powers following its absorption of the beads of Rainbow Fire Pill Sand.

It had only come of seclusion not long ago, and as it did so, it was unable to suppress the rainbow flames that erupted out of its body, which would've easily incinerated the entire secret area had it been left unchecked.

Thankfully, Weeping Soul was able to intervene in a timely fashion and prevent the flames from reaching the golden hall that Han Li was in. However, the forest up ahead had already been burned to the ground, and half of the white stone plaza had also been charred black.

Right at this moment, the entire plaza suddenly shuddered violently, following which the entire secret area began to tremble.

Weeping Soul immediately flew up into the air upon seeing this, and the Essence Fire Raven was caught off guard by her sudden movement, almost falling off her shoulder in surprise.

After rising up into the sky, Weeping Soul looked down to discover that the gray mist around the secret area was churning violently while displaying signs of retreating, thereby causing the secret area to expand.

This has already been the third time this month...

This was not the first time that she had witnessed this phenomenon, but with each passing instance, the gray mist receded by a more significant degree, revealing larger and larger areas in the process.

Close to twenty seconds later, the tremors completely subsided, and the surrounding gray mist also gradually settled down.

Weeping Soul cast her gaze toward the golden hall with a concerned look in her eyes.

Han Li had already reached the late-High Zenith Stage eighty years ago, triggering a series of breathtaking phenomena in the secret area, but for some reason, he had chosen to remain in seclusion all the way up to this point.

......

That night.

There was a semi-transparent golden flower bud situated at the center of the golden hall.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed inside the flower bud, and his skin and flesh had become as translucent as jade, making his bones and meridians clearly visible.

At this moment, there were as many as 359 immortal acupoints glowing over his body, indicating that he had already reached the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage.

The rippling golden light glowing over the three jade cushions beneath had already become quite dim, clearly indicating that the time law powers within were close to running out.

Right at this moment, Han Li's eyes suddenly sprang open, and two beams of incredibly bright golden light erupted out of her pupils.

At the same time, he opened his mouth, and a wisp of white mist seeped out from within.

Moments later, the golden light and white mist slowly dissipated, and Han Li blinked a few times as he took a moment to compose himself.

At a glance, nothing seemed to have really changed about him, but upon closer inspection, one would discover that his body was shrouded in a layer of barely visible divine light, which was a sign of a High Zenith cultivator that had attained a flawless Jade Immortal Physique.

Looks like this is as far as I can go for now. As expected, jumping straight to the Great Encompassment Stage was an unrealistic goal...

In the span of less than three hundred years, he had progressed from the mid-High Zenith Stage to the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage, taking him to only a single step short of the Great Encompassment Stage.

While it was true that his cultivation had been enhanced by the special environment here, the seven time-attribute dao pills, and all of the profound acupoints that he had opened, this was still an astounding rate of progression that would have the jaws of the vast majority of cultivators dropping straight to the floor.

Hence, even though he had failed to reach the Great Encompassment Stage, he was still ecstatic nonetheless, and after sitting for a while longer, he rose to his feet before performing some stretches.

Right as he was about to make his way out of the hall, a faint crack suddenly rang out beside his ears.

Chapter 1033: Astonishing Phenomenon

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he turned to the source of the sound, only to discover that a crack had appeared on the white jade cushion that he had been sitting on, which then disintegrated right before his eyes.

The cushion had disintegrated into powder that spread through the entire hall, and at the same time, the golden hall began to tremble violently as a burst of peculiar energy fluctuations spread through the air.

A thought suddenly occurred to Han Li upon seeing this, and he immediately flew out of the hall before arriving on the plaza outside.

The tremors outside were even more violent than inside the hall, and Weeping Soul hurriedly approached him with the Essence Fire Raven as she asked, "What's happening, Master?"

"I'm not sure, but I seem to have triggered some type of mechanism in this secret area, which could lead to some unpredictable changes," Han Li replied.

"In that case, we should get out of here," Weeping Soul hurriedly said.

Han Li nodded in response as he heaved a forlorn sigh.

There were clearly still far more secrets to be discovered in this secret area, but there was no time to explore them.

With their minds made up, the two of them immediately turned to fly toward the spatial rift in the sky, only to discover that it had disappeared!

"Where did the spatial rift go? It was there just a moment ago!" Weeping Soul exclaimed.

The silver figure on her shoulder immediately stood up and nodded vigorously to back her up, causing the seven lines of rainbow fire on its head to bob up and down incessantly.

"I believe you. Something must've changed in this secret area," Han Li replied with a nod.

He had already noticed the changes that had taken place in the Essence Fire Raven, but this wasn't the time to be focusing on such matters.

"By the way, during your seclusion, there were some tremors that ran through the secret area on over ten separate occasions, the most intense of which came right after you reached the late-High Zenith Stage. This is already the fourth time that it's happened this month, and everytime it happens, the mist around the secret area will recede, revealing new areas," Weeping Soul said.

"Have you explored any of those new areas? Is there anything special about them?" Han Li asked.

"I only went exploring once nearby, and I didn't discover anything abnormal. Over time, the tremors became more and more frequent, and I didn't dare to stray, so I've been staying here the entire time," Weeping Soul replied with a shake of her head.

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly upon hearing this, and right as he was contemplating what he had just been told, a pillar of golden light that was over a thousand feet thick suddenly erupted out of the golden hall and into the heavens, immediately following which the tremors around the hall suddenly subsided.

Han Li was rather perplexed to see this, and he attempted to approach the hall for a closer examination, only to be kept out by a burst of invisible force.

"Master, are you getting the feeling that the ground is slowly elevating?" Weeping Soul suddenly asked.

Han Li's attention had been focused on the golden light this entire him, and after hearing this question form Weeping Soul, he immediately sprang up into the air before scouring his surroundings, upon which he discovered that the gray mist around the secret area was churning violently, while new land was beginning to appear bit by bit.

......

Inside the Azure Silk Col outside the secret area, the ground was trembling violently, as if an earthquake were taking place.

"The earth dragon is rolling over!"

All of the villagers of the Spare Food Village hurriedly rushed out of their homes before arriving on a spacious plot of vacant land outside.

Right at this moment, a burst of thunderous rumbling rang out from underground, and a massive pillar of golden light erupted out of the White Head Valley. The pillar of golden light rose all the way up into the heavens, turning all of the clouds within a radius of several hundred kilometers a bright golden color.

The pillar of light was incredibly thick, dwarfing even the nearby mountains, and the world's origin qi around it trembled violently as the golden clouds in the sky churned and rumbled incessantly.

All of the villagers were looking on with flabbergasted expressions.

All of a sudden, someone yelled, "This is a divine miracle from the gods!"

All of the villagers hurriedly fell to their knees and began worshiping the pillar of golden light upon hearing this.

Meanwhile, seven or eight streaks of light were approaching the Azure Silk Col from the southeast, and they drew to a halt close to ten kilometers away from the col to reveal a group of cultivators.

They were led by a Golden Immortal Stage elderly woman holding a yellow serpent staff, while the rest of the group was comprised of young men and women who were all at the True Immortal Stage.

They were all dressed in uniform yellow robes, indicating that they were members of the same sect, and all of the True Immortals in the group were very excited at the sight of the phenomenon taking place before them.

"It looks like some type of treasure or secret area must've emerged here, Martial Aunt Lin. Let's go down and take a look. Otherwise, once other people arrive, we could be faced with a lot of competition," a male disciple said in an excited manner, and all of the other disciples nodded eagerly in agreement.

The elderly woman was looking quite excited, but she remained calm as she said, "Don't make any rash moves. This phenomenon is indeed a precursor for the emergence of a treasure, but it still hasn't completely revealed itself yet, so even if we go down there now, it won't amount to anything.

“On top of that, judging from the scale of this phenomenon, whatever's going to appear here isn't something that we can handle. Send a message back to the sect to inform everyone of what's happening here."

The young disciples behind her immediately sprang into action upon hearing this, pulling out their communication array plates to contact their sect.

Right at this moment, two more streaks of light shot forth from afar, then drew to a halt near the col to reveal a pair of black-robed Golden Immortals.

"They're from the Dark Scorn Sect," a young man informed.

"Ignore them. Come over here with me," the elderly woman said as she descended onto a nearby mountain summit.

The two black-robed cultivators took a glance at their group, then also descended onto a nearby mountain before pulling out communication treasures to contact others.

Word of the phenomenon taking place in the central region of the Golden Origin Mountain Range spread like wildfire, and more and more powers within the mountain range were sending people to the scene.

Close to a month flew by in the blink of an eye, and not only had the pillar of golden light not faded in the slightest, it was only growing more and more massive.

Inside the secret area, Han Li was watching intently as the surrounding gray mist rapidly faded.

At this point, the space within the secret area had already expanded to around twice its normal size, gradually revealing its true appearance.

Two enormous golden mountains were revealed on either side of the dense forest, standing like a pair of unfathomably tall city walls to form an enormous canyon that the forest was nestled into.

The majority of the two mountains were concealed above the gray mist, making it impossible to see them in their full glory.

What was most intriguing of all was that a series of gray chains that were as thick as water vats were hanging down from the gray mist, trailing all the way down to the foot of the two mountains.

The chains were flashing with arcs of gray lightning, presenting a rather fearsome sight to behold.

Han Li descended to the foot of one of the mountains, and after a brief hesitation, he reached out to touch one of the gray chains, upon which an arc of gray lightning instantly sprang forth to strike him.

Han Li gave a muffled groan as he took a step back, and his hand had been charred black by the lightning strike.

As he channeled his immortal spiritual power, the coloration of his hand quickly returned to normal, but he was still stunned by how formidable this gray lightning was.

Furthermore, that was only a single arc of lightning. If he were to be struck by more of these arcs of lightning at once, then that could spell some trouble.

Han Li withdrew his gaze from the mountain summit, then peered deep into the canyon formed by the two mountains. The gray mist there was constantly receding, revealing a path that led deeper into the secret area.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li decided to fly in that direction.

......

At the same time, tens of thousands of figures had already gathered around the Azure Silk Col.

They were from a wide array of different sects and powers, each of which had established their own temporary territories, and there were also some itinerant cultivators among them who required no territories other than some ground to stand on.

The areas nearest to the pillar of light had been claimed by seven or eight sects, while the mountain previously occupied by the elderly woman and the golden-robed disciples had since been taken, forcing them further to the back.

They had been joined by three more people, consisting of a yellow-skinned middle-aged man, a seductive young woman, and an elderly man with a head of white hair.

These three were all Golden Immortals, and in particular, the yellow-faced man was already at the late-Golden Immortal Stage, seemingly the leader of the group.

"The Spirit Heaven Sect, the Worry Not Pavilion, Blazing Light City, the Ink Fragrance Pavilion, the Azure Lock Valley, the Rising Moon Pavilion, and the White Cloud Mountain Cottage have all sent people here. Those scoundrels from the Rising Moon Pavilion have taken our territory!" the elderly woman said in a resentful voice.

"There's nothing we can do. Those sects all have High Zenith cultivators among their ranks, so there's no way that our tiny Yellow Wind Sect can compete with them," the yellow-faced man sighed.

"According to our observations, the phenomenon taking place here seems to be a precursor for the emergence of a secret area or immortal manor. When it comes to exploring these areas, luck is sometimes more important than power," a middle-aged woman said.

Everyone knew that she was grasping at straws a little, but they still nodded in agreement to make themselves feel a little better.

"How strange... I would've expected to see cultivators of the Immortal Palace here, but there doesn't appear to be any present," the white-haired elderly man said.

Chapter 1034: Mass Gathering

"You must've not heard about what happened to the Golden Origin Immortal Palace because you've just come out of seclusion, Brother Lian Shi. Someone stormed into the Golden Origin Immortal Palace on their own over a century ago, slaying Palace Master Dongfang Bai, the Five Heavenly Yin Disciples, and many other powerful Immortal Palace cultivators in the process.

“For some reason, the Heavenly Court hasn't sent anyone to take the reins from the deceased Dongfang Bai, so the Immortal Palace is far less powerful than before, and I'm assuming they're not going to be sending anyone," the elderly woman said.

"That's incredible! I heard that Dongfang Bai was at the pinnacle of the High Zenith Palace and possessed powers not inferior to those of a Great Encompassment cultivator! Who could've possibly killed him? Was it someone from the Reincarnation Palace?" the elderly man exclaimed.

"Apparently, it was a man on the Immortal Slaying List by the name of Han Li, and it's unclear whether he's a member of the Reincarnation Palace. In any case, the Heavenly Court is currently offering an enormous reward for his head. However, there's been no news of him since the Immortal Palace incident, and no one knows if he's still in the Golden Origin Immortal Region," the elderly woman said.

The white-haired elderly man nodded in response with a contemplative look in his eyes.

All the while, a man and a woman had been standing near the group of Yellow Wind Sect cultivators.

Both of them were dressed in black robes, and the woman was quite beautiful and youthful in appearance, while the man was rather thin and had a slightly pale complexion.

After hearing the conversation between the Yellow Wind Sect cultivators, the two of them exchanged a peculiar glance with each other, and a faint smile appeared on the woman's face as she mused to herself in a barely voice, "You certainly are always full of surprises, Brother Han."

"Are you thinking about going to find him? Don't forget about our mission," the black-robed young man asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"Rest assured, I know what our top priority is at the moment," the young woman replied.

Right at this moment, several streaks of blue light shot forth from afar, giving off immense water-attribute spiritual qi.

The streaks of blue light then faded to reveal four blue-robed cultivators that descended out of the sky.

All four of them were giving off extremely formidable High Zenith Stage auras, and the people ahead of them hurriedly parted to make way.

"Those are cultivators from the Heavenly Water Sect!" the yellow-faced man from the Yellow Wind Sect exclaimed, and everyone else in the nearby area was also displaying a similar reaction.

The four Heavenly Water Sect cultivators paid no heed to the people around them as they quickly arrived near the pillar of golden light.

Two of the four figures were leading from the forefront, and one of them was a young woman who appeared to be in her early-twenties. She was extremely beautiful, but there was a cold demeanor about her that made her feel very unapproachable.

She was accompanied by a middle-aged man with a pair of long and thin eyes and a hooked nose, giving him a rather sinister appearance.

The two people behind them consisted of an exceptionally tall and imposing man with a pair of bushy eyebrows and a refined and elegant young man holding a folding fan.

Even the sects that occupied the areas nearest to the pillar of golden light hurriedly scrambled to make way for the Heavenly Water Sect cultivators.

A square-faced man from the Spirit Heaven Sect approached the Heavenly Water Sect cultivators with a smile as he greeted, "It's been a long time since we last met, Celestial Maiden Su Anqian, Fellow Daoist Jin Liu. I see that the two of you have also been drawn to the phenomenon here."

"Are we not welcome here? Is this the territory of your Spirit Heaven Sect?" Jin Liu asked in a cold voice.

"Of course you're welcome here. It's just that the Heavenly Water Sect is quite far away from here, and both of you are very important figures in the sect, so I wasn't expecting the two of you to make the trip. Could it be that you know what's about to appear here?" the square-faced man asked, and his questions instantly drew the attention of all of the cultivators from the nearby sects.

Jin Liu's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of this widespread scrutiny, while Su Anqian replied, "The two of us just so happened to be doing something else nearby, and we decided to come and take a look after hearing about the phenomenon here, so we don't know anything about this place. Now that I think about it, the Azure Lock Valley is very close to this place, so surely they have some leads."

A handsome azure-robed man emerged from the Azure Lock Valley cultivators, and he hurriedly explained, "Our Azure Lock Valley is indeed very close to this place, but this is a very barren area that we've never paid much heed to. Having said that, I've sent some people to do some investigating, and I've been informed that this place is called the Azure Silk Col.

“Inside the col is a place called the White Head Valley, which apparently contains a spring that can restore the youth of those who bathe in it. However, the spring is currently encompassed within the pillar of light, making it impossible to verify these claims."

"A spring that can restore one's youth? How fascinating. Perhaps it has something to do with the laws of time? Maybe the water in the spring is the legendary water of time?" Su Anqian speculated.

"How could something as precious as the water of time appear in such a secluded place? Mortals are very foolish creatures, so perhaps the spring doesn't even have anything to do with this pillar of light," Jin Liu scoffed.

Su Anqian took a glance at him, but didn't say anything.

Right at this moment, a booming voice suddenly rang out, reverberating loudly within the col.

"Well, well, well, it appears I'm late to the party."

Everyone immediately looked up upon hearing this, including Jin Liu and Su Anqian, who were looking into the sky with intense animosity in their eyes.

A streak of golden light appeared on the distant horizon, and it expanded rapidly, transforming into a radiant golden sun that forced everyone in the col to avert their eyes.

"What a grand entrance, Lei Yuce," Jin Liu sneered as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of rippling blue light that quickly spread through the air.

Much of the blinding golden light was absorbed by the blue light, and the rest of the golden light faded to reveal a pair of figures, one of whom praised, "I can see that you've made some impressive strides in your Divine Vast Sea Arts, Fellow Daoist Jin."

The man who had spoken appeared to be in his thirties, and he had a very muscular build that was quite apparent even through his loose-fitting golden robe.

He was accompanied by a handsome young man who possessed a tranquil and seemingly completely harmless aura.

The leaders of many of the nearby cultivating powers immediately gathered to greet the two men, displaying even more respect than they had toward the four Heavenly Water Sect cultivators.

"Rest assured, everyone, our Almighty Sword Sect has no intention of claiming this place solely for ourselves," the handsome young man assured. "We'll leave it down to luck to see what rewards we can reap from this secret area."

Everyone else was very relieved to hear this, and they all offered up words of gratitude and praise.

The Heavenly Water Sect cultivators were far from happy to see the two men, but they didn't say anything.

Lei Yuce paid no heed to everyone else as he cast a longing gaze toward Su Anqian and said, "Long time no see, Celestial Maiden Sun. You were cultivating your Zenith Yin Ice Soul Arts in seclusion some years ago, and I visited you on several occasions during that time, but was refused an audience. I certainly wasn't expecting to run into you here today. Looks like you've broken through your late-High Zenith Stage bottleneck, I'm truly happy for you."

Su Anqian harrumphed coldly as she looked away in a disdainful manner.

Lei Yuce wasn't bothered at all as he stared at Su Anqian in an entranced fashion, and everyone else seemed to have already grown accustomed to this.

It was common knowledge on the Golden Origin Continent that Lei Yuce of the Almighty Sword Sect had been pursuing Su Anqian of the Heavenly Water Sect for hundreds of thousands of years.

"What is this Almighty Sword Sect?" the black-robed young woman standing near the Yellow Wind Sect cultivators asked through voice transmission.

"The Almighty Sword Sect is the number one sect in the Golden Origin Immortal Region, and it's at least on par with the Golden Origin Immortal Palace. Lei Yuce is a mid-High Zenith cultivator and the deputy sect master, while the young man with him is Elder Wen Zhong of the Almighty Sword Sect, a very powerful cultivator in his own right.

“Those two are going to be formidable foes of ours, along with Su Anqian and Jin Liu of the Heavenly Water Sect. Did you read the information given to us prior to coming here? I'm beginning to wonder if our higher-ups made the right decision in sending you here," the black-robed young man replied with tightly furrowed brows.

The young woman wasn't bothered by her companion's remarks, and she gestured into the distance as she replied, "Formidable foes? You're taking them far too seriously. Those people are our main competition."

The black-robed young man cast his gaze in that direction to find two streaks of blue light approaching from the distance.

The two streaks of light weren't particularly bright, and they didn't really stand out among all of the other streaks of light currently flashing through the col.

The two streaks of light quickly arrived in the col before fading to reveal a square-faced male cultivator with a pair of bushy eyebrows and a round-faced woman with a very petite mouth, both of whom were very unremarkable in appearance.

"Who're those two?" the black-robed young man asked.

The young woman flipped a hand over to produce an egg-sized white jewel, within which was a flashing ring of spiritual light.

Two figures appeared within the ring of spiritual light, but they were different from the two that had just arrived in the col.

The man looked to be in his thirties with a rather scholarly appearance, while the woman appeared to be only seventeen to eighteen years of age, and she had a pair of exuberant and adorable eyes that were constantly darting around in an energetic fashion.

"Those are the Lan Siblings from the Vast Golden Immortal Palace, Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yna! What are they doing here? Could it be that we've already been exposed?" the black-robed young man exclaimed.

Chapter 1035: Tai Sui Immortal Manor

"I don't know. On the surface, the Lan siblings are under the control of the Vast Golden Immortal Palace, but in reality, they take orders from the Nine Origins Temple, so it's definitely not good news that they're here," the young woman said in a grim voice as she stowed her white jewel away.

"I've also heard that they specialize in carrying out secret missions for the Nine Origins Temple. What do we do then?" the black-robed young man asked.

"The situation is still unclear at the moment, so let's just wait and see for now," the young woman replied.

The two of them discussed their options for a while longer before fading into the crowd behind them.

"I didn't think that there would be so many people gathered here. It looks like we're going to be able to have some fun!" Lan Yan remarked as she examined the crowds around them.

"Of course these people would all swarm to a new secret area like flies to a piece of rotten meat," Lan Yuanzi scoffed disdainfully.

"But Brother, even though our objectives are different from these people, we also came here for the new secret area, so aren't you denouncing us as flies as well?" Lan Yan grumbled in a displeased manner.

Lan Yuanzi was momentarily rendered speechless upon hearing this, following which he snapped in a frustrated manner, "I'm not taking you on the next mission if you don't learn to keep your mouth shut!"

"Don't blame me when you're the one who misspoke!" Lan Yan countered in a completely unfazed manner.

"Alright, quit fooling around, we need to get down to business," Lan Yuanzi said with a serious expression.

"Do you think Han Li is going to be here, Brother? If I were him, I would go into hiding in a completely uninhabited place and never come out for the rest of my life," Lan Yan said.

"That would definitely be the strategy adopted by the average person, but it seems like this Han Li is someone who doesn't play by the rules, so there's a chance that he could be here. On top of that, according to the information we've received from the Immortal Palace, he really was traveling in this direction before suddenly disappearing, so this is definitely a place that's worth exploring," Lan Yuanzi replied.

"How boring. You're always so calculated in everything that you do," Lan Yan sighed in a displeased manner.

Lan Yuanzi paid no heed to her as he flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized blue mirror, then chanted an incantation before pointing a finger at it.

Rays of illusory instantly appeared over the surface of the mirror before spreading outward, only to ultimately fade into the surrounding space.

Immediately thereafter, he stowed the mirror away before rushing forward.

"Hey, where are you going all of a sudden? Wait for me!" Lan Yan hurriedly called out, and the two of them quickly vanished into the crowd.

Not long after they left, a hideous, yellow-robed woman appeared amid a flash of yellow light elsewhere in the col.

"What a useless idiot that Lan Yuanzi is! Even with the Heavenly Detection Mirror at his disposal, he still hasn't been able to track down Han Li even after all these years. What a pain it is to have to follow him on this wild goose chase!" the woman grumbled to herself.

"Having said that, judging from the scale of this phenomenon, it appears that a very remarkable secret area is about to appear here. At the very least, its former owner should've been a Great Encompassment cultivator. It doesn't look like Lan Yuanzi will be tracking down Han Li anytime soon, so I may as well stay here to check out the secret area," the woman murmured to herself, then abruptly vanished from the spot.

Somewhere in the crowd, a golden-robed man was observing the yellow-robed woman, and it was none other than Qi Mozi, with Xiong Shan still by his side.

"Things are certainly getting interesting," Qi Mozi remarked with a faint smile.

By following Qi Mozi's gaze, Xiong Shan had also spotted the yellow-robed woman, but he had no idea who it was, so he asked in a curious manner, "Who was that just now?"

"Her name is She Chan. She's an old toad from the Nine Origins Temple who only knows how to lurk in the shadows and sneak attack people like a coward," Qi Mozi harrumphed in a disdainful manner.

Xiong Shan drew a sharp breath upon hearing this, clearly having heard of this name before.

Even though Qi Mozi was very disdainful of She Chan, she was still a revered Great Encompassment cultivator in Xiong Shan's eyes.

"I heard that She Chan is always cultivating in seclusion in the Nine Origins Temple, so why is she suddenly here? Could she be here for the secret area that's about to emerge?" Xiong Shan speculated, and Qi Mozi's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

According to the intelligence that he had gathered, She Chan and the Lan siblings had arrived in the Golden Origin Immortal Region with the objective of capturing Han Li. The Golden Origin Immortal Palace and the Nine Origins Temple shared very close ties, and Dongfang Bai belonged to the Nine Origins Temple, so it only made sense that they would send people after Han Li following Dongfang Bai's demise.

However, a question had sprung into Qi Mozi's mind after hearing what Xiong Shan had to say. It was very normal for the Nine Origins Temple to be hunting Han Li, but surely there was no need to send the likes of She Chan after him unless they were hunting him for some other reason.

"Is Han Li really in this secret area?" Xiong Shan asked in a hesitant manner.

"It's all but confirmed. Over two hundred years ago, a man with the Han surname stayed briefly in the village down below. I've searched the souls of all those who've seen him, and even though he changed his appearance, I'm certain that man was none other than Han Li.

“Ever since he was last sighted in this village, it's as if he had disappeared off the face of the earth, so there's a very good chance that he's still here and somehow snuck into the secret area. In fact, I'd say there's a good chance that the emergence of this secret area has a lot to do with him," Qi Mozi replied in a confident manner.

"That does sound like a strong possibility," Xiong Shan agreed.

Right at this moment, a burst of rumbling suddenly rang out from within the col, and the ground encompassed within the pillar of golden light suddenly began to bulge, as if there were something rising up from down below.

Everyone's attention was instantly drawn to the ground there, and the earth bulged further and further before finally splitting apart amid a dull thump, revealing a giant opening, at the bottom of which was a stone gate that was around seventy to eighty feet tall.

It was clear from a glance that the stone gate had already been standing for countless years, and the words "Tai Sui Immortal Manor" were engraved above the gate in ancient text.

......

Inside the canyon within the secret area.

The gray mist up ahead was churning incessantly while rapidly receding, and there was an ecstatic look on Han Li's face as he flew through the air, closely following the receding mist.

The gray mist had shown bouts of recession in the past, but at a rather slow rate, and this was the fastest that the mist had ever receded.

After flying for a while longer, he finally reached the end of the canyon, where he drew to a halt.

The gray mist up ahead continued to rapidly recede, displaying a large area.

The sky was blue, and there were some white clouds drifting along. The ground below was a lush, boundless plain, and a gentle breeze was blowing from afar, while a refreshing and relaxing fragrance was wafting through the air.

Dotted along the horizon up ahead were some mountains, and the scene was as beautiful as a piece of scenic artwork.

Han Li took a deep breath, feeling a little more relaxed, but then immediately focused on the situation at hand again.

This was not the time to be appreciating scenery. He could sense that the entrance of this space deep within the canyon was in a very unstable state, seemingly displaying signs of reopening.

Even though Han Li didn't know that there were already tens of thousands of people gathered outside, he could guess that the reopening of the spatial entrance would be sure to attract a great deal of attention.

With that in mind, he released his spiritual sense as far and wide as it would go, and in the next instant, his eyes lit up slightly as a burst of golden lightning appeared over his body.

A resounding thunderclap rang out as he vanished from the spot, only to reappear in the sky above a mountain.

There was a cluster of white pavilions on the mountain, looking as if they had been constructed from some type of jade material, and they were giving off a faint, white glow.

Furthermore, all of the pavilions were enshrouded within a white light barrier.

Han Li raised an arm before sweeping a finger through the air, and a streak of golden swordlight that was around a thousand feet in length shot out of his sleeve before slicing down upon the white light barrier.

The nearby space trembled and buzzed incessantly, as if it were about to be split apart.

Having reached the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage, his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had become even more formidable.

However, the white light barrier was able to withstand the streak of golden swordlight, albeit with some difficulty.

A surprised look appeared on Han Li's face, and he flew over to the light barrier before throwing a punch into it.

The white light barrier was instantly torn apart upon contact with Han Li's fist, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he descended into the cluster of pavilions down below.

Shortly thereafter, he flew back up into the air with an excited look on his face, then vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden lightning.

......

Meanwhile, outside the secret area.

Most of the people gathered were looking at the stone gate that had risen up from the ground with puzzled expressions, having never heard of this Tai Sui Immortal Manor before.

However, excited looks had appeared on the faces of the likes of Su Anqian, Jin Liu, and Lei Yuce, and a stunned look had appeared on Qi Mozi's face as well.

Xiong Shan was rather intrigued by Qi Mozi's expression, but ultimately chose not to ask any questions.

So this is where your cave abode is, Tai Sui! Looks like I was right to have come on this trip to the Golden Origin Immortal Region! Qi Mozi thought to himself with an excited expression.

Chapter 1036: Unsealed

Shortly thereafter, the enormous pillar of golden light suddenly began to flash erratically, giving the antiquated stone gate beneath it a rather indistinct appearance.

Everyone immediately fell silent upon seeing this, waiting with bated breath for what was about to unfold next.

After flickering for some time, the pillar of golden light suddenly became brighter than ever, only to then immediately shrink down rapidly. Within the span of just a few seconds, the pillar of golden light had vanished entirely, fully revealing the stone gate below.

In the same instant, Su Anqian, Lei Yuce, and the others immediately pounced on the stone gate.

A dull thump rang out as a series of transparent ripples appeared over the stone gate, sending all of them flying back.

Jin Liu was the one that was flying at the stone gate with the most urgency, and the skin on his forehead was split open by the sudden impact, causing him to curse loudly.

Everyone else immediately stopped in their tracks upon seeing this, and only then did they notice that there was a barely visible transparent light barrier over the stone gate.

Lei Yuce's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he swept his left hand through the air in the direction of the stone gate, unleashing five streaks of golden swordlight that were each around a hundred feet in length.

Each streak of golden swordlight was as radiant as the sun, and they struck the stone gate like lightning, but the transparent light barrier was able to withstand them with ease.

"This light barrier may be resilient, but it's not indestructible. There are so many of us here, I'm sure we'll be able to break through it if we all work together," Lei Yuce declared.

"Then what are we waiting for? I've heard that the Azure Lock Valley has an azure lock array that's quite powerful, so hurry up and bring it out. The Spirit Heaven Sect also has a Spirit Heaven Blazing Sun Technique that's quite powerful, and the Rising Moon Pavilion..."

Jin Liu began barking instructions at the people of the nearby sects as if he were ordering around his personal servants, and the cultivators of those sects were naturally not very pleased, but they still obliged.

After all, the top priority was to break open this light barrier so that they could access the secret area.

Su Anqian, Lei Yuce, and the others also sprang into action, and a formidable barrage of attacks and immortal treasures were sent raining down upon the transparent light barrier.

The light barrier appeared quite thin, but it was incredibly resilient, holding itself together with ease in the face of the ferocious barrage, much to everyone's astonishment.

"Don't stop! Keep going!" Lei Yuce yelled.

Qi Mozi was standing further back in the crowd, choosing not to participate in the collective effort.

At the moment, he was only displaying a Golden Immortal Stage aura, so he didn't stand out in the crowd, and the only people attacking the light barrier were the cultivators from a handful of the most powerful sects present.

After all, there was only so much space in front of the stone gate, so only a certain number of people could be accommodated.

"Do you think they'll be able to break the restriction like this? Should we lend them our assistance?" Xiong Shan asked.

"The method that they're employing is a bit barbaric, but it should work. At this rate, it's only a matter of time, so let's not expose ourselves for now," Qi Mozi replied, and Xiong Shan nodded in response.

A day and a night flew by in a flash.

The stone gate had been withstanding relentlessly waves of attacks this entire time, and it was finally beginning to thin out.

"Keep it up, everyone!" Lei Yuce encouraged, and everyone immediately redoubled their efforts.

Close to another day passed by in the blink of an eye, and the light barrier was finally shattered with a dull thump.

A vast expanse of golden light surged out of the stone gate, forming a golden vortex with countless specks of golden light flashing within it.

......

Deep within the secret area, Han Li was in the process of unraveling a restriction outside a palace when his expression suddenly changed slightly, and he cast his gaze toward the entrance of the secret area, where he could detect a burst of powerful spatial fluctuations.

Looks like the entrance of this place has been discovered. I wonder how many people are going to come in.

With that in mind, a decisive look appeared on Han Li's face, and he adopted his Giant Mountain Ape form before throwing an almighty punch into the restrictions around the palace.

The restriction rippled violently before falling apart, but at the same time, the residual force of Han Li's punch caused some damage to the palace inside.

Han Li paid no heed to this as he flew in without any hesitation.

Time was of the essence, and he couldn't afford to waste any of it.

......

Inside the Azure Silk Col.

"Go!" Lei Yuce yelled in an ecstatic manner as he rushed into the golden vortex, instantly vanishing out of sight.

There were around twenty High Zenith cultivators present, and Lei Yuce was undoubtedly the leading figure among them both in terms of power and reputation, so no one saw it as unfit that he had flown into the golden vortex first.

The cultivators of the other major sects present quickly followed along, and everyone else came after them.

The Lan siblings, She Chan, and Qi Mozi were all concealed within the crowd as they entered the golden vortex to arrive inside the secret area, specifically the same canyon that Han Li had been situated in earlier.

There was a slowly revolving golden vortex behind everyone, and Qi Mozi examined his surroundings briefly before declaring, "Xiong Shan, I'm going on ahead, you can go search for opportunities on your own."

Before Xiong Shan had a chance to reply, Qi Mozi vanished from the spot, and Xiong Shan didn't display any reaction, but internally, he was quite pleased.

After all, he would no longer have to take orders from Qi Mozi, but at the same time, he was feeling a little uneasy as without Qi Mozi by his side, he was nothing more than a Golden Immortal on his own.

While the situation was still quite chaotic, She Chan and the Lan siblings snuck away deeper into the canyon, unleashing some self-concealment techniques as they did so.

Elsewhere in the crowd were the black-robed man and woman, and the latter said, "Lan Yuanzi and the others are traveling deeper into the secret area. Let's go as well, we can't let them get too far ahead of us."

The black-robed young man nodded in response, and the two of them vanished from the spot.

Meanwhile, everyone else was marveling at the environment within the secret area.

Right at this moment, the sky above suddenly began to tremble violently, and bolts of lightning-like white light appeared up above, giving off bursts of dull yet deafening rumbling, as if there were several bursts of almighty force crashing against each other.

Everyone looked up with alarmed expressions as a series of enormous black rifts appeared in the sky above, and the ground beneath their feet also shuddered violently.

Immediately thereafter, the golden vortex up above abruptly disintegrated with a dull thump, following which the tremors in the sky and the earth gradually subsided.

Deep within the secret area, Han Li flew out of the palace, and a puzzled look appeared on his face at the sight of what had just taken place.

What just happened?

The palace behind him had been completely torn apart, and even the ceiling had been entirely demolished.

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly as he withdrew his gaze before flying deeper into the secret area.

Meanwhile, everyone was still astonished by the abrupt disappearance of the spatial passageway that led to the outside world.

"Fellow Daoist Lei, Fellow Daoist Su, do either of you know what this place is?" the square-faced man from the Spirit Heaven Sect asked, and everyone else immediately turned to Lei Yuce and Su Anqian to await their response.

Lei Yuce exchanged a glance with Su Anqian, then said, "I've heard some things about the Tai Sui Immortal Manor. There was once a Great Encompassment cultivator by the name of Immortal Lord Tai Sui tens of millions of years ago, and he was a cultivator of the laws of time, so I'm sure all of you can imagine how powerful he was.

“However, he was a very reclusive person who kept a low profile, so he wasn't particularly renowned. At some point, he disappeared without a trace, and I wouldn't have heard of him had I not just so happened to have seen some scriptures describing his feats in our Almighty Sword Sect. My guess is that he was the one who left behind this Tai Sui Immortal Manor."

Looks of elation appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this, washing away much of the unease that they felt from the disappearance of the spatial entrance.

If this really was a cave abode left behind by a Great Encompassment Stage immortal lord who had cultivated the laws of time, then it had to be filled with countless precious treasures. Furthermore, if it really had already been lost for tens of millions of years, then any precious spirit plants in this place had to have been ridiculously advanced in age.

Lei Yuce turned to Su Anqian, then communicated something to her through voice transmission, in response to which she gave a barely noticeable nod.

"In that case, do either of you have any idea of what just happened?" the square-faced man asked.

"That's the extent of my knowledge on this place. My assumption is that this place has been sealed for too long, and we just forcibly destroyed the restriction at the entrance, so this space is already beginning to collapse and won't be around for much longer," Lei Yuce speculated, much to everyone's concern.

Chapter 1037: Mounting Tensions

There was no lack of individuals with vast wealths of knowledge and experience present, and many of them had already guessed this to be the case, but they were still rather dismayed to have received confirmation from Lei Yuce.

Now that the spatial entrance was gone, and the entire secret area was displaying signs of collapsing, didn't that mean that they were all going to die in here?

"Rest assured, everyone. This place is a former cave abode of a Great Encompassment cultivator, so there must be other ways out. The space here is rather frail, but it should last at least a month, which will be enough time for us to find an exit," Lei Yuce said, and everyone was slightly reassured to hear this, but it was clear that many people were still feeling very uneasy.

Right at this moment, Wen Zhong took a step forward beside Lei Yuce as he declared, "Please listen to me, everyone."

His voice wasn't very loud, but it rang out very clearly within everyone's ears, and everyone immediately turned to him for guidance.

"Time is of the essence right now, and we don't know what dangers could be present in this secret area. If all of us were to split up and explore this place on our own, then there's a very good chance that widespread casualties could be suffered. Hence, I propose that we all form an alliance to travel together. Even if we encounter any dangers ahead, I'm sure we'll be able to overcome them with our collective powers. What do you all say?" Wen Zhong proposed with a smile.

"I think that's a good idea. There's no need for us to throw our lives away for potential rewards that may not even exist," Jin Liu chimed in, but no one else said anything, and everyone was looking rather hesitant.

For most of the people present, their initial reaction was to turn down this proposal. After all, everyone had come to this secret area in search of opportunities, and traveling as part of a massive alliance would undoubtedly be cumbersome and counterproductive to that goal.

However, it was also true that this was a completely unknown place to everyone, so there were benefits to joining forces as well.

On top of that, the alliance had been proposed by the Almighty Sword Sect, and it had been agreed upon by the Heavenly Water Sect.

The Almighty Sword Sect, the Heavenly Water Sect, and the Golden Origin Immortal Palace were the three leading powers of the Golden Origin Immortal Region. Now that the Golden Origin Immortal Palace had faded into obscurity, the statuses of the Almighty Sword Sect and the Heavenly Water Sect had been even further elevated, and no one dared to directly oppose them.

"Rest assured, everyone, this is only going to be a temporary alliance, and there aren't going to be many rules. All of the treasures that you obtain will go to you, but while you're a part of this alliance, you must travel with everyone, and you're forbidden from wandering off on your own," Wen Zhong added, and everyone instantly became much more receptive to the idea.

Hence, all of the other cultivators present began to express their approval of the proposal one after another.

"In that case, the alliance is hereby officially formed," Lei Yuce declared.

"An alliance cannot be without a leader, so let's make a decision on that as well. Fellow Daoist Lei is the most powerful cultivator out of all of us, so I think he should serve as the alliance leader. Celestial Maiden Su's powers are second only to his, so I propose that she serves as the deputy alliance leader. What do we all think?" Wen Zhong proposed.

The Heavenly Water Sect cultivators raised no objections to this proposal.

The formation of the alliance had been proposed by the Almighty Sword Sect, and it had received support from the Heavenly Water Sect, so everyone had already guessed that this would be the proposed arrangement.

"In that case, I am honored to accept the role of alliance leader. As the alliance leader, the first rule that I'm going to establish is that everyone is forbidden from attacking fellow alliance members. Can you all do that?" Lei Yuce asked.

This rule was basically already a given, so no one raised any objections to it.

"Alright, let's set off then," Lei Yuce declared as he led the way forward, and everyone immediately followed along.

Before long, they arrived at the palace where Han Li had been cultivating in seclusion earlier.

At this point, the pillar of golden light rising up from the palace had already vanished.

Elated looks appeared on everyone's faces at the sight of the palace, and some of them immediately swooped down to search the palace, only for Wen Zhong to step forward as he declared in an authoritative voice, "Stay back! Follow the alliance leader's instructions!"

Only then did those people recall that they had to follow the orders of the alliance, and they sheepishly stopped in their tracks.

"Wen Zhong, Jin Liu, Azure Lock Valley Master, Ink Fragrance Pavilion Master, each of you take some people with you to explore the palace," Lei Yuce instructed, and the four people that were named immediately gave affirmative responses before doing as instructed, while everyone else could only look on with forlorn expressions.

A short while later, the four of them returned with glum looks on their faces.

"Alliance Leader, everything in the palace below has already been taken, and there are also some very recent signs of battle, so someone must've come here before us," Wen Zhong reported with a dark expression.

"Are you sure?" Lei Yuce asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I'm certain," Wen Zhong confirmed.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Lei Yuce declared, "In that case, let's continue onward for now."

The alliance advanced onward at his behest, and they quickly emerged from the canyon, arriving in a much more open area that instilled renewed hope within them.

Lei Yuce was also feeling slightly more reassured upon seeing this. Given how vast this area was, even if someone had arrived here before them, there was no way that they would be able to explore the entire place in a short time.

Furthermore, it was clear that they hadn't left yet, so if he could catch the culprits, then he certainly wouldn't mind making them hand over what they had found by force.

"Wen Zhong, Fellow Daosit Jin Liu, split everyone here up into twenty groups so that we can all cover more ground and explore more places at once. Don't go too far, gather back here in half a day," Lei Yuce instructed.

Wen Zhong did as he was told, and everyone quickly split up to explore different parts of the secret area.

The cultivators of the Azure Lock Valley, the Ink Fragrance Sect, and other powers were all assigned to more secluded areas, while the cultivators of the Almighty Sword Sect and the Heavenly Water Sect were sent deeper into the secret area.

The cultivators of the other sects were naturally not happy with this arrangement, but they didn't dare to raise any objections.

Deep inside the secret area was a hill that was enshrouded under a thin layer of mist, and there was a faint medicinal aroma in the air.

The hill was split up into three tiers, each of which was several thousand feet in size. Together, the three tiers formed a diverse spirit medicine garden, and every single spirit medicine planted in the garden was at least tens of thousands of years old.

At this moment, there were over a hundred giant ape puppets were busy at work, harvesting all types of spirit medicines before rushing out of the garden.

There was a giant door of silver light outside the spirit medicine garden, and it led to another spirit medicine garden.

At this moment, Han Li was standing beside the door of silver light, instructing the giant mountain apes to transfer the harvested spirit medicines into the spirit medicine garden in the Flower Branch domain in an orderly fashion.

Right at this moment, Weeping Soul emerged from the Flower Branch domain, then said, "All of the spirit medicines at or above a million years of age have already been planted, and those that aren't fit to be replanted have been stored into the spirit medicine pavilion."

"The plots of spirit farmland that in our spirit medicine garden are rather limited area, so I'm assuming there's not much space left at this point, right?" Han Li asked.

"There's already no space left," Weeping Soul replied.

"The replanted spirit medicines have already been planted with the smallest possible gaps between them. If we plant them any closer, it's going to affect their growth," Han Li mused.

All of a sudden, he took a glance up at the sky.

"What's wrong?" Weeping Soul asked.

"Some people have already entered the secret area. It looks like I'm going to have to take some drastic measures..." Han Li sighed.

"What do you have in mind, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"Leave these spirit medicines, just instruct the puppets to harvest all of the Nine-Leaved Ice Herbs, Heavenly Sun Parasol Flowers, and Bell Spirit Herbs. Even if they're less than a hundred thousand years old, make sure to take every single one and leave none behind. As for the other spirit medicines that aren't yet of age, just leave them behind," Han Li instructed.

"I can understand harvesting all of the Nine-Leaved Ice Herbs and Heavenly Sun Parasol Flowers as they're ingredients required in the refinement of many types of dao pills, but why do you want these Bell Spirit Herbs as well?" Weeping Soul asked.

"Bell Spirit Herbs aren't particularly precious in themselves, but they can act as a catalyst. If I plant them near the other two types of spirit medicines, then there's a chance that the Nine-Leaved Ice Herbs could mutate into Nine-Leaved Ice Flame Herbs, while the Heavenly Sun Parasol Flowers could become Heavenly Sun Fire Parasol Flowers," Han Li explained with a smile.

"I see," Weeping Soul replied with an enlightened expression.

"By the way, where's the Essence Fire Raven?" Han Li asked.

"It devoured a Nine Sun Fire Stone not long ago in the Purple Sun Pavilion, and it seems to have been feeling rather unwell since then, so it's been hiding in the bamboo pavilion beside the lotus flower pond this entire time," Weeping Soul replied, much to Han Li's amusement and exasperation.

The Essence Fire Raven had only recently devoured several beads of Rainbow Fire Pill Sand, and the Nine Sun Fire Stone was even more formidable than Rainbow Fire Pill Sand, so Han Li couldn't help but feel a little concerned.

However, given how powerful the Essence Fire Raven had become, his concerns were entirely unnecessary. At the moment, if the Essence Fire Raven were to go all-out, even Han Li would struggle mightily to deal with it.

Chapter 1038: Outrage

Following Weeping Soul's departure, Han Li flew directly into the air above the plots of spirit farmland before surveying the area from the sky.

Half of the spirit medicines had already been harvested. Out of the remaining spirit medicines, most were below a million years of age, but there was no lack of specimens above a hundred thousand years old.

After scouring the area briefly, Han Li's gaze settled on a plot of spirit farmland that had a high concentration of spirit medicines, and he flew down to its edge.

He then quickly made a lap around the plot of spirit farmland, periodically stomping a foot down onto the ground as he did so. With each stomp, a long crack would appear in the ground underfoot, and by the time he completed the lap, the entire plot of spirit farmland, which was over ten acres in area, had already sunk down by a foot, looking completely disjointed from the surrounding land.

Han Li crouched down slightly, rolling up his sleeves before reaching his hands into the crack on the edge of the plot of spirit farmland, and a burst of azure light surged out of his hands to encompass the entire plot of land.

Immediately thereafter, the plot of spirit farmland was lifted up by him like a giant piece of fabric, following which he began to make his way toward the door of silver light.

At this moment, Weeping Soul was still instructing the giant ape puppets nearby, and she couldn't help but be amused by the sight of Han Li under the giant plot of spirit farmland.

We should've just done the same thing to all of the spirit farmland here!

As Han Li arrived before the door of silver light, it abruptly swelled up in size at his behest, becoming large enough to fit both him and the plot of spirit farmland.

The door of light led directly to the spirit medicine farm in the domain, and Han Li made his way to a vacant area outside the farm before setting down the plot of spirit farmland.

Of course, he had also considered carrying in all of the spirit farmland, but ultimately, the Flower Branch domain was limited in area, and it couldn't be used entirely to house plots of spirit farmland.

At this point, he had already scoured all of the buildings in the secret area that had been revealed by the receding mist, and he had taken every single treasure at or above the spirit treasure caliber before stowing them away in the domain.

In order to store these treasures, Han Li had disassembled a three-story pavilion inside the secret area before reconstructing it near the spirit medicine garden in his Flower Branch domain, right next to the spirit medicine pavilion.

After setting down the plot of spirit farmland, Han Li immediately emerged from the Flower Branch domain to find that Weeping Soul and the giant ape puppets were beginning to enter the door of silver light.

"Weeping Soul, I've set down the plot of spirit farmland, but it still needs to be connected to the earth veins in the domain and watered with spirit liquid," Han Li said.

"Leave it to me, Master," Weeping Soul replied as she entered the Flower Branch domain, following which Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to close the door of silver light.

After that, he turned and cast his gaze deeper into the secret area.

That area was riddled with restrictions, making it very difficult to access.

All of a sudden, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he suppressed his own immortal spiritual power fluctuations, then rushed around the hill to hide behind it.

Not long after his departure, several figures arrived on the scene, including cultivators from the Spirit Heaven Sect, Blazing Light City, and the Azure Lock Valley.

The square-faced man from the Spirit Heaven Sect was also among them, and he rallied in a loud voice, "Everyone, all of us must unite against the Heavenly Water Sect and the Almighty Sword Sect if we want to reap any substantial rewards in this immortal manor. At a time like this, we cannot afford to be selfish and divided."

"Cut the preamble, Yu Kuohai. What exactly is it that you want to say?" a Blazing Light City elder asked.

"Be patient now, Elder Yang. What I want to propose is that we all join forces to harvest the spirit medicines here together, and if any other sects try to encroach upon this place, then we unite to oppose them. What do you say?" Yu Kuohai proposed.

"That's not a bad proposal. What I'm wondering is how we're going to split the spirit medicines here. This immortal manor has been sealed for countless years, so this place must be laden with precious spirit medicines of very advanced ages," the handsome man from the Azure Lock Valley said.

"There are three tiers on this hill, are there not? Let's just pick one each, Valley Master Fu," Yu Kuohai replied.

"Alright, then it's settled," Elder Yang agreed, and the group of cultivators immediately entered the spirit medicine fields.

However, it didn't take long before all of them erupted into furious fits.

"What the hell happened here?!" Elder Yang roared.

"Someone got here before us!" Valley Master Fu yelled.

"Which bastard did this?! They even dug out an entire chunk of spirit farmland!"

The cultivators of the other two sects faltered slightly upon hearing this, then turned to examine their designated plots of spirit farmland. At the very least, none of the spirit farmland had been dug out, and there were still some spirit medicines left behind ranging from tens of thousands to over a hundred thousand years of age.

Meanwhile, Yu Kuohai could barely contain his own fury as he glowered at the massive chunk of missing land before him. The soil on the edges of the crater was still very moist, indicating that the spirit farmland had clearly only been dug out not long ago.

He sprang up into the air before scouring his surroundings, trying to find the perpetrator, but to no avail.

The cultivators of the three sects quickly gathered what little remained of the spirit medicines in the fields, then reunited with one another before loudly cussing out whoever had gotten here before them.

"There's no point in venting right now. The cultivators of the Yellow Wind Sect and the Ink Fragrance Pavilion seem to have gone to a building not far away from us. If we go there now, we should be in time to intercept them," Yu Kuohai said.

"But if we do that, won't we pit ourselves in direct conflict with those two sects?" Valley Master Fu asked in a hesitant manner.

"It's just the Yellow Wind Sect and the Ink Fragrance Pavilion, what do we have to fear?" Elder Yang scoffed.

"In that case, it's decided. If they're willing to hand over some of their treasures, then we'll let them off the hook, but if they refuse to hand over anything to us, then we'll have no choice but to make them suffer a little," Yu Kuohai said with a cold smile.

After reaching a consensus, the cultivators of the three sects began to fly in the direction of the building in question.

However, on the way there, they discovered the Yellow Wind Sect and Ink Fragrance Pavilion cultivators flying toward them, and they had been joined by the cultivators of the White Cloud Mountain Cottage and the Worry Not Pavilion.

The two groups drew to a halt several thousand feet apart, and looking at the disgruntled expressions on one another's faces, all of them were struck by a sense of foreboding.

"Could it be that everything has already been looted on your end as well?" Yu Kuohai asked.

"It sounds like the same thing happened to you," the elderly woman from the Yellow Wind Sect mused.

"There was even an entire chunk of spirit farmland taken away," Yu Kuohai replied through gritted teeth.

"The entire building on our end was almost taken apart," the elderly woman from the Yellow Wind Pavilion sighed.

"What kind of shameless bastard could've done something like this?!"

In a forest hundreds of kilometers away, Han Li suddenly sneezed without any warning.

At this moment, there was a rather hesitant look on his face.

At this point, it was already abundantly clear that people from the outside had entered the secret area. However, in order to avoid being discovered, he had refrained from using his spiritual sense to do any scouting. As a result, he had no idea how many people had entered the secret area.

At the moment, he was still some distance away from the deepest parts of the secret area, so there simply wouldn't be enough time for him to break the restrictions up ahead and loot all of the treasures ahead of everyone else.

If he were to get into a conflict with these people, then his identity would inevitably be exposed, and if he were to attract the attention of the likes of Qi Mozi, then he wasn't confident in his ability to escape safely.

However, it was clear that this was no ordinary secret area, so there had to be some extremely precious treasures hidden in its deepest parts.

Most importantly, Han Li could sense a faint hint of time law power fluctuations coming from up ahead, and he couldn't bear to turn his back on it.

After much contemplation, he was finally able to think of a middle ground idea.

With his mind made up, he released some of his spiritual sense, sweeping it through the nearby area.

Moments later, he flipped a hand over to produce a crimson Reincarnation Palace mask that he promptly put on, and in the blink of an eye, he transformed into a middle-aged man with eyes that were set quite far apart, giving him a slightly dull and slow-witted appearance.

Immediately thereafter, his body shrank down in height while becoming more compact and muscular, giving him the appearance of a hard-working farmer.

At the same time, he released part of his immortal spiritual power fluctuations, restricting his own aura to the early-Golden Immortal Stage.

He then flipped a hand over to conjure up a mirror or azure light, and after examining his own reflection momentarily, he gave a pleased nod.

After that, he leaped into the greenery to the side and vanished out of sight.

Chapter 1039: Playing Hard to Get

Several minutes later, a rowdy group began passing through on a nearby path.

The group was led by Yu Kuohai of the Spirit Heaven Sect, and trailing along behind him were Elder Yang of Blazing Light City and Valley Master Fu of the Azure Lock Valley, followed by all of the other cultivators of the three sects.

"That bastard better pray that I don't get my hands on him! Otherwise, I'm going to skin him and grind his bones down into powder! I've never met anyone so shameless in my entire life!" Elder Yang grumbled, clearly still feeling extremely bitter and enraged.

"Calm down, Elder Yang. Back when the secret area opened up, all of us entered it together, and we were sent out to our designated areas under the arrangements of the Heavenly Water Sect and the Almighty Sword Sect, so there shouldn't be anyone capable of getting here ahead of us," Yu Kuohai mused.

Elder Yang faltered slightly upon hearing this, then asked, "Are you saying that there's been some foul play from those two sects?"

"I wouldn't put it out of the question. Perhaps they had already sent out people in secret to loot all of the places ahead of time before assigning us our areas of exploration," Valley Master Gu speculated.

The three of them fell silent at this notion. Even if the two sects really had played a trick on them, did they have the power required to oppose them?

"If that's the case, then we're most likely going to continue to be at their mercy unless we do nothing. Do any of you have any counter strategies?" Yu Kuohai asked.

Elder Yang and Valley Master Fu exchanged a glance with each other, but neither of them said anything.

After a long silence, Elder Yang sighed, "All we can do is take things one step at a time and proceed with caution. If we can fight for some opportunities, then don't hesitate to do so, but if we can't, then at the very least, we should do our best to ensure that we won't be used by others."

"Indeed, that appears to be all that we can do for now," Valley Master Fu sighed.

As the three of them were conversing with one another, they suddenly heard a loud commotion coming from the forest up ahead, immediately following which a large cloud of dust rose up into the air from afar.

Everyone turned in that direction to discover a well-built middle-aged man with his clothes in tatters, fleeing for his life from a boar-like metal beast.

The beast was over a hundred feet tall, and its golden fur resembled masses of steel needles, while a pair of curved golden tusks were protruding out of its mouth, resembling a pair of halberds.

Upon catching sight of Yu Kuohai's group, the man immediately began frantically yelling for help.

"Save me, fellow daoists!"

Before anyone had a chance to figure out what was happening, the man was already upon them, and he sprang over everyone's heads in a blind panic, only stopping his tracks after crashing into a huge tree.

The metal beast immediately abandoned the man to attack Yu Kuohai's group, who hurriedly summoned their treasures to defend themselves.

They weren't taking on the metal beast because they wanted to help the man out of the kindness of their hearts. Instead, it was because metal beasts were formed by the purest metal-attribute spiritual qi, so their beast cores contained metal law powers, thereby making them quite desirable.

"Let's kill this thing and take its beast core!" Yu Kuohai yelled, and everyone immediately sprang into action, raining down attacks upon the metal beast.

The metal beast only possessed powers roughly on part with a mid-Golden Immortal cultivator, so it stood no chance against the cultivators from the three sects, and it didn't take long before Elder Yang was able to pierced a fiery blade through its head, obtaining its beast core in the process.

The body of the metal beast didn't contain any law powers, but it made for a very good tool refinement material, so it was smashed into bits and split among everyone.

After all of that was done, Yu Kuohai and the others turned to the middle-aged man who had just fled out of the forest, only to discover that he was about to sneak away.

"Where do you think you're going?" Yu Kuohai yelled, and with a flick of his wrist, a black whip shot out of his sleeve like a spirit snake, wrapping itself around the man's waist before dragging him to Yu Kuohai, sending him tumbling to the ground.

"I don't think I've seen this man before. Do any of you have any recollection of him?" Valley Master Fu asked.

"I don't recall seeing him before, either. At the very least, I'm fairly certain he's not from any of the major sects," Elder Yang said.

"Everything will become clear once I've searched his soul," Yu Kuohai said with a sinister grin.

"Don't do that! Let's be civilized now, Fellow Daoist," the middle-aged man hurriedly yelled.

"Shut your mouth! How do we know you're not the one who looted all the treasures that were meant to be ours?" someone from the Spirit Heaven Sect yelled.

"Seeing as none of us have seen him before, that is a possibility," Elder Yang mused, and everyone immediately began calling for his soul to be searched.

Yu Kuohai took a glance at the man to find that he had a rather slow-witted appearance, indicating that he wasn't some sly individual, but as a safety precaution, he was still planning to search the man's soul.

The man was naturally none other than Han Li in disguise.

Earlier, he had sensed this group of people approaching the forest, and he decided to try and incorporate himself into their group to try and dig up some useful information. Hence, he had gone to seek out that metal beast and goaded it into chasing him.

However, right as Yu Kuohai was about to reach out for Han Li, a burst of golden light suddenly flashed over his body, and he was able to slip out of the black whip before rising to his feet.

"Rest assured, fellow daoists, my name is Shi Mu, and I bear no ill will," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a respectful salute.

Everyone was quite alarmed to see him slipping out of Yu Kuohai's whip so easily, and they immediately surrounded him with wary looks on their faces.

Han Li hurriedly raised his hands in surrender upon seeing this, and he explained, "I'm proficient in some techniques that allow me to escape from bindings, but rest assured, I pose no threat to any of you. May I ask where we are right now?"

Everyone was rather taken aback by this question.

"You don't know what this place is?" Yu Kuohai asked.

Han Li put on a fearful expression as he explained, "I was hunting a beast in the forest earlier, and I somehow stumbled into a strange col. It seemed to be a completely open area, but somehow, I kept walking around in circles, like I was in a maze.

“Thankfully, I'm somewhat proficient in a few illusion and restriction dispelling techniques, and I was able to make it out of the col, only to end up here. Almost as soon as I entered this place, I was attacked by that metal beast, and it chased me all the way here."

"Are we just supposed to take your word for it? Someone looted this entire area before us, and we suspect that you're that person. If you want to prove your own innocence, then hand over your storage tool for us to examine," Yu Kuohai ordered.

"That's too unreasonable a request! The contents of one's storage tool is a matter of privacy..." Han Li protested in a reluctant manner.

"I'm afraid you don't have much of a choice in the matter," Elder Yang said in a cold voice, and everyone began to close in around Han Li, further exacerbating the fear in his eyes.

Finally, he succumbed to the pressure, heaving a resigned sigh as he said, "Fine, you can examine my storage tool, but please let me go after that."

He slipped a storage finger that he had prepared earlier off his finger as he spoke, then handed it over.

Yu Kuohai took the storage ring from him, then inspected its contents briefly with his spiritual sense, upon which his brows furrowed slightly as he handed the ring to Elder Yang.

After examining its contents, Elder Yang's brows also furrowed slightly as he handed the ring to Valley Master Gu.

"How are you this impoverished as an early-Golden Immortal cultivator?" Valley Master Fu couldn't help but ask.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he sighed, "I'm just an itinerant cultivator, so I'm naturally not as blessed as yourselves. It's a struggle for me just to acquire enough cultivation resources to get by."

"Looks like you really are just some poor idiot who stumbled into this place by chance," Valley Master Fu mused as he tossed the storage ring back at Han Li, who eagerly grabbed it before putting it on with a bashful smile.

"I've already taken up far too much of your precious time, so I'll be taking my leave now."

"Hold on a second, Fellow Daoist Shi," Yu Kuohai suddenly called out.

"Can I help you with something else, Fellow Daoist?" Han Li asked.

"Earlier, you mentioned that you're well-versed in some restriction dispeling techniques, is that correct?" Yu Kuohai asked with a smile.

Han Li immediately feigned a smug expression as he replied, "I don't mean to brag, but despite my mediocre cultivation base, when it comes to restriction dispelling techniques, I..."

He then pretended to have realized that he had misspoken, and he hurriedly amended, "Of course, I still can't even begin to compare with all of you in this regard."

"Why are you asking him this, Fellow Daoist Yu?" Elder Yang asked through voice transmission.

"Seeing as the Heavenly Water Sect and the Almighty Sword Sect want to use us as cannon fodder, why don't we find some cannon fodder as well? This man has delivered himself right to our doorstep, and he claims to be proficient in restriction dispelling techniques, so he's the perfect candidate, is he not?" Yu Kuohai replied through voice transmission.

Chapter 1040: Cannon Fodder

Even though Han Li was unable to hear the contents of the voice transmission conversation between Elder Yang and Yu Kuohai, it wasn't difficult to guess what they were talking about.

However, he displayed no reaction to this, instead looking around with a contemplative look on his face.

After a brief conversation, Elder Yang and Yu Kuohai turned their attention back to Han Li again.

"Would you be able to point out a way for me to leave this place, fellow daoists? I still have some urgent matters that I have to attend to," Han Li said.

"Why are you in such a hurry to leave, Fellow Daoist Shi? Truth be told, you've stumbled upon a massive stroke of luck! This place is a lost immortal abode with countless treasures and opportunities inside. As long as you come with us, you'll be sure to reap some significant rewards," Yu Kuohai said with a benevolent smile.

"What? A lost immortal abode? I knew something looked a little different about this place!" Han Li immediately exclaimed as he feigned an ecstatic expression.

"That's right, this is the former immortal manor of a Great Encompassment cultivator by the name of Immortal Lord Tai Sui. You must've been fated to stumble into this place, so don't squander this opportunity that fate has bestowed upon you!" Yu Kuohai urged.

"Indeed. We are all cultivators from righteous sects, and the fact that we've met here means that our fates were destined to intertwine, so why not come explore this immortal manor with us together?" Valley Master Fu offered with a smile.

Han Li's heart was full of disdain upon hearing this. If some clueless itinerant cultivator were in his place, perhaps they really would be led astray by this tantalizing offer.

All of the other cultivators from the three sects were looking much more friendly and relaxed at this point, but they still formed a loose circle around Han Li, so it was clear that they weren't going to let him slip away.

Han Li put on a conflicted expression, acting as if he were feeling swayed by the offer.

From Yu Kuohai's perspective, all Han Li needed was a little bit more of a push, and he gave Elder Yang a subtle look, upon which the latter immediately said, "Fellow Daoist Shi, you don't know where to go anyway, so as opposed to stumbling around aimlessly in this secret area, it would be much safer for you to travel with us."

Before Han Li had a chance to reply, a hostile look suddenly appeared on Valley Master Gu's face as he asked, "Why are you so hesitant, Fellow Daoist Shi? Could it be that you don't think very highly of the Spirit Heaven Sect, Blazing Light City, and our Azure Lock Valley."

"Of course not! I have nothing but respect for you all, and I'm flattered that you think highly enough of me to invite me along. I am willing to come with you, and I don't wish for any compensation, all that I wish for is to be useful to you all," Han Li hurriedly replied as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"You know what? He's not so bad. If he really does prove himself to be useful, then we should spare him," Valley Master Gu said to Yu Kuohai and Elder Yang through voice transmission.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Shi. As long as you do your best to help us, you'll certainly be rewarded for your efforts," Yu Kuohai said with a benevolent smile.

Han Li hurriedly nodded in response with a grateful and awestruck look on his face.

After a brief conversation, everyone continued to make their way deeper into the secret area.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, you came from a different direction from the one that we came from, did you encounter anything useful along the way?" Elder Yang suddenly asked.

"I didn't even know that I was in a lost immortal manor, so I didn't have the presence of mind to search for any treasures. Not long after entering this place, I encountered that metal beast, and I was in such a panic to get away from it that I don't even recall what route I took to flee here," Han Li replied with an embarrassed expression.

"Don't worry about it. Now that you're with us, something like that won't happen again," Yu Kuohai assured.

"Thank you, everyone," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

Yu Kuohai's trio exchange a glance with one another, and the three of them were all feeling a hint of derision toward Han Li, thinking to themselves that they were going to use him as cannon fodder should the need arise.

The group continued onward down the forest path, and Han Li remained silent as he listened to their conversations, only to discover that the majority of the conversations consisted of verbally denouncing whoever had claimed the treasures in this area before them.

Similarly, they were also expressing disdain and dissatisfaction toward the Heavenly Water Sect and the Almighty Sword Sect.

"Are there cultivators from the Heavenly Water Sect and the Almighty Sword Sect in this secret area as well, Fellow Daoist Yu?" Han Li asked.

Yu Kuohai was about to ignore him, but upon seeing the fearful look on his face, he was worried that Han Li would be too scared to continue onward, so he could only offer some reassurance.

"Do not fear, Fellow Daoist Shi. This secret area is massive. Those two sects may be quite powerful in the outside world, but they haven't sent many people into this place this time, and there's no way they'll be able to claim all of the opportunities in here."

"That's right! If they dare to try any more funny business, then we'll just have to join forces with the Yellow Wind Sect, the Ink Fragrance Pavilion, and the others. Even they will have to be wary of our collective power!" Valley Master Fu chimed in.

Han Li hurriedly nodded in response, looking much more reassured.

A mocking sneer appeared on Valley Master Gu's face upon seeing this, but he made sure to hide it from Han Li.

Unbeknownst to him, Han Li didn't regard the cultivators of the Heavenly Water Sect and the Almighty Sword Sect as a threat at all. Instead, what he wanted to know was whether Qi Mozi and cultivators from the Immortal Palace were in this secret area.

With that in mind, he asked, "May I ask if there are any other powers that we should be particularly wary of aside from the Heavenly Water Sect and the Almighty Sword Sect?"

"Why are you asking so many questions, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

Valley Master Fu was beginning to lose his patience.

"Please forgive me, Fellow Daoist Fu. It's just that I don't want to inadvertently make any powerful enemies and bring trouble to everyone," Han Li replied in a sheepish manner.

"That's actually a good thing to consider. Having said that, aside from the cultivators of the Heavenly Water Sect and the Almighty Sword Sect, there isn't really anyone else in here that we have to be particularly wary of," Elder Yang replied.

This response yielded no useful information, and Han Li heaved an internal sigh upon hearing this.

However, it was clear that if Qi Mozi and cultivators from the Immortal Palace were present in the secret area, at the very least, then they had to have disguised themselves. Otherwise, the presence of a Great Encompassment cultivator in this secret area would've been sure to create quite a stir.

At the moment, all he could do was follow this group and see where it took him.

With that in mind, he didn't ask any further questions, and after walking through the forest for several hours, the group arrived at a majestic red palace.

However, Yu Kuokai and the others weren't particularly elated to see this. Instead, they were all trying to temper their expectations in case this place had also been looted in advance.

Upon arriving in front of the hall, a relieved look appeared on Yu Kuohai's face as he declared, "It looks like the restrictions are still intact."

"You're quite skilled at breaking restrictions, are you not, Fellow Daoist Shi? Why don't you come and take a look at this one here?" Elder Yang proposed with a smile.

"Alright, I'll give it a try."

Han Li knew that Elder Yang was trying to test him, and he rolled up his sleeves, looking as if he were eager to meet the challenge.

Upon arriving at the palace gates, he discovered that there was a round metal slab embedded into its surface. The metal slab carried a design of a pair of beasts with their heads and tails interconnected to one another, as well eight lightning runes.

Han Li was immediately able to identify the eight runes as ones that represented the legendary Eight Thunder Gods, while the two beasts at the center were the Bipolar Lightning Beasts.

However, he didn't immediately say anything. Instead, he began scratching his own head while feigning a puzzled expression.

"Can you break this restriction or not, Fellow Daoist Shi? If you can't, then speak up, and I'll break it by force," Yu Kuohai called out in a slightly disgruntled manner.

"I can recognize the Bipolar Lightning Beasts on this metal slab, but I don't recognize all of the surrounding runes. All I can tell is that this is a lightning restriction, and that if it's broken by force, then the restriction will be activated, and the entire palace will be destroyed by lightning," Han Li replied with a hesitant expression.

"Really?" Yu Kuohai asked with a skeptical expression.

"If you don't believe me, then you can give it a try, Fellow Daoist Yu," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

A contemplative look appeared on Yu Kuohai's face upon hearing this, following which he smiled as he said, "Of course I believe you, Fellow Daoist Shi. Do you have any way to break this restriction?"

"I can only give it a try. Would any of you like to do the honors?" Han Li asked.

Everyone looked back and forth at one another, following which all of them turned collectively to Han Li.

"You're the one breaking the restriction, so it would naturally be best for you to test out your own methods yourself," Elder Yang said with a smile, and everyone else nodded in agreement.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he said, "In that case, please step back a little, everyone. I don't know how powerful this restriction is going to be."

Everyone did as they were told, retreating to over a thousand feet away.

Han Li turned to face the palace with his back to everyone, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he began working on the restriction.

Breaking this restriction wasn't a difficult task for Han Li at all, and it only took him less than a minute to open it by using the Divine Devilbane Lightning in his body.

However, he didn't say anything. Instead, he released his Essence Fire Raven discreetly into the palace.

Some time later, a burst of silver lightning suddenly exploded in front of Han Li, sending him flying back through the air.

Everyone was quite alarmed to see this, and no one noticed a burst of silver flames flying out of the lightning before vanishing up Han Li's sleeve.

In order to sell the act, Han Li flew back over a thousand feet before tumbling heavily to the ground with his clothes in tatters.

Yu Kuohai and the others only took a glance at him before noticing that the palace gates had been opened, and all of them immediately rushed inside, but it didn't take long before a chorus of angry voices rang out from inside.

Chapter 1041: Close Call

Han Li was quite taken aback to hear everyone's furious reactions, and he hurriedly communicated to the Essence Fire Raven through their spiritual connection, "Didn't I tell you not to take everything and leave some behind for them?"

However, he received no response from the Essence Fire Raven. It had been quite groggy ever since it devoured the Nine Sun Fire Stone, and it seemed like it still hadn't returned to normal yet.

Han Li could only shake his head in a resigned manner, then slumped to the ground, pretending to be hurt.

Moments later, Yu Kuohai and the others emerged from the palace with disgruntled expressions before arriving by Han Li's side.

"Are you alright, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Elder Yang asked.

"I'm fine, it's just some external injuries," Han Li replied as he splayed open his charred hands.

"How is this possible? The restrictions were clearly intact, yet there was nothing inside!" Valley Master Fu grumbled.

"Well done, Fellow Daoist Shi. We may not have found anything here, but I'm sure there are plenty of precious treasures waiting for us further up ahead," Yu Kuohai said as he helped Han Li up from the ground.

"Thank you," Han Li replied in a grateful manner.

After taking a short rest here, everyone continued onward, encountering several more buildings, all of which had their restrictions unraveled by Han Li. All of the most precious treasures in those buildings were naturally taken by Han Li, but he made sure to leave some behind for everyone else.

Several days flew by in a flash.

At this moment, Han Li's group was standing at the entrance of a gray canyon.

The canyon was filled with mist, and an enormous gray pagoda could be seen in the distance, standing like a pillar that supported the heavens.

Yu Kuohai was ecstatic at the sight of the pagoda, and he immediately urged everyone to speed up.

Before long, they arrived in front of the pagoda, which was rather antiquated in design and dozens of kilometers in size. In terms of the area that it occupied, it was comparable to the mountains around it, but it was far taller than all of the nearby mountains, reaching all the way up into the clouds.

A series of gray lightning designs had been engraved onto the pagoda, and arcs of gray lightning occasionally sprang out from within, causing the nearby space to tremble violently.

At the very top of the pagoda was a huge golden flame that was burning as radiantly as the sun.

However, it was also rather illusory in appearance, as if it existed in an alternate space that was completely out of reach.

Upon arriving at the pagoda, the excitement felt by Yu Kuohai and the others instantly evaporated.

As it turned out, there were already many people gathered in front of the pagoda.

"Looks like we're late to the party," Yu Kuohai harrumphed in a disgruntled manner.

Han Li paid no heed to the crowd up ahead as he cast his gaze toward the golden flame at the top of the pagoda.

He could sense hints of time law power fluctuations within the fire, but they seemed to have been restricted by something, and if it wasn't for Han Li's heightened sensitivity to time law powers, he wouldn't have been able to detect them at all.

"Let's go. Fellow Daoist Shi, if you're scared of causing trouble, then make sure to be careful with your words and actions here," Yu Kuohai cautioned, and Han Li hurriedly nodded in response.

At this point, almost the entire alliance had already gathered in front of the gray pagoda.

Lei Yuce, Su Anqian, and the leaders of several other major powers were currently gathered in front of a tightly shut stone gate at the foot of the pagoda, above which was a plaque that read "Eon Pagoda".

The stone gate was dark gray in color, and it was also riddled with lightning patterns that released a formidable, gray lightning barrier.

At this moment, Lei Yuce, Su Anqian, and the others seemed to be discussing something among themselves.

On the way here, Han Li had gathered a lot of information by playing dumb and asking questions, so he had compiled decent profiles on Lei Yuce and the others.

The arrival of the Spirit Heaven Sect, Blazing Light City, and Azure Lock Valley cultivators didn't attract much attention. Most of the people gathered in front of the pagoda merely took a glance at them before turning their attention back to the pagoda.

At this moment, the Lan siblings were standing together in a discreet corner of the crowd.

"This must be where the most precious treasures left behind Immortal Lord Tai Sui are being held," Lan Yuanzi said as he looked up at the pagoda with a fervent look in his eyes.

Even though the siblings' mission was to capture Han Li, they naturally didn't want to pass up such a massive opportunity.

"The lightning on this pagoda seems to be very formidable. Do you recognize this lightning?" Lan Yan asked with a curious expression.

"It seems to be some type of yin lightning. I don't know much about lightning, so..."

All of a sudden, Lan Yuanzi's voice trailed off here, and his expression suddenly changed slightly as he flipped a hand over to produce a blue mirror, the surface of which was currently flashing incessantly.

Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and the former exclaimed, "It's Han Li!"

Meanwhile, the time law powers in Han Li's body suddenly rippled slightly, as if it had just been stirred up slightly by something.

Someone's using a sensory immortal treasure to track me!

As soon as he arrived at this realization, he immediately channeled his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique to seal off all of his immortal acupoints. At the same time, he channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and the five distinct time law powers in his body intertwined with each other to form a seal deep within his body, keeping his immortal spiritual power completely contained.

As a time-attribute cultivation art of the highest caliber, not only was the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra extremely powerful, it also granted the user exceptional aura concealment abilities.

Now that Han Li had reached the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage, he was gradually beginning to capitalize on the alternative uses of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

All of a sudden, the blue mirror in Lan Yuanzi's hand stopped flashing, and it reverted back into a normal mirror.

A surprised look appeared on Lan Yuanzi's face upon seeing this, following which he composed himself before stowing the mirror away.

"What happened? Was it a false alarm?" Lan Yan asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"No, Han Li must've detected that someone's trying to track him, so he concealed his own aura. It seems like he's very alert," Lan Yuanzi replied with a grim expression.

"How is that possible? The Heavenly Detection Mirror was given to us by our master, and even Great Encompassment cultivators aren't guaranteed to be able to avoid its detection," Lan Yan exclaimed.

"This just tells us that this Han Li is no ordinary High Zenith cultivator. Having said that, at least we now know that Han Li is currently nearby," Lan Yuanzi said as he began scouring his gaze through the crowd.

"You're right! That group of people that just arrived are very suspicious. The Heavenly Detection Mirror immediately registered a reaction as soon as they arrived, so there's a very good chance that Han Li is among them," Lan Yan said as she cast her gaze toward Han Li's group.

"That is indeed very likely, but we can't just completely ignore everyone else, either," Lan Yuanzi replied with a contemplative expression.

Lan Yan nodded in response, and she was just about to approach Han Li's group for a closer look, only to be stopped by Lan Yuanzi.

"Don't make any rash moves. Right now, we're unable to confirm Han Li's identity, and he most likely hasn't discovered us, either. What we have to do now is engage him in a battle of attrition and observation. I'm sure he won't be able to conceal his own aura forever!"

A look of admiration appeared on Lan Yan's face as he said, "There's no way he'll be able to get away from you, Brother. If he hands himself over to us now, that'll spare us the trouble of having to find him!"

......

Who's trying to track me? Qi Mozi? That feels unlikely. If he had this tracking method up his sleeve, then he would've used it long ago. Who else could it be? Could it be those Lan siblings of the Nine Origins Temple?

Han Li's mind was racing as he discreetly scanned his gaze over the surrounding crowd.

All of a sudden, his gaze settled on a certain young man, following which he quickly looked away again to avoid attracting the attention of the subject of his observation.

That young man was none other than Xiong Shan, and at this moment, he was standing with a group of itinerant cultivators at the edge of the crowd.

Even though Han Li had only caught a brief glimpse of the young man back at the Golden Origin Immortal Palace, he was certain that it was the same person.

Why is it that he seems so familiar to me? Who is he? On top of that, if he's here, then Qi Mozi must be here as well. Could it be that it really was Qi Mozi that was trying to track me just now?

Upon arriving at the realization that Qi Mozi was present, Han Li immediately became more apprehensive.

Even though he had reached the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage, he still wasn't confident in his own ability to match up against Qi Mozi, considering he was a Great Encompassment cultivator who had also mastered the laws of time.

On top of that, there was a chance that Lan siblings from the Nine Origins Temple were also here, and if that were the case, then that would only further compound his woes.

Right as Han Li was weighing up his options, Yu Kuohai's trio made their way to the entrance of the giant pagoda.

"Fellow Daoist Yu, how did things go on your end?" Lei Yuce asked.

"Almost all of the places that we passed through had already been completely looted!" Yu Kuohai replied in a hateful voice.

"Don't be disheartened, Fellow Daoist Yu. The restrictions here are still intact, so the treasures inside this Eon Pagoda are most likely still inside. However, the Thousand Integration Yin Lightning Array on the gate is not going to be easy to bypass. Do any of you have good ideas?" Lei Yuce asked.

Yu Kuohai's trio exchanged a glance with each other, following which Valley Master Gu said, "None of us can even hold a candle to your expertise when it comes to breaking restrictions, Fellow Daoist Lei. If you've already identified the restriction on the gate, then I'm sure you have a plan on how to break it, right?"

"I do have an idea in mind, but I'm going to require everyone's assistance," Lei Yuce replied with a smile.

"Not a problem, go ahead and tell us what we need to do, Fellow Daoist Shi," Yu Kuohai declared.

A pleased look flashed through Lei Yuce's eyes, and he began, "In that case, please..."

A discussion that lasted close to an hour took place before the group dispersed to gather helpers, and in the end, close to a hundred people were assembled for the purposes of setting up an elaborate array on the ground in front of the pagoda.

Chapter 1042: Breaking the Array

Lei Yuce and Wen Zhong were standing together, observing the ongoing work from nearby.

"How confident are you that this will work, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Wen Zhong asked through voice transmission.

"60% to 70% at a conservative estimate. For the sake of the Eon Divine Lamp, even if there's only a 10% chance of success, we still have to give it a try, do we not?" Lei Yuce asked.

"According to legends, the Eon Divine Lamp is an immortal treasure that Immortal Lord Tai Sui spent his entire life to refine. I wonder exactly what type of treasure it is," Wen Zhong said as a look of longing appeared in his eyes.

A serious look then appeared on his face as he turned to Lei Yuce and continued, "Fellow Daoist Lei, I know that you've always held a great deal of admiration toward Su Anqian, but securing the Eon Divine Lamp is vital for the future prosperity of our Almighty Sword Sect, so make sure you don't let your private feelings get in the way of pursuing the greater good."

Lei Yuce's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but he replied in a serious manner, "Rest assured, I understand my responsibilities as the deputy sect master."

"Good," Wen Zhong said with a pleased expression.

Under everyone's collective efforts, the construction of the array was progressing rapidly, and in less than half a day, an enormous black and white array had already taken shape in front of the giant pagoda.

Han Li was observing the array from within the crowd, and all of a sudden, an intrigued look appeared in his eyes as he called upon Weeping Soul and the Essence Fire Raven through their spiritual connection.

A few moments later, two drastically contrasting auras, one scorching hot and one freezing cold, seeped out of his body.

"Everyone, this is a twin array designed by our alliance leader for the purpose of breaking this restriction. Each half of the array needs to be powered by fifty fellow daoists. Now, I'm going to call out the people who have been chosen to power the array, please step forward once I've instructed you to do so," Wen Zhong declared.

At this moment, there were over a thousand cultivators gathered in front of the pagoda, and none of them dared to raise any objections, but they were all praying that they weren't chosen.

It was clear that the restriction outside the pagoda was very formidable, so breaking it had to have been a very risky endeavor.

Wen Zhong could tell what everyone was thinking from their reactions, but he hardly cared, and he immediately began picking out the people that he wanted.

With each person that he called out, he would point at that person, and a beam of white light would shoot out of his fingertip before adhering to that person's body.

It didn't take long before a hundred people were picked out, and they were reluctant to step forward, but ultimately did so nonetheless.

The one hundred chosen individuals displayed a wide range of cultivation bases ranging from the True Immortal Stage all the way up to the High Zenith Stage, but the one common trait among them was that they were all cultivating either yin or yang-attribute cultivation arts, and there was a perfectly even split.

So it's a yin yang twin array, Han Li thought to himself with a contemplative expression.

Under normal circumstances, he would've taken some risk to help power the array in order to access the pagoda, but at the moment, there were people observing him in secret, and that was why he had released the auras of Weeping Soul and the Essence Fire Raven, giving himself a very chaotic aura.

Even though Han Li had already been traveling with Yu Kuohai's group for several days, he never revealed to them what cultivation arts he was using, so they weren't suspicious of his slight change in aura.

The Lan siblings were both using yin-attribute cultivation arts, and even though they had used secret techniques to conceal their true cultivation bases, they hadn't done anything to alter their own auras, so they had also been chosen to power the array.

The two of them obediently obliged, perhaps in order to avoid unnecessary conflict.

''What a pain!" Lan Yan grumbled through voice transmission as she sat down onto a certain point in the black half of the array.

"Just bear with it for now. Make sure you don't reveal your true cultivation base," Lan Yuanzi cautioned.

"I know. You can count on me, Brother," Lan Yan promised with a nod.

Right at this moment, a black-robed middle-aged man beside Lan Yan asked in an uneasy manner, "Senior Wen, may I ask if there will be any risk in the process of using this array to break the restrictions ahead?"

"There is always an element of risk when exploring any secret area. If you're so afraid of taking risks, why did you come in here in the first place?" Wen Zhong countered, and the man lowered his head in an embarrassed manner.

"There's no need to be overly concerned. Right now, we are using one array to counteract another, so there will be some risk, but barring any mishaps, it won't be too significant. On top of that, everyone who plays a role here will receive a reward from the alliance, so you won't be contributing your services for nothing," Wen Zhong declared, somewhat easing the tense atmosphere.

"Let's begin!" Lei Yuce declared, and the array immediately began operating, giving off radiant black and white light.

A burst of powerful restrictive force instantly acted upon everyone in the array, rooting them firmly to the spot, and at the same time, a burst of suction force erupted out of the array, rapidly devouring their immortal spiritual power.

Everyone was initially slightly alarmed by this, but the array did nothing else aside from devouring their immortal spiritual power, and that discovery instilled within them a sense of reassurance.

Lei Yuce was hovering in the sky above as he examined the array, and upon ensuring that everything was functioning as it should, he gave a pleased nod before joining his palms together, then spread them apart again.

The array down below instantly lit up, and hundreds of bursts of black and white light flew out from within before surging toward the stone gate of the giant pagoda.

The lightning restriction on the stone gate seemed to have sensed the threat that was being posed, and thick bolts of gray lightning that gave off formidable law power fluctuations erupted out of its surface to strike the bursts of black and white light, instantly tearing them apart with ease.

"What formidable yin lightning!" Han Li murmured to himself with a stunned expression.

The law powers imbued within this type of yin lightning were completely different from those of the lightning in his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The lightning in his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had taken on the properties of Divine Devilbane Lightning, which contained extremely righteous law powers, completely opposite from the immense baleful energy in this gray lightning.

If given the opportunity, Han Li was quite interested in further studying this type of yin lightning.

Lei Yuce seemed to have already anticipated this outcome, and he began chanting an incantation while making a rapid string of hand seals.

The black and white array on the ground instantly glowed over ten times brighter than before, giving rise to enormous pillars of black and white light that gave off a tremendous yin and yang aura.

At the same time, two large flags, one black and one white, flew out of Lei Yuce's body before hovering above his head.

Embroidered onto the white flag was a design of a sun, while a moon had been embroidered onto the black flag. Both flags were giving off astonishing spiritual power and law power fluctuations, indicating that they were immortal treasures of a very high caliber.

As he raised his hands up into the air, the two flags began to revolve in mid-air.

Influenced by the flags, the pillars of black and white light also began to intertwine with one another before rapidly revolving to form an enormous black and white whirlwind.

The whirlwind was radiating dazzling black and white light, as well as bursts of incredibly formidable law power fluctuations, and it swept forward at Lei Yuce's behest, advancing toward the base of the gray pagoda.

The restriction around the pagoda retaliated even more intensely, releasing countless arcs of gray lightning that struck the black and white whirlwind to produce a sound akin to that of metal grating on metal.

In particular, incredibly thick bolts of gray lightning were erupting out of the stone gate, decimating all of the space in their path.

However, the whirlwind was far more resilient than the bursts of black and white light from earlier, and not only was it not torn apart, it had even swept up some of the gray lightning into itself.

The arcs of gray lightning that were swept up into the whirlwind resembled fish that had fallen into a net, unable to break free despite their frantic struggles, and all of the cultivators outside the array erupted into thunderous cheers upon seeing this.

Meanwhile, those inside the array could feel their own immortal spiritual power gushing out of their bodies, and bursts of yin lightning power were also being transmitted to them from afar, resulting in a very painful experience.

Lan Yan's brows were tightly furrowed, and as the bursts of yin lightning power were funneled into her body, she felt as if there were countless tiny insects tearing at her meridians from the inside, inflicting intense agony upon her.

She was able to persevere thanks to her advanced cultivation base, but she was far from happy about the role that she had been assigned.

Outside the array, Han Li was observing the one hundred cultivators inside the array while discreetly releasing his own spiritual sense.

If the people who were tracking him were currently inside the array, then this would be the perfect opportunity for him to try and identify them.

High up in the air above, Lei Yuce was quickly cycling through a string of hand seals, and the black and white whirlwind was revolving rapidly while slowly rising upward.

The lightning that had been swept up into it also rose up with it, and the lightning patterns on the parts of the pagoda's surface that it swept over instantly dimmed, as if the yin lightning inside had been stripped away by the passing whirlwind.

Shortly thereafter, the whirlwind had risen to an altitude of over a hundred feet, and that was where it drew to a halt.

At this point, some of the cultivators in the array below with the lowest cultivation bases had already had their immortal spiritual power completely exhausted, and they had collapsed to the ground with blood flowing out of all of their orifices.

As for the rest, they were also struggling immensely, so they didn't have the spare capacity to worry about the welfare of those around them, and all of the bystanders outside the array were feeling very fortunate that they hadn't been selected to power the array.

As the whirlwind continued to rise up, more and more gray lightning erupted out of the pagoda to strike it, as if the restriction on the pagoda had been infuriated by the challenge that it had been posed.

The black and white whirlwind was still revolving as it captured all of the oncoming arcs of gray lightning, but it was clearly revolving much slower than before.

The stone gate of the giant pagoda was revealed beneath the whirlwind, and all of the gray lightning on it had faded away, leaving the gate enshrouded beneath only a translucent light barrier.

This translucent light barrier was very similar in appearance to the one at the entrance of the secret area, and it appeared even thicker and sturdier.

Chapter 1043: Identifying the Enemy

Lei Yuce's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, following which he gritted his teeth and shot forward through the air, instantly arriving in front of the stone gate before pressing his hands against the light barrier.

One hundred and eight golden flying needles shot out of his body, and there was an extremely life-like golden dragon engraved onto the tailend of each one, presenting a display of exceptional craftsmanship.

In the blink of an eye, all one hundred and eight flying needles pierced almost halfway into the light barrier.

"Those are Golden Immortal Slaying Needles!" someone exclaimed from within the crowd.

Immediately thereafter, Lei Yuce began to chant an incantation, and all of the golden needles began to glow radiantly while vibrating at a rapid frequency.

The translucent light barrier began to tremble while giving off bright translucent light, and it was also giving off a piercing shriek, akin to the sound of countless swords and sabers scraping against each other.

A pained look flashed through Lei Yuce's eyes, but it was then instantly replaced by a look of resolve as he let loose a thunderous roar, upon which all of the Golden Immortal Slaying Needles glowed even brighter as they pierced fully into the translucent light barrier before exploding inside.

A string of resounding explosions rang out, and countless cracks instantly appeared over the translucent light barrier, following which it shattered and disintegrated into countless specks of light, exposing the stone gate within.

A relieved look appeared on Lei Yuce's face upon seeing this, while all of the cultivators observing from afar let loose a collective celebratory cheer.

However, right at this moment, the lightning patterns on the pagoda suddenly began to glow brighter than ever while flashing erratically. Immediately thereafter, countless thick arcs of gray lightning that were far more powerful erupted forth, lashing out in all directions.

The black and white whirlwind was already close to a spent force, and it was instantly torn apart by the flailing arcs of gray lightning.

The black and white flags fell out of the air, having already been torn into shreds that were completely devoid of spiritual nature.

After eradicating the black and white whirlwind, the arcs of gray lightning continued to rain down from above.

Lei Yuce's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he immediately shot back in retreat to several dozen kilometers away.

All of the other cultivators in front of the pagoda also sprang back in an alarmed manner, and Han Li was among them.

He had actually anticipated the retaliation from the lightning restriction ahead of everyone else, but he hadn't retreated right away, instead delaying his retreat in order to avoid attracting attention.

Even though the crowds of cultivators were situated some distance away from the pagoda, and all of them had reacted quite quickly, there were still some who were unable to get away in time, and they were struck by the formidable arcs of gray lightning, instantly eradicating both their bodies and their nascent souls.

As for the cultivators inside the Bipolar Yin Yang Array, they were still bound to the spot, and the wave of gray lightning instantly washed over them.

The radiant arcs of lightning had formed a gray sea with astonishingly destructive lightning law power fluctuations churning within, and everything that came into contact with the gray lightning was instantly blown to smithereens.

A string of bloodcurdling howls rang out from within the sea of lightning, only to instantly fade into silence.

Han Li heaved a forlorn internal sigh upon seeing this, and at the same time, he became even more apprehensive of this Eon Pagoda.

If the restriction outside the pagoda was already this dangerous, then the interior of the pagoda surely had to be fraught with peril as well.

Right at this moment, he suddenly spotted a streak of blue light flying out of the sea of lightning.

Immediately thereafter, an earth-shattering explosion rang out within the sea of lightning, and an enormous ball of blinding white light erupted out from within, tearing a huge opening into the sea of lightning.

Around a dozen streaks of light flew out of the opening in the blink of an eye, then faded to reveal a group of around a dozen cultivators.

These people were the most powerful cultivators in the array, and three of them were High Zenith cultivators, while the rest were all at the late and peak-Golden Immortal Stages.

Despite their lofty cultivation bases, all of them were looking very much worse for wear. Their clothes were in tatters, their bodies were riddled with wounds, and some of them were even missing appendages.

The sea of gray lightning flashed momentarily before quickly dissipating, revealing the charred earth underneath. All of the cultivators in the Bipolar Yin Yang Array were already nowhere to be seen, and all that was left behind were some scattered immortal treasure fragments.

Even though all of the bystanders had already anticipated this outcome, it was still a very sobering sight to behold.

Among the dozen or so survivors, a white-robed middle-aged man stepped forward with a furious expression as he yelled, "Lei Yuce, Wen Zhong, didn't you two say that breaking the restriction wasn't going to be a very risky endeavor? How do you explain this?"

There was a white immortal treasure that resembled a round moon hovering before the middle-aged man, but the light that was emanating from it had dimmed significantly, indicating that it had lost much of its spiritual nature.

The man was Daoist Master Sky Moon, the pavilion master of the Rising Moon Pavilion. He was at the mid-High Zenith Stage, possessing the loftiest cultivation base among the dozen or so survivors.

The cultivators of the Rising Moon Pavilion excelled in yin-attribute cultivation arts, so most of the Rising Moon Pavilion cultivators had also been chosen alongside him to enter the array, and they had all met their demise, so he was understandably furious.

All of the other survivors were also glowering intently at Lei Yuce and Wen Zhong, and it was clear from the expressions on the faces of the other cultivators in the alliance that they were also feeling very disgruntled.

A cultivator from the Heavenly Water Sect had also been selected to enter the Bipolar Yin Yang Array, but he had managed to survive, so neither Su Anqian nor Jin Liu said anything as they stood silently off to the side.

"I understand that all of you must be very angry right now. This was a completely unexpected development for me. I had thought that after the restriction on the stone gate was broken, the lightning array on the pagoda would also be disabled, but it's clear that I was too complacent," Lei Yuce explained.

Daoist Master Sky Moon gave a cold harrumph upon hearing this, and the fury on his face didn't abate in the slightest.

"Everyone, Alliance Leader Lei and I are also very saddened in the wake of this tragic incident. Having said that, I made it clear from the beginning that the exploration of a secret area will always come with a major element of risk. No one knows who's going to die where, so we can only leave things in the hands of fate.

“On top of that, Alliance Leader Lei had to sacrifice two of his most powerful treasures to dispel the restriction outside the pagoda, so he's sustained some significant losses as well," Wen Zhong declared.

"Indeed, this was a completely unforeseen accident, so the blame can't be placed on any single person. Without Alliance Leader Lei's Bipolar Yin Yang Array, we would've most likely suffered even more casualties in the process of breaking this restriction, so I suggest that we calm down a little," Jin Liu said.

"Rest assured, once we've completed our exploration of this immortal manor, the alliance will issue compensation for all those who perished here," Wen Zhong reassured.

Daoist Master Sky Moon was clearly not satisfied with this outcome, but seeing as both the Heavenly Water Sect and the Almighty Sword Sect had already spoken, he had no choice but to cut his losses and storm away with a cold harrumph.

Meanwhile, Han Li's attention was focused on the two people who had flown out of the Bipolar Yin Yang Array within that streak of blue light. Those two were none other than the Lan siblings.

No one else had noticed this amid all of the chaos, but thanks to Han Li's tremendous spiritual sense, he was able to detect a burst of tremendous spiritual pressure within the sea of lightning that was not inferior to his own.

As opposed to Daoist Master Sky Moon's immortal treasure, it was this burst of spiritual pressure that had actually torn the sea of lightning apart.

It was abundantly clear to Han Li that those two were concealing their true cultivation bases, and the fact that it was a duo consisting of a man and a woman made him strongly suspect that they could be the Lan siblings of the Vast Golden Immortal Palace.

"I'm sorry, Brother. I panicked a little just now and used my powers to tear open the sea of lightning. Do you think we've already been exposed?" Lan Yan asked through voice transmission as a hint of guilt flashed through her eyes.

"The situation was very urgent just now, so I would've done something even if you hadn't. On top of that, the power of the yin lightning just now would've been enough to conceal your aura from everyone present. At the very least, there shouldn't be anyone present with sufficiently powerful spiritual sense to have detected anything," Lan Yuanzi consoled.

A relieved look appeared on Lan Yan's face upon hearing this.

Meanwhile, a discussion was being held between the cultivators of the Heavenly Water Sect and the Almighty Sword Sect.

Following the conclusion of the discussion, Jin Liu stepped forward as he declared, "Now that the restriction has been undone, we should enter the pagoda right away, but given how formidable the restriction outside the pagoda is, the interior of the pagoda is almost certainly going to be even more perilous.

“Hence, after some discussion, we've decided that those of us with lower cultivation bases should stay outside in order to avoid excessive casualties."

"Senior Jin, what is the cultivation base cutoff that you propose?" an itinerant Golden Immortal immediately asked.

"My proposal is that all fellow daoists below the Golden Immortal Stage stay outside the pagoda, both to keep a lookout and for your own safety," Jin Liu replied.

"That's not fair!"

"Just now, there were so many True Immortals called upon to break the restriction, yet now that the restriction has been undone, you're asking us to stay outside? How does that make any sense?"

"This is a completely unacceptable arrangement!"

The True Immortals that belonged to sects didn't raise much objections to this proposal, but all of the itinerant True Immortals were very much opposed to this arrangement.

"Quiet!" Lei Yuce yelled in an authoritative voice.

His voice wasn't very loud, but it caused the entire surrounding area to tremble and buzz, instantly silencing all of the dissenting True Immortals.

"This decision was made for the sake of everyone's safety. How about this? 30% of the spoils that the alliance reaps will be offered up to be split among all of the fellow daoists that remain outside the pagoda. On top of that, there's no need for all of you to stay here.

“Only a small number of you need to stay here on lookout duty, while the rest can go elsewhere to explore. This secret area is an enormous place, and we only have a limited amount of time, so it would be more efficient for all of you to split up anyway," Lei Yuce said.

All of the dissenting True Immortals immediately began weighing up their options upon hearing this.

In the end, the vast majority of people decided that this was the best arrangement for them when it came to balancing risk and reward, so this course of action was the one that was ultimately agreed upon.

Many of the sects present were reluctant to send their True Immortal Stage disciples into the Eon Tower to begin with, so they were ecstatic to hear that they were going to be compensated for something that they were going to do anyway, and they eagerly instructed their True Immortal Stage disciples to stay outside the pagoda on lookout duty.

Chapter 1044: No Turning Back

"Time is of the essence, so let's enter the pagoda now!" Lei Yuce declared as he descended to the pagoda's stone gate, while everyone else gathered behind him.

With all of the True Immortals barred from entry, the crowd had been whittled down to no more than five hundred people, and Han Li was standing in a relatively discrete area of the crowd.

At this moment, he was scanning his gaze across the nearby crowd in a nonchalant manner, paying particular attention to the duo that he suspected to be the Lan siblings.

Even though he was still unable to confirm their true identities, in his eyes, even if they weren't the Lan siblings, they were still two people that he had to keep an eye on.

Even though the Golden Origin Immortal Palace had been left without a leader in the wake of Dongfang Bai's demise, it would be far too naive to believe that the Heavenly Court wouldn't have sent someone into this secret area, so the fact that he hadn't spotted any Heavenly Court cultivators up to this point was rather suspicious.

Lei Yuce stood at the foot of the pagoda, inspecting his surroundings, and only after ensuring that nothing was amiss did he press a hand against the stone gate.

However, before he even had a chance to exert any force into the gate, it slid away on its own amid a burst of dull rumbling, revealing a dark entrance with what appeared to be the light of a dim flame deep inside.

Lei Yuce was rather taken aback by this, and instead of immediately entering the pagoda, he began to examine its interior from the entrance.

Everyone else also peered into the pagoda while attempting to release their spiritual sense inside, only to discover that there was some type of restriction inside the pagoda designed to keep out spiritual sense.

"Make sure to be on your guard, everyone. If you want to back out now, it's still not too late," Wen Zhong said.

However, everyone had already come this far, and no one was willing to turn back now. All of them had their attention focused on Lei Yuce, waiting for his instructions.

"Let's go," Lei Yuce declared as he stepped into the pagoda, followed immediately by the other cultivators from the Almighty Sword Sect and the Heavenly Water Sect, after whom came everyone else.

Upon entering the pagoda, everyone discovered that there were braziers hanging from the walls with some type of fat burning inside. Whatever the fuel source was, it wasn't releasing any smoke, but it was giving off a faint rank odor.

Directly up ahead was a two-headed statue that was over a hundred feet tall.

The statue was very strange in appearance, with a benevolent, smiling head of a heavenly official, accompanied by a fearsome, monstrous-looking head. Its body was clad in a suit of golden chainmail armor, and there was a pair of golden wings on its back. In one hand, it held a golden scepter, while in its other hand was a mountain-splitting ax.

There was a dark passageway that led deeper into the pagoda beneath both the golden scepter and the mountain-splitting ax, and light could be seen at the ends of both passageways, but it was impossible to make out exactly what lied beyond them.

Right at this moment, someone suddenly yelled, "There's something written on the scepter and the ax!"

Han Li focused his gaze on the scepter and the ax to discover that there was a short line of text on each of them, collectively reading "No turning back once a path is chosen, both paths lead to the same destination."

After reading the displayed text, a contemplative look appeared on Jin Liu's face as he mused, "It looks like there will be different perils awaiting us on each path, but both will ultimately take us to the same place."

"Splitting up would be perfect. Our Heavenly Water Sect and your Almighty Sword Sect can each lead half of the fellow daoists present down one of the two paths," Su Anqian said.

"The interior of this immortal manor is sure to be fraught with peril, so I think it would be unwise for us to split up," Lei Yuce said.

A hesitant look also appeared on Jin Liu's face as he said through voice transmission, "I know that you don't want to take the same route as him, but he's right. If both paths lead to the same destination, then it makes no difference which one we take, and we should all stick together."

"Since when did you become so naive, Senior Martial Brother Jin? How do we know that this statue is telling the truth? How do we know that Immortal Lord Tai Sui hasn't set up a trap, and one of these two paths actually leads to certain death?" Su Anqian countered.

"You're right, that was an oversight on my part. In that case, do you have any idea of which path we should take?" Jin Liu asked with a wry smile。

"There are restrictions in both paths that keep out spiritual sense, so I'm afraid we'll only be able to find out once we're inside," Su Anqian replied.

"Celestial Maiden Su, what do you think of my proposal just now?" Lei Yuce asked.

"I disagree. Your Almighty Sword Sect and our Heavenly Water Sect are the leaders of this alliance. If we go down the same path together, what will all the other fellow daoists do? We can't get them to explore a path on their own," Su Anqian countered in a cold manner.

A hesitant look appeared on Lei Yuce's face upon hearing this.

"I appreciate that you're looking out for us, Fellow Daoist Lei, but Junior Martial Sister Su is right. We have been elected as the leaders of the alliance, so we have to fulfill our rightful duties," Jin Liu said with a smile.

"In that case, go ahead and choose a path, Celestial Maiden Su," Lei Yuce said.

"The heavenly official on the left, while the monster is on the right... I'll choose the right path," Su Anqian decided.

"Alright, in that case, our Almighty Sword Sect will choose the left path. Fellow daoists of the Spirit Heaven Sect, the Azure Lock Valley, Blazing Light City, the Ink Fragrance Pavilion, and the Worry Not Pavilion, please go with Celestial Maiden Su. Everyone else, come with me," Lei Yuce instructed.

Everyone else was rather hesitant about which path to take, but seeing as the alliance leader had spoken, the choice had been made for them.

Before long, everyone had been split up into two groups, and they made their way down the two paths.

Prior to parting ways, Lei Yuce cautioned Su Anqian to be careful, but the latter offered no response.

The Lan siblings were among the Worry Not Pavilion cultivators, and they were conversing with each other through voice transmission.

"Lei Yuce is quite a handsome man, and his cultivation base isn't inferior to Su Anqian's, so why is she so cold to him?" Lan Yuanzi mused in a perplexed manner.

"How is that strange? Men are all the same, regardless of whether they're mortal or immortal. The more something is out of reach, the more alluring it is to them. The more distant and unapproachable Celestial Maiden Su makes herself, the more alluring she'll be to Lei Yuce," Lan Yan replied with a smile.

"Is that right? I suppose this must be what it means to play hard to get," Lan Yuanzi mused.

"Why are you suddenly asking about something like this? Could it be that there's a woman who's recently caught your eye?" Lan Yan asked in a teasing tone.

A slightly embarrassed look appeared on Lan Yuanzi's face, following which he put on a stern expression as he said, "We need to focus on the task at hand. We don't know what perils lie up ahead, so make sure to stay close to me at all times."

Han Li was walking along near the rear of the group, and as he passed by the mountain-splitting ax, he looked up to discover a small line of text where the hand of the statue met the hilt of the ax, which read "an ax to sever the bridge of immortality".

At the same time, a black-robed young woman on the other path looked up at the golden scepter above her as she was passing by, and she also spotted a short line of text that read "fortune or misfortune".

By the time both groups had ventured several thousand feet down their respective paths, a resounding boom suddenly rang out from behind them as the ax and the scepter in the statue's hands came crashing down in unison, sealing the paths shut from behind.

Both groups immediately stopped in their tracks, and Wen Zhong and Jin Liu doubled back to examine the blockages momentarily then returned to their respective groups before declaring that there was no longer a path for retreat, so the only way to go was forward.

The text on the statue had already warned everyone that there would be no turning back once a path was chosen, so everyone quickly accepted this outcome and continued onward.

As the group led by the Heavenly Water Sect made its way down the passageway, Han Li noticed that the stone walls on either side were riddled with all types of patterns, but they were so chaotic and haphazard that even Han Li couldn't tell what purpose they were meant to serve.

The further they went, the narrower the passageway became, and after venturing close to ten kilometers down the passageway, it had narrowed from its initial width of several thousand feet to only several hundred feet.

Initially, everyone had been been feeling quite cautious and apprehensive, looking out for traps and restrictions, but aside from the narrowing of the passageway, nothing else of note was observed.

However, this only made everyone feel more uneasy, as if they were anticipating this being the calm before the inevitable storm.

Upon reaching the end of the passageway, a giant golden gate that was several hundred feet tall appeared up ahead. Engraved onto each half of the gate was a halberd-wielding deity, both of which were very powerful and imposing in appearance.

Everyone's attention was drawn to a pair of deities engraved onto the gate, but there were a small number of people who were looking at the doornails on the gate.

"This appears to be a Yin Yang Latch Array," Yin Liu mused as he observed the doornails, and Han Li couldn't help but be amused by his ignorance.

There was indeed a yin and yang distinction between the doornails in that some were protruding outward, while others were sunken inward, but they actually represented star palaces, with the ones protruding outward zenith yang palaces, and the ones sunken inward zenith yin palaces.

Hence, the true name for this restriction was actually the Star Palace Standoff Array. As for the so-called Yin Yang Latch Array, that was only a smokescreen to conceal the true nature of the array.

"Do you know how to dispel this array, Senior Martial Brother Jin?" Su Anqian asked.

"I can give it a try," Jin Liu replied with a nod.

He then turned around to face everyone as he said, "Everyone, please listen to me. I have something to declare."

Everyone in the passageway immediately fell silent to listen to what he had to say.

Chapter 1045: Hesitance

"What do you have to declare, Fellow Daoist Jin?" Yu Kuohai asked.

"If we want to enter the pagoda to access the treasures inside, then we have to bypass this stone gate, which would require us to unravel this restriction. If I were to do that on my own, it would take at least two days, but if I can have all of your help, then perhaps the restriction can be overcome in an instant," Jin Liu said.

Wary looks immediately appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this. The memory of what had happened to the cultivators in the Bipolar Yin Yang Array was still clear in their minds, and they were terrified of repeating their mistakes.

With no one answering his call, Jin Liu's expression instantly darkened slightly, and he said, "So all of you want to only reap the benefits without putting in any work. Surely that's too much to ask for, is it not?"

"Fellow Daoist Jin, please elaborate on how you plan to break this restriction. That way, we can all be mentally prepared and react accordingly if any unforeseen mishaps occur," Elder Yang said.

"The array on this gate is called a Yin Yang Latch Array, and all that's required is for all of us to inject our immortal spiritual power into the gate at once to create an imbalance in the yin and yang doornails. That will be enough to unravel the restriction and allow us to open this gate," Jin Liu explained.

"That certainly sounds very simple, but is there any potential for backlash from the restriction? Do we run the risk of meeting the same fate as all those fellow daoists in the Bipolar Yin Yang Array?" Yu Kuohai asked.

"This array is different from the previous one, and I can assure you that there's no risk involved here. In order to allay everyone's concerns, I'm willing to join all of you in this effort. If something happens, then I'll have to suffer the consequences as well," Jin Liu replied.

Even after this attempt at reassurance from Jin Liu, there was still no one willing to heed his call, and Su Anqian's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"Is there anyone willing to volunteer themselves?" she asked.

Everyone remained silent, pretending not to have heard her.

A cold look appeared on Jin Liu's face upon seeing this, and he said, "In that case, I'll have to trouble Sect Master Yu, Elder Yang, Valley Master Fu, Pavilion Master Zhao, and Pavilion Master Qin to pick out some cultivators from your respective sects to help me break this array."

"Fellow Daoist Jin..."

As soon as Yu Kuohai's voice rang out, he was sternly cut off by Jin Liu, who snapped, "You've all chosen to join the alliance, so I suggest you follow the orders assigned to you. Otherwise, once we leave this secret area, you won't be the only ones that will have to bear the consequences of your insubordination."

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon hearing this. What Jin Liu was implying here was that if they were to oppose his orders, then the Heavenly Water Sect would come after their sects once they left the immortal manor.

In the face of this thinly veiled threat, everyone had no choice but to comply, and Valley Master Fu was the first to make his stance known, cupping his fist in a salute as he declared, "The Azure Lock Valley is willing to follow the alliance's arrangements."

After that, he began picking out some cultivators from his own sect.

The other important figures present exchanged a few glances with each other upon seeing this, then also followed suit.

Jin Liu's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, and he reminded, "Make sure to pick out one person from each sect who's skilled in unraveling restrictions."

Yu Kuohai immediately turned his gaze to Han Li upon hearing this.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, I'm afraid our Spirit Heaven Sect is sorely lacking in individuals well versed in the art of arrays, so I'll have to trouble you to step forward as our representative," Yu Kuohai said with a warm smile.

Elder Yang and Valley Master Gu couldn't help but roll their eyes upon hearing this, and they were kicking themselves for reacting too late and allowing Yu Kuohai to use this piece of cannon fodder ahead of them.

Han Li was cursing Yu Kuohai internally, and he put on a reluctant expression as he said, "Surely I'm not worthy of representing the Spirit Heaven Sect..."

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Shi. For your contribution here, you can join our Spirit Heaven Sect, and I'll instate you as an inner sect elder, so you'll no longer have to be an itinerant cultivator," Yu Kuohao promised as he laid a hand on Han Li's shoulder.

"Are you being serious, Fellow Daoist Yu?" Han Li exclaimed as he feigned an ecstatic expression.

"Of course! Everyone here has just bore witness to my promise to you," Yu Kuohai replied with a smile.

"In that case, I'll do it," Han Li decided with a nod.

At this moment, Lan Yan was watching Han Li from nearby, and a hint of mockery and sympathy flashed through her eyes as she said to Lan Yuanzi through voice transmission, "What a poor idiot he is, willing to put his life on the line for the promise of such a tiny reward."

"You don't know how difficult life is for itinerant cultivators. For someone like him, an opportunity to become an elder of the Spirit Heaven Sect is far from a tiny reward," Lan Yuanzi replied.

Lan Yan was just about to say something else when Pavilion Master Zhao of the Worry Not Pavilion called upon the two of them to participate in the array-breaking effort.

Shortly thereafter, all of the sects had chosen their representatives, and Jin Liu gave all of the chosen individuals a rundown of the process that had to be undertaken to unravel the restriction on the gate.

Han Li heaved a forlorn internal sigh after hearing what Jin Liu had to say. If they were to follow his proposed method to unravel the restriction, then there was a very good chance that they would incur backlash from the array.

However, given his current identity, he naturally couldn't say anything.

After returning to the Spirit Heaven Sect representatives, he relayed the instructions from Jin Liu, but made some slight alterations that were subtle enough to escape everyone's notice.

Several minutes later, the dozens of cultivators that had been chosen to break the restriction were arranged on either side of the stone gate.

"Everyone, make sure to channel your immortal spiritual power with all your might while breaking the restriction, and do not hold back. Otherwise, if something goes wrong, then you'll have to answer to me," Jin Liu said in a stern manner, and everyone hurriedly gave a collective affirmative response.

"Alright, let's begin," Jin Liu instructed, then cast a burst of blue light into the stone gate, and everyone else immediately followed suit, injecting their immortal spiritual power into the gate as well.

Streaks of light of different colors surged into the doornails on the gate, and the sunken doornails began to protrude outward, while the protruding doornails began to sink inward.

The light that had converged over the stone gate began to swirl like a yin yang symbol, and the gate rumbled violently as it began to loosen.

"Keep it up, everyone! We're almost there!" Jin Liu encouraged in an ecstatic manner.

Everyone immediately redoubled their efforts upon seeing this.

Han Li had been observing the restriction on the gate this entire time, and he knew that this was nothing more than a precursor of the restriction on the gate being activated. At this rate, it was only going to take a few seconds before everyone was struck by backlash from the restriction.

Of course, he didn't really care about whether everyone here lived or died.

Everyone had to take responsibility for their own decisions, and there was always a risk of meeting a premature demise in the pursuit of opportunities.

However, the problem was that there was another group of cultivators currently making their way down the other path, so if he were to be delayed here, only for the other group to get to the treasures in the pagoda first, then that would be a far from desirable outcome.

Right as the yin yang symbol was accelerating in its revolution, the Spirit Heaven Sect representatives suddenly broke off from the rest of the group, injecting their immortal spiritual power into several doornails that Jin Liu hadn't mentioned.

The yin yang symbol instantly ceased in its revolution before disintegrating altogether.

Jin Liu was furious to see this, but before he had a chance to say anything, he suddenly noticed that the disintegrated yin yang symbol had been replaced by an image of a starry sky.

His expression changed slightly as he instantly arrived at the realization that he had misidentified the array, and he yelled, "Listen to me, everyone! There's been a change of plans..."

With that, he began issuing a series of instructions, ordering everyone to inject their immortal spiritual power into different doornails from before.

Thank heavens he's not a complete idiot. Otherwise, I would've had to take matters into my own hands, Han Li thought to himself.

With this new approach adopted, a burst of radiant starlight appeared over the stone gate, and the two deities engraved onto the gate suddenly raised their halberds, following which the gate began to open inward.

A dull grinding sound rang out as the two heavy stone gates gradually parted, revealing a vast expanse of golden light that gave off a burst of very peculiar energy fluctuations.

Everyone immediately peered into the golden light, but they were unable to see anything beyond the golden radiance, even through the use of various spirit eye abilities.

"Could this golden light be coming from some type of treasure?" Yu Kuohai speculated, and fervent looks instantly appeared in everyone's eyes upon hearing this.

"All of you are from major sects in the Golden Origin Mountain Range, are you not? How is it that you're unable to detect that these are clearly energy fluctuations from a metal forcefield?" Su Anqian scoffed with a derisive sneer.

"There are many metal force fields in the Golden Origin Mountain Range, so we are very familiar with such things. These energy fluctuations are clearly different, so surely they're coming from some type of metal-attribute treasure," Elder Yang countered as he raised an eyebrow.

Su Anqian offered no explanation, merely shaking her head with a faint smile, and upon seeing her reaction, Elder Yang was beginning to doubt his own judgment.

Meanwhile, Han Li had already grasped the nature of the situation after just a single glance.

Most of the metal force fields in the Golden Origin Mountain Range were formed naturally, so they received no enhancements from arrays, and as a result, the metal-attribute spiritual power that they released wasn't all that pure.

In contrast, the golden light beyond the stone gate was giving off extremely formidable and pure metal-attribute spiritual power fluctuations, and that was why everyone had been fooled into thinking that it was coming from some type of treasure.

Everyone was standing at the entrance, and they were very keen on getting their hands on whatever treasure lied up ahead, but none of them dared to rush in.

Chapter 1046: Leading the Way

"Regardless of whether there's a metal forcefield inside, we have to proceed with caution. I suggest that we split up into two groups and enter this place one after another. What do we all think?" Jin Liu proposed.

"What sequence are we going to follow?" Yu Kuohai asked.

"Those among us who are using metal-attribute cultivation arts and are adept at breaking restrictions will go in first. If there really is a metal forcefield inside, then the first group will be responsible for disabling it, following which the rest of us will come through," Jin Liu replied.

"This is not a bad proposal, but I don't think it's particularly fair. All of us from the Worry Not Pavilion specialize in metal-attribute cultivation arts. Doesn't that mean that all of us will have to go in first to test the waters for everyone else?" Pavilion Master Zhao countered.

"How about this? Regardless of whether there's a metal forcefield or any restrictions inside, everyone in the first group gets to keep all of the treasures that they obtain. On top of that, the people in the second group won't just be standing around doing nothing. Instead, they'll be constantly ready to reinforce the first group should the need arise," Jin Liu proposed.

Pavilion Master Zhao contemplated this arrangement briefly, then nodded in response.

"That does seem like a reasonable course of action."

"In that case, it's decided. The first group will consist of cultivators using metal-attribute cultivation arts from Blazing Light City, the Worry Not Pavilion, and our Heavenly Water Sect, and they'll be accompanied by cultivators from the Spirit Heaven Sect, the Ink Fragrance Pavilion, and the Azure Lock Valley who are adept at breaking restrictions. What do we all think?" Jin Liu proposed.

Everyone found this to be a reasonable plan, and no one raised any objections.

Once again, Yu Kuohai turned to Han Li, clearly intent on taking as much advantage of him as possible, and Han Li was left feeling a little speechless.

Having said that, his original intention was to enter the hall with the first group anyway, so he readily heeded Yu Kuohai's call. However, what was rather surprising to him was that Yu Kuohai had also volunteered to be part of the first group.

Before long, the lineup for the first group was decided, consisting of fewer than a hundred cultivators.

"I was thinking that I would have to choose a leader for the first group, but my job has been made easy. Fellow Daoist Yu, Fellow Daoist Yang, Fellow Daoist Zhao, I didn't think all three of you would volunteer to be part of the first group," Jin Liu said with a smile.

"The majority of our Worry Not Pavilion's cultivators will be going in, so I certainly can't back down as the pavilion master," Pavilion Master Zhao declared in a righteous manner, drawing much admiration from the disciples of the Worry Not Pavilion.

"Quite a few of our Blazing Light City cultivators will also be going in, so I naturally have to accompany them," Elder Yang said.

"Our Spirit Heaven Sect doesn't specialize in metal-attribute cultivation arts, but I'm an exception, so I wanted to make a contribution on behalf of our sect," Yu Kuohai proclaimed.

Han Li couldn't help but sneer internally at their pretentious displays.

Ultimately, their goal was to seize the initiative and enter the hall first to claim the treasures inside. As for the possibility that there was a metal forcefield inside, perhaps they were merely hoping that this wasn't the case, or perhaps they were of the opinion that they could overcome such an obstacle.

At this moment, Han Li's attention was focused on the Lan siblings, who were also part of the first group.

Lan Yuanzi was conversing with Lan Yan when he suddenly felt an intrusive gaze, and his brows furrowed slightly as he turned around to determine the source of the scrutiny, only to discover that there was no one looking at him.

"What's wrong, Brother?" Lan Yan asked.

"Nothing, it was probably just my imagination," Lan Yuanzi replied with a smile.

"What should we do if there really are treasures inside?" Lan Yan asked through voice transmission.

"If there are treasures inside, then of course I'll be taking all of it for you," Lan Yuanzi replied with a smile.

"In that case, you focus on collecting the treasures, I'll kill everyone else that comes in with us," Lan Yan said with a wide smile.

"Don't be in a hurry to kill these people, they can still be used as cannon fodder," Lan Yuanzi said.

Lan Yan's face immediately puckered up with displeasure upon hearing this.

"But if I don't kill them, I'll have to continue wearing this hideous disguise!"

"If you kill them all, even if you revert back to your original appearance, there will be no one to see it," Lan Yuanzi chuckled.

"You'll get to see it, and that's enough! None of these scoundrels are worthy of laying eyes upon me anyway," Lan Yan giggled.

"It doesn't matter to me what you look like. In my eyes, you will always be the most beautiful woman in the world," Lan Yuanzi said in a gentle manner, and a deep blush immediately appeared on Lan Yan's face upon hearing this. [1]

After making some brief preparations, the first group arrived before the doorway.

"Rest assured, fellow daoists, all of us will be here to back you up if any unforeseen mishaps arise," Jin Liu assured.

Yu Kuohai exchanged a glance and a nod with Elder Yang, following which the two of them stepped in through the doorway, followed by everyone else in the first group.

As soon as they passed through the doorway, everyone immediately vanished into the radiant golden light up ahead, and their auras became undetectable.

Han Li was trailing along behind Yu Kuohai and Elder Yang, and as soon as he entered the space beyond the doorway, he immediately felt a burst of powerful restrictive force act upon him from all directions.

This type of restrictive force was different from the crushing weight of the earth attribute or the viscosity of the water attribute. Instead, it felt like being bound by countless extremely resilient metal threads while simultaneously being subjected to gusts of scathing, metallic wind that felt like tiny daggers scraping over one's skin.

Due to the pervasive golden light in the surrounding area, visibility was significantly impaired, and no one was able to see more than several hundred feet in any direction.

An alarmed look appeared on Pavilion Master Zhao's face as he exclaimed, "What's going on? Could it be..."

"It looks like Celestial Maiden Su was right, there really is a metal forcefield in here," Elder Yang said with a wry smile, then flipped a hand over to produce a golden bead, which he tucked down the front of his own robe, and it immediately released a burst of golden light to encompass his entire body.

Even with his cultivation base, he still had to call upon a protective treasure to withstand the effects of the metal forcefield in this place, and everyone else was naturally faring even worse, frantically summoning protective treasures of their own to shelter themselves.

Yu Kuohai made a hand seal as he channeled some type of cultivation art, and a series of golden patterns appeared over his body, allowing him to ward off the effects of the metal forcefield, but at the expense of rapidly accelerated immortal spiritual power expenditure.

"Have any of you ever seen such a formidable metal forcefield? It must be enhanced by some type of array. Go and track down the cores of the array and destroy them," Yu Kuohai ordered as he pointed at Han Li and a few others.

Han Li was also being affected by the metal forcefield, but given his physical constitution, he was barely feeling the strain at all. However, in order to fit in with everyone else, he was also hunched over while feigning an agonized expression.

"But Fellow Daoist Yu, I can barely even walk in this metal forcefield! It's not that I don't want to contribute, it's just that..."

Before Han Li had a chance to finish, he was cut off by Yu Kuohai, who snapped. "Shut up and go! If this array isn't deactivated, all of us are going to die here!"

Han Li feigned a resigned expression upon hearing this, then departed to explore the array.

Spiritual sense wasn't completely disabled within this metal forcefield, but it was severely hampered, and even with Han Li's spiritual sense, his sensory range had been cut down to no more than a thousand feet.

On top of that, his Infernal Devilish Eyes were also far less effective than usual, so he was still yet to catch a clear glimpse of the space that he was in.

After advancing for roughly a hundred meters, he spotted a thick, golden stone pillar up ahead with countless patterns engraved upon it, and it was constantly flashing with golden light while giving off bursts of peculiar energy fluctuations.

Could this be one of the cores of the array?

Han Li strode over to the pillar, then gently pressed his hand against it, and a burst of sharp power instantly shot up his arm.

His gaze traveled up along the stone pillar, and he discovered that the top section of the pillar was concealed within the golden light, but he could just barely make out a statue of a winged beast perched on top of the pillar.

Right as he was about to take a closer look, the winged beast revealed itself to be a living creature rather than a statue, and it came swooping down from above.

Han Li immediately shot back in retreat upon seeing this, and the winged beast just barely glanced past his body. The edges of its wings were extremely sharp, tearing large gashes into the surrounding space.

Han Li took advantage of this opportunity to take a closer look at the winged creature, upon which he discovered that it was a metal beast. It wasn't particularly large, but the metal-attribute law powers in its body were extremely formidable.

This metal beast's aura was even more powerful than that of the two tiger-like metal beasts that Han Li had previously encountered, and when still, it blended in perfectly with the surrounding environment, so even Han Li wasn't able to detect anything amiss about it.

After missing Han Li with its first attack, it swept its wings horizontally through the air, releasing a streak of radiant golden light that sliced through the air while sweeping toward Han Li.

In response, Han Li summoned an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword to ward off the streak of golden light, and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword began trembling and buzzing upon impact, while half of the golden lightning around it was eradicated.

[1]. Sweet Home Alabama starts playing.

[Back]

Chapter 1047: Clueless

Han Li made a hand seal upon seeing this, and bursts of golden lightning instantly erupted out of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, forming a blade of golden lightning that swept through the air.

The blade of lightning tore through the golden light in the air with ease, revealing an area of clarity in which Han Li's vision wasn't impeded.

The winged metal beast seemed to be rather wary of the oncoming lightning blade, and it flapped its wings and sprang up into the air.

Meanwhile, Han Li was peering through the opening in the golden light that had just been created by the blade of lightning, and he spotted no fewer than a hundred golden stone pillars in the distance, with a different metal beast perched on top of each one.

Right before Han Li's eyes, these metal beasts opened their eyes one after another before leaping down from their stone pillars and silently approaching Han Li like a pack of predators stalking their prey.

As the swordlight unleashed by Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword faded away, the surrounding golden light filled his field of view again, concealing the approaching metal beasts from him.

"What's going on?" Yu Kuohai yelled upon hearing the commotion up ahead, but he received no answer.

At this moment, a sense of foreboding had begun to well up in everyone's hearts, and they instinctively gathered a little closer to one another to form a more tightly knit group.

"There seems to be something in the golden light," Elder Yang said in a hesitant manner, and everyone felt even more uneasy upon hearing this.

Right at this moment, the sound of urgent footsteps suddenly rang out from up ahead, and everyone hurriedly raised their weapons, preparing for an attack.

All of a sudden, a figure burst out of the golden light, and Yu Kuohai was already prepared to strike, yet right as he was about to lash out, the figure yelled, "Stop! It's me, Shi Mu!"

Yu Kuohai hurriedly raised a hand to stop everyone, then asked, "How did it go, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

"There are metal beasts in here, Fellow Daoist Yu. Lots and lots of metal beasts," Han Li replied in a panicked manner.

"Metal beasts? That's it?"

Yu Kuohai was rather relieved to hear this.

Right as his voice trailed off, several severely maimed bodies flew through the air from different directions before tumbling down onto the ground nearby.

Han Li focused his gaze upon them to discover that they were the cultivators who had been sent out to scout the array.

"They're coming!" Han Li warned, and at the same time, he took a subtle glance at the Lan siblings.

The two of them had clearly already detected that something was amiss, and they had distanced themselves slightly from the rest of the group while standing with their backs facing each other.

Maybe this will force you two to show your hands, Han Li thought to himself.

Right at this moment, countless blades of golden light converged from all directions, forming a massive golden tornado around everyone.

Much of the golden light in the surrounding area was scattered, improving visibility for everyone.

As a result, everyone was horrified to discover that over a hundred giant, golden metal beasts had appeared around them, and all of them were giving off extremely formidable auras.

Yu Kuohai was left kicking himself upon seeing this.

During all of the years that he had spent in the Golden Origin Mountain Range, he had encountered all types of metal beasts and even ventured into a few metal force fields, but never had he seen such a formidable lineup of metal beasts before.

"Disciples of the Worry Not Pavilion, get into formation!" Pavilion Master Zhao yelled, and the Worry Not Pavilion disciples immediately heeded his call, gathering around him before each of them summoned a golden wheel, which they tossed up into the air.

Immediately thereafter, they began chanting an incantation, and the dozens of golden wheels began slowly revolving, forming a golden array that was constantly releasing proliferations rings of golden light.

"Let's work together!" Yu Kuohai hurriedly yelled upon seeing this.

There were far fewer Spirit Heaven Sect and Blazing Light City cultivators present compared with the Worry Not Pavilion, so if they were to form an array on their own, then it definitely wasn't going to be a particularly powerful one.

"We're using different cultivation arts, so I'm afraid we won't be able to work together cohesively. I suggest you and the cultivators of your Spirit Heaven Sect establish an array of your own, Fellow Daoist Yu," Pavilion Master Zhao said as a hint of derision flashed through his eyes.

Yu Kuohai gave him a resentful glare upon hearing this, then hurriedly turned to Elder Yang, and the cultivators of the Spirit Heaven Sect and Blazing Light City immediately sprang into action, creating an array of their own.

Even though they were working together, all they actually did was set up two separate arrays before arranging them together. After all, it simply wasn't possible for them to create a joint array without any advanced rehearsal.

"What are you standing there for, Fellow Daoist Shi? Hurry up and join us!" Yu Kuohai yelled.

Han Li turned to discover two light barriers above the cultivators from the two sects, one crimson and one azure, and a hint of sympathy appeared in his eyes as he dropped the act altogether.

"I even went out of my way to come back and inform you of the dangers ahead so that you could get away, but you really are a clueless bunch. What could you possibly hope to keep out with such a pathetic array?"

"What the hell are you saying, you bastard?" Yu Kuohai snapped in a furious voice.

"So be it. I can only wish you all the best of luck," Han Li said with a nonchalant smile, and right as his voice trailed off, a giant golden wolf sprang out of the surrounding pack of metal beasts before swiping its front paw through the air, sending it crashing down upon the array established by the Worry Not Pavilion cultivators.

"Bolster the array!" Pavilion Master Zhao yelled, and all of the Worry Not Pavilion cultivators immediately began injecting their immortal spiritual power into the array with all their might.

The array above them began to glow as radiantly as the sun, glowing even brighter than the surrounding metal forcefield.

The claws of the giant wolf struck the array with a sharp screeching sound, instantly tearing three huge gashes into the array.

The array was far from weak, but in the face of this metal beast, it may as well have been constructed from paper.

The golden wheels were all shattered into countless pieces, and a string of bloodcurdling howls rang out as most of the Worry Not Pavilion cultivators were torn to bits by the giant wolf's powerful claws in the blink of an eye.

A horrified look finally appeared on Yu Kuohai's face upon seeing this.

Even the Worry Not Pavilion's array stood no chance against these metal beasts, so their makeshift array most certainly wasn't going to be able to protect them.

"We have to split up and run!" Yu Kuohai yelled.

The cultivators of the Spirit Heaven Sect and Blazing Light City were already extremely on edge, and they immediately scattered and fled for their lives upon hearing this.

However, their attempts to escape only stirred all of the metal beasts up into a hunting frenzy, and they sprang into action all at once, pouncing on the fleeing cultivators.

The entire area instantly descended into complete chaos, with cries of agony and despair ringing out from all directions.

A layer of golden scales had appeared over Yu Kuohai's robe, and with the emergence of these scales, he was able to weave his way freely through the chaotic crowd like a fish in water, seemingly no longer affected by the metal forcefield at all.

If it weren't for the fact that the entire area was surrounded by metal beasts, he would've already been able to flee back to the main group outside at this point.

Elder Yang of Blazing Light City had changed into a fiery crimson robe, and he was darting through the crowd as a fiery dragon that was around ten feet in length.

Many of his allies were scorched by the flames burning over his body, but he held no regard for them as he evaded the attacks from the surrounding metal beasts while searching for an opportunity to get away.

Right at this moment, a golden eagle came swooping down from above, grabbing down at him with its sharp talons.

Elder Yang hurriedly sprang forward to just barely evade the eagle's talons, but as a result, began barreling headfirst at Han Li.

"Get out of my way!" Elder Yang yelled in a furious voice.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he turned to Elder Yang, then began swinging a hand in his direction in a slapping motion.

Elder Yang was even more furious upon seeing this, and he opened his mouth to release a plume of scorching flames that instantly inundated Han Li.

"What a pathetic fool," Elder Yang sneered, but right at this moment, a hand came swinging out of the flames up ahead before crashing heavily down onto his head with a loud slap.

Elder Yang immediately felt a burst of tremendous force crashing down upon him, scattering his consciousness for a moment, and by the time he returned to his senses, he had already fallen into the clutches of the golden eagle.

"No!" he roared in despair, right before his body was torn into three pieces by the golden falcon, and the pieces of his body fell out of the sky before being devoured by three separate metal beasts.

Yu Kuohai just so happened to witness this as he was frantically fleeing for his life, and he was momentarily rooted to the spot, following which a sinking sensation welled up in his heart.

On one hand, he was cursing Han Li for hiding his true power, while on the other hand, he was praying that Han Li wasn't going to come after him for vengeance.

Of course, Han Li could hardly care less about them, and he wouldn't have killed Elder Yang if the latter hadn't been so intent on rushing to his own demise.

At this moment, his gaze was focused on the Lan siblings.

Chapter 1048: True Appearance

At this moment, Lan Yan was holding a weapon that resembled a curved sickle with an extended shaft, and there were three glowing blue crystals embedded into the sickle's blade.

As for Lan Yuanzi, he was wielding a thin longsword that also had three blue crystals on its blade, and the sword was releasing bursts of rippling blue light as he swung it through the air.

The two of them were calmly opposing a pair of lion-like metal beasts, and Lan Yan smiled as she said, "These metal beasts are quite powerful, so I'm sure their beast cores must contain metal-attribute law powers. Let's kill some of them so we can harvest their beast cores."

"These metal beasts are nothing compared with the treasures in the Eon Pagoda, so there's no point in wasting time here. Instead, we should focus on finding a way out as soon as possible," Lan Yuanzi said with a shake of his head.

"You're right. It would be quite a pain having to kill all of these metal beasts anyway," Lan Yan agreed with a nod.

"Don't get complacent. These things possess a great deal of offensive prowess, so you could sustain injuries from them if you're not careful," Lan Yuanzi cautioned.

Lan Yan nodded in response, then sprang up into the air before pointing a finger forward, and a burst of blue light instantly erupted out of her fingertip, forming a blue light barrier.

A series of ring-shaped patterns appeared on the light barrier, giving off a formidable water-attribute law aura.

The metal beast that was pouncing at her crashed headfirst into the light barrier with a resounding boom, and the light barrier immediately began to ripple violently, but it managed to hold itself intact and keep the metal beast at bay.

At the same time, she swung her sickle through the air, releasing an arc of blue light that resembled a blue crescent moon.

A sharp screeching sound rang out as the blue light barrier was torn apart, following which the golden lion was sliced into two down the center by the arc of blue light.

Meanwhile, Lan Yuanzi was more direct and barbaric with his approach, making no effort to defend himself at all as he sprang forward and pierced the thin longsword in his hand directly at the other golden lion's glabella.

The heads of these metal beasts were incredibly resilient, yet Lan Yuanzi's sword was able to piece a huge hole into the golden lion's head with ease, much to the astonishment of the onlooking Yu Kuohai.

Only then did he come to realize that Shi Mu wasn't the only one that had been putting on an act of weakness. With that in mind, he promised himself there and then that he would never judge a book by its cover again.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly took a glance in his direction, and his heart instantly leaped up into his throat upon seeing this. Thankfully, Han Li's gaze only lingered on him for a moment before he looked away again.

Even so, Yu Kuohai was still feeling very uneasy, and he actively distanced himself from Han Li and the Lan siblings to flee in another direction, making it absolutely certain that he would stay out of their way.

In reality, Han Li didn't care about him at all, and the only reason why he had taken a glance in Yu Kuohai's direction was because he could sense an even more powerful metal beast currently approaching from that direction.

As he turned his gaze back to the Lan siblings, he was surprised to discover that they were nowhere to be seen.

Before he had a chance to search for them, the golden eagle that had just slain Elder Yang swooped down upon him from above.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he turned slightly to the side before throwing a punch upward.

As soon as the golden eagle's talons came into contact with Han Li's fist, its entire body instantly exploded amid a powerful eruption of starlight, and its remains were quickly devoured by a qilin-like metal beast.

Immediately thereafter, the golden qilin let loose a thunderous roar as a pair of golden wings sprouted on its back.

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this, and this golden qilin seemed to have been the metal beast that he had detected earlier.

The golden qilin rushed directly at Han Li while opening its mouth to release a ball of golden, molten fluid that came raining down upon him from above.

Han Li immediately summoned an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword before swinging it upward, and releasing a net of golden lightning that clashed against the molten fluid cascading down from above.

There seemed to be bursts of sharp energy within the molten fluid, and it was able to quickly tear the net of golden lightning apart.

However, the golden fluid had also been whittled down significantly by the golden lightning, and what little remained of it was torn to shreds by the sword qi from Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li sprang up into the air directly at the golden qilin, which flapped its wings with all its might in retaliation, conjuring up gusts of golden wind that swept through the air like a storm of sharp golden blades.

The path up ahead was sealed off by the gusts of golden wind, so Han Li sprang up further into the air, vaulting himself over the gusts of golden wind before throwing an almighty punch down upon the golden qilin's head.

A burst of tremendous power erupted out of Han Li's fist, causing the space below to compress upon itself in layers, following which his fist struck the golden qilin on the top of its head.

The qilin's legs instantly folded under the weight of Han Li's punch, sending it crashing to the ground.

Its head wasn't split open by Han Li's fist, but it was clearly very much disoriented.

Han Li landed on the top of its head, and a contemplative look appeared on his face, following which he pressed a finger against his own glabella before drawing it outward.

A translucent thread that was as thin as a strand of hair was pulled out of his glabella, and it swirled around his fingertip like a spirit snake.

Immediately thereafter, the translucent thread burrowed its way into the golden qilin's head at his behest, and its head instantly drooped down as if it had fallen asleep.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, then conjured up a huge door of silver light in front of the golden qilin.

"You'll make a decent guard dog," Han Li murmured to himself, then sprang back through the air, landing behind the golden qilin before giving it a kick on the backside to send it flying into the door of light.

After that, he closed his Flower Branch domain before turning to a certain direction.

A blue light barrier emerged from the golden light in that direction, and the Lan siblings made their way out from within.

"That's a domain treasure, is it not? No wonder you were able to completely loot such a massive part of the secret area. Having said that, don't you feel a little ashamed, stooping as low as to scrape up an entire plot of spirit farmland for yourself, Fellow Daoist Han?" Lan Yan said with an amused smile.

"When did you discover my true identity?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"You've been spying on us this entire time, Fellow Daoist Han. Did you think we wouldn't have noticed?" Lan Yuanzi chuckled.

Looking at the physical affection on display between the two, Han Li couldn't help but feel a little sick to the stomach as he asked, "Aren't you two supposed to be siblings?"

A furious look appeared on Lan Yan's face at the sight of Han Li's disgusted expression, and she snapped, "My brother and I are not related by blood! We were both orphans who were picked up by our master, so we both adopted our master's surname. Only a filthy scoundrel like you would think of something so putrid."

In contrast, Lan Yuanzi seemed to be completely unbothered.

"I couldn't care less about your relationship. I was hoping to avoid a battle against you two, but it looks like that's out of the question now," Han Li mused.

"A battle is still very much avoidable," Lan Yuanzi countered with a faint smile. "All you have to do is surrender yourselves to us, and we'll take you back to the Nine Origins Temple with us after we leave this secret area."

"Does everyone from your Nine Origins Temple like to make this same joke? The last person who said this to me was Dongfang Bai. Are you two familiar with him?" Han Li asked.

"How dare you!"

A furious look immediately appeared on Lan Yan's face as she prepared to pounce at Han Li, only to be stopped by Lan Yuanzi.

"Don't fall for his provocation. He was able to storm into the Immortal Palace and kill Dongfang Bai, so he's most definitely not to be taken lightly, even for us," Lan Yuanzi cautioned.

Lan Yan composed herself slightly upon hearing this, and she switched to a two-handed grip on her long-shaft sickle as she glowered intently at Han Li.

"Seeing as you insist doing things the hard way, the two of us will gladly oblige," Lan Yuanzi said in a serious manner as he gently swept his longsword through the air, conjuring up a spherical, blue light barrier that encompassed the entire surrounding area in a radius of several thousand feet.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this. He could sense that much of the metal-attribute spiritual qi in the air had suddenly faded away, and all of the surrounding metal beasts were also driven out by the spirit domain.

As for the cultivators of the Spirit Heaven Sect, Blazing Light City, and the Worry Not Pavilion, close to all of them were already dead at this point.

"This spirit domain of yours is quite interesting. It doesn't appear to harbor any offensive power, but it's able to drive back those metal beasts," Han Li mused in an intrigued manner.

Chapter 1049: Breaking the Ice

"Certain laws of interaction have always existed between the five elements. Metal enhanced water, so it's no surprise that my water-attribute spirit domain is bolstered in this metal forcefield. If those metal beasts had remained in my spirit domain, then I would've been able to absorb the metal-attribute spiritual qi in their bodies, so they'll naturally avoid my spirit domain like the plague," Lan Yuanzi explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

"I hold the environmental advantage here in this metal forcefield, so there's no way you can defeat me. Are you truly not going to consider surrendering yourself to us, Fellow Daoist Han?" Lan Yuanzi asked.

"If you were a Great Encompassment cultivator, perhaps you would be entitled to say something like this, but as you are now..."

Han Li's voice trailed off here as he took a step forward, using only the power of his own physical body to forge ahead without drawing upon any immortal spiritual power.

However, as soon as he attempted to step forward, he immediately felt as if he had crashed headfirst into a vast sea that was holding him back with all its might.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, and all of his profound acupoints lit up, releasing a burst of tremendous starpower that allowed him to force his way through the impeding water law powers up ahead.

"There's no way a High Zenith cultivator should possess such a formidable physical constitution!" Lan Yuanzi exclaimed.

"Let's see if he can take an Origin Water Slash from me!" Lan Yan harrumphed coldly.

She had already been suppressing her own fury for quite some time, and she launched herself at Han Li as a streak of blue light.

Unlike Han Li, she was completely unaffected by Lan Yuanzi's spirit domain, and she reached him in the blink of an eye.

A burst of formidable water law power fluctuations erupted out of her sickle, and it swelled to around twice its original size as it swept through the air.

"No! Get back!" Lan Yuanzi hurriedly yelled, but it was already too late as Han Li channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, significantly enhancing his own speed, allowing him to calmly evade her sweeping sickle before reaching out to make a grab for her throat.

Lan Yan was completely unable to resist as his hand closed around her throat, but instead of displaying any panic, she burst into laughter instead.

Han Li immediately tried to retract his hand, but it was already too late.

A bone-chilling sensation speared through his hand as a burst of blue light erupted out of Lan Yan's body, instantly washing over him to transform him into a blue ice statue, while Lan Yan herself also turned into a statue of ice.

Meanwhile, a burst of blue light appeared beside Lan Yuanzi before reforming her body.

"I know he's mastered the laws of time, Brother. I'm not that reckless," Lan Yan said with a wide smile.

"You really had me worried for a second there," Lan Yuanzi sighed.

"We've got him now, but you still need to completely seal him, Brother. My ice will only be able to keep him contained for a few minutes," Lan Yan said in an urgent voice as the smile on her face faded away.

As soon as her voice trailed off, a cold sneer rang out from nearby.

"A few minutes? You think far too highly of yourself, Fellow Daoist Lan."

Immediately thereafter, a dull thump rang out, and countless arcs of golden lightning erupted out of Han Li's body to shatter the ice around him.

"Impossible!" Lan Yan exclaimed with a stunned expression.

For the average High Zenith cultivator, their immortal spiritual power circulation would've completely ceased while encased in her ice, thereby rendering them unable to break free, and this applied even to peak-High Zenith cultivators.

However, with all of the profound acupoints that Han Li had opened, his physical strength and starpower were more than enough for him to break the ice, even without access to his immortal spiritual power.

As soon as he broke out of the ice, Han Li immediately released a golden spirit domain of his own, making it just large enough to fully encompass Lan Yuanzi's spirit domain.

Both of the Lan siblings' expressions changed slightly upon sensing the pervasive sluggishness within the time spirit domain.

"This man is far more difficult to deal with than we imagined. Only by using that technique will we have any chance at victory," Lan Yuanzi said with a grim expression, and Lan Yan nodded in response, then stowed her sickle away before snapping her fingers.

A spirit domain that was a slightly lighter shade of blue erupted out of her body, and a peculiar attractive force arose between her spirit domain and Lan Yuanzi's, fusing them together.

As soon as the two spirit domains came together, they immediately released a strange bone-chilling sensation, striking Han Li with a sense of asphyxiation, as if he were being crushed at the bottom of the sea.

At the same time, both Lan Yan and Lan Yuanzi had already vanished from the spot, replaced by a blue ice sculpture that was around a hundred feet tall. The statue had a gender-neutral appearance and bore some resemblance to both of the Lan siblings.

Right at this moment, four bursts of light rose up from the ground around Han Li, forming four blue ice sculptures that were identical to the original one.

Immediately thereafter, the five ice sculptures opened their mouths in unison, and waves of white glacial qi that were visible even to the naked eye converged toward Han Li from all directions.

Rays of light began to refract in the air, and a layer of white frost quickly began to take shape over Han Li's body.

His expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he swept a sleeve through the air to summon eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which released arcs of golden lightning that converged to form golden balls of lightning.

However, right as the balls of lightning were about to explode, a gust of glacial wind swept over the area, freezing Han Li and the eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords solid.

Even the balls of golden lightning had been encased within the ice, with every single arc of lightning still clearly visible.

To Han Li's surprise, he discovered that some glacial qi had even seeped into his consciousness, causing his spiritual sense to go a little numb.

"Brother, our combined spirit domain can trap him, but not for long. How are we going to take him back to the Nine Origins Temple?" one of the ice sculptures asked.

"It was never a requirement to take him back alive, our top priority is to recover the Heaven Controlling Vial. It's going to be extremely difficult to capture him, so let's kill him and take his soul back with us," another sculpture replied.

"Should we use the Profound Origin Iceslash Sword?" a third ice sculpture asked.

"Let's do it!" the remaining two ice sculptures answered in unison, immediately following which all five ice sculptures began making a string of hand seals.

A radiant blue array took shape above Han Li's head, and the tip of a blue ice sword emerged from within.

The surrounding air temperature instantly plummeted even further as a burst of terrifying pressure came crashing down upon Han Li from above.

This must be an immortal treasure of an extremely high caliber!

Judging from the fearsome aura emanating from the sword, Han Li could tell that even the average Great Encompassment cultivator wouldn't be able to withstand its power, so it was no wonder that the Lan siblings had to join forces to unleash it.

At the moment, the immortal spiritual power in his body had been completely frozen, and his starpower circulation had also become very sluggish. On top of that, his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had also been sealed in ice, so there was no way for him to free himself.

Meanwhile, a chaotic battle was still taking place in the surrounding area, and those outside the stone gate could only hear the commotion ringing out from within, but their vision remained impeded by the golden light inside.

"When should we go in?" Su Anqian asked through voice transmission.

"Let's keep waiting for now. There's clearly a battle of a very large scale going on inside, so if we were to go in now, it's very likely that we'll be swept up in it. Hence, I think we should wait until the battle concludes before we go in," Jin Liu replied.

Right at this moment, a burst of formidable glacial qi erupted out of the metal force field upon ahead.

Several Worry Not Pavilion cultivators were standing too close to the entrance, and they were instantly frozen solid. Before anyone had a chance to save them, they had already perished.

Everyone hurriedly retreated further from the stone gate in a fearful manner upon seeing this, while Su Anqian and Jin Liu exchanged an alarmed glance with each other.

"There's been no news from Fellow Daoist Yu and the others, even though they've already been in there for a very long time. Could it be that something's gone wrong, Fellow Daoist Jin?" Valley Master Fu of the Azure Lock Valley asked.

Before Jin Liu had a chance to reply, a resounding boom rang out from up ahead, following which a wave of scorching heat erupted through the air, forcing everyone back even further.

At this moment, Han Li was still encased in ice within the space beyond the stone gate, but there were silver flames swirling around his entire body, giving off an incredibly fearsome scorching aura.

A sharp cry then rang out as a silver fire raven with rainbow flames on its head sprang out of the silver flames, crashing directly into the Profound Origin Iceslash Sword that was descending from above.

Countless rays of glacial blue light rained down from the Profound Origin Iceslash Sword before clashing against the scorching flames with a resounding boom, raising a huge cloud of steam that filled the entire space.

"Is that... an Essence Fire Raven?" one of the ice sculptures asked.

"How could there be such a powerful Essence Fire Raven?" another ice sculpture exclaimed.

"That bastard, Dongfang Bai, didn't mention this at all!" a third ice sculpture cursed.

Chapter 1050: Search

The Essence Fire Raven let loose another loud cry as it spread its wings and ascended with all its might, forcing back all of the rays of blue light released by the Profound Origin Iceslash Sword, following which the sword itself was also forced back into the array of blue light above.

Even after forcing back the Profound Origin Iceslash Sword, the Essence Fire Raven still refused to relent, and countless silver fireballs erupted out of its body before striking the Lan siblings' combined spirit domain, causing it to tremble violently.

Before long, a series of cracks had appeared all over the spirit domain, and shortly thereafter, the five ice sculptures within the spirit domain exploded in unison.

Immediately thereafter, the entire spirit domain faded away, but the Lan siblings were also nowhere to be seen.

Even after freeing himself from the spirit domain, Han Li's limbs were still feeling a little numb from the cold, and he made a beckoning motion, upon which the Essence Fire Raven flew back to him before perching itself on his shoulder.

A burst of warmth instantly flowed through his entire body from his shoulder, and wisps of glacial qi that were visible even to the naked eye were forced out of his skin before fading away.

He swept his gaze over the surrounding area to discover that all of the metal beasts had disappeared, and all of the cultivators that had been sent into the area with him had met their demise.

Pavilion Master Zhao had been torn to shreds by a metal beast, while Yu Kuohai had been frozen to death by the eruption of glacial qi from earlier.

Han Li patted the Essence Fire Raven on his shoulder with a grim expression, and it vanished into his body, following which he began to make his way deeper into the golden space.

It had been confirmed that those two were indeed the Lan siblings, and his cover had already been blown, so he had to hunt them down and kill them. Otherwise, if they were allowed to return to the Heavenly Court, then he would truly be in a world of trouble.

......

Meanwhile, everyone outside the stone gate was waiting for further instructions.

The sounds of battle inside had already subsided, and after waiting for a while longer, Jin Liu finally declared, "Let's go in."

All of the other cultivators exchanged some wary glances with one another upon hearing this, but none of them made a move, clearly still feeling very apprehensive.

Jin Liu's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he urged, "It's been quiet in there for quite some time now, so the first group must've already taken care of the hazards up ahead. If we don't go in now, they'll claim all of the treasures inside!"

Hesitant looks appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this, but once again, no one was willing to make a move.

Jin Liu exchanged a glance with Su Anqian, and the two of them entered through the stone gate together.

Only then did everyone follow along.

Everyone's brows instantly furrowed slightly upon making their way into the metal forcefield, but their concern and annoyance quickly turned to shock and horror as they caught sight of all of the maimed and frozen bodies that littered the ground.

"What the hell happened here?" Valley Master Fu murmured to himself with a horrified expression.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he abruptly raised his head to cast his gaze toward the top of a nearby golden pillar.

A thunderous roar rang out as a panther-like metal beast pounced down upon him with incredible speed, and it was quickly joined by more metal beasts as another horrific slaughter commenced...

Meanwhile, Han Li had already arrived in front of another stone gate deep within the golden space.

The stone gate was slightly ajar, clearly indicating that the Lan siblings had already fled inside.

Han Li swept his spiritual sense over the surrounding area, then made his way through the stone gate as well.

Beyond the gate was a spacious hall that was completely empty with the exception of a winding stone staircase that led upward.

Han Li made his way to the top of the staircase, arriving before a dark red door of light. It seemed to be a spatial teleportation door, but it was unclear what destination it led to.

He attempted to examine it with his spiritual sense, only to discover that his spiritual sense was completely unable to pass through the door of light.

After a brief hesitation, he made his way through the door of light, arriving in a crimson world.

It was a boundless crimson desert with a dark red sky and red clouds above, and the entire surrounding area was filled with scorching heat.

Behind him was a disembodied stone gate that was standing in the middle of nowhere, and at its center was a rippling black light barrier.

Standing beside the gate was a stone plaque that had the character for "two" engraved upon it in majestic, free-flowing text.

Han Li reflexively swept his spiritual sense across his surroundings, upon which he discovered that even though his spiritual sense was still restricted, he was able to release it further than he could on the first level.

Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan were still nowhere to be seen, but he could sense their residual auras in the air, indicating that they had most definitely been here before.

After ensuring that nothing was amiss, Han Li set off in pursuit of the Lan siblings as a streak of golden light.

As soon as he rose up into the air, he immediately felt the effects of a special restriction in the surrounding space. It was giving off time law power fluctuations, and it cut his speed down by roughly half.

This restriction is rather similar to my time spirit domain, except my time spirit domain doesn't have any impact on spiritual sense, Han Li thought to himself, then quickly put the thought out of his mind as he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability.

Seeing as the restriction in this place was related to time law powers, his Reversal True Axis ability should be effective.

Sure enough, as soon as he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, his speed was instantly significantly enhanced, almost returning to its normal level, and it didn't take long before Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan appeared in his field of view.

Their clothes were in tatters and charred in many places, as if they had been scorched by flames, and their auras were also far weaker than before.

On top of that, it seemed that their speed had also been greatly hampered by the restriction in this place.

The gap between Han Li and the Lan siblings was rapidly shrinking, and a stunned look appeared on Lan Yuanzi's face upon sensing Han Li's presence.

"He's coming!"

"We have to do it now!" Lan Yan said in an urgent manner, and Lan Yuanzi displayed no hesitation, latching onto Lan Yan's hand as the two of them began to chant an incantation in unison.

A burst of law powers surged out of each of their bodies before fusing together, forming a projection of a giant blue bird that was several thousand feet in size around them.

The bird projection flapped its wings vigorously, thereby greatly enhancing their speed, but they were still quite a bit slower than Han Li, and before long, the gap between them had dwindled to less than ten kilometers.

"How is he this fast?" Lan Yan exclaimed as she turned to Lan Yuanzi with a slightly panicked expression.

Lan Yuanzi gritted his teeth as a decisive look appeared in his eyes, following which he gave Lan Yan a firm push, sending her flying into the distance as he yelled, "I'll hold him back, you get out of here!"

"Brother!" Lan Yan exclaimed as she immediately stabilized herself before turning around to fly back to his side.

"Get away, you idiot! Don't worry about me, I can look after myself!" Lan Yuanzi roared in a furious voice, following which he raised his hands to summon a small white flag with a blue wyrm embroidered upon it, as well as a blue bowl with fiery blue light flashing inside.

The two items flew out of his grasp, and the white flag instantly transformed into a blue and white wyrm that was over a thousand feet in length before swooping down upon Han Li while releasing an almighty breath.

Its breath was interspersed with chunks of white ice crystals that crashed against one another to produce a thunderous rumbling noise, and it was clear that anything caught within the breath would be instantly torn to shreds.

Meanwhile, the bowl was revolving in mid-air as it released a burst of glacial blue flames, which descended upon Han Li as a massive screen of blue fire, freezing all of the space in its wake.

Both the wyrm's breath and the glacial flames spanned an enormous area, instantly turning the scorching hot temperatures freezing cold.

Lan Yan stared after Lan Yuanzi with tears swimming in her eyes, but ultimately, she still did as she was told, fleeing into the distance.

In the face of the oncoming attacks, Han Li stopped in his tracks, then swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of green light that swelled drastically in size before forming a pair of massive green hands that plunged into the wyrm's breath and glacial blue flames in a flash.

However, the wyrm's breath and the glacial flames abruptly vanished into thin air around a hundred feet in front of Han Li.

Further up ahead, the white flag and the blue bowl had been caught in the clutches of the giant green hands, and both were struggling with all their might to free themselves, but to no avail.

Furthermore, Lan Yuanzi was nowhere to be seen.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he made a beckoning motion, and the burst of green light vanished up his sleeve alongside the pair of immortal treasures, following which he set off in pursuit of Lan Yan, who was still yet to fully disappear into the distance.

Right at this moment, the space up ahead suddenly began to quiver and rumble violently.

Immediately thereafter, numerous blue spatial rifts appeared up ahead, releasing countless rays of blue light that inundated Han Li's entire body like a flurry of turbulent waves, stopping him cold in his tracks.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and before he had a chance to do anything, all of the surrounding blue light converged rapidly around him to form a ball of blue light that was several thousand feet in size.

Bursts of law power fluctuations were churning incessantly within the ball of blue light, compressing toward Han Li from all directions, and even with his immense physical constitution, he was momentarily rendered immobile.

However, after just a few seconds, he was able to acclimate himself to the surrounding pressure, and after scouring his surroundings momentarily with his Infernal Devilish Eyes, a translucent chain abruptly shot out of his glabella before vanishing into the nearby space in a certain direction.

A figure was dragged out of thin air, bound by the translucent chain, and it was none other than Lan Yuanzi.

At this moment, there was blinding blue light flashing over his body, giving off incredibly formidable law power fluctuations.

Chapter 1051: Exposed?

A look of realization flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

As it turned out, Lan Yuanzi was using some type of secret technique to set alight the law power within his body, and that was how he was able to release such a formidable burst of law powers all of a sudden.

As these thoughts were running through Han Li's mind, he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which began revolving rapidly, releasing countless golden ripples that instantly filled the surrounding area in a radius of over ten thousand feet.

The surrounding ball of blue light immediately fell completely still. Lan Yuanzi was trying to free himself from Han Li's spiritual sense chain, but the golden ripples were too fast, and they washed over him before he could free himself, rendering him completely immobilized.

Meanwhile, Han Li flew out of the ball of blue light with ease, arriving in front of Lan Yuanzi before pressing his fingers into Lan Yuanzi's head, yet right as he was about to crush his skull, he suddenly stopped what he was doing.

He turned to look in the direction that Lan Yan had just fled in, then looked back at Lan Yuanzi, and an image of his little sister surfaced in his mind.

He heaved a forlorn sigh as the killing intent drained out of his body, and he pressed a hand against Lan Yuanzi's lower abdomen, releasing five burst of time law powers that formed five-elemental seal in Lan Yuanzi's dantian, sealing away all of his immortal spiritual power.

The sealing secret technique enclosed in the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra could be used on both himself and others.

After that, Han Li removed Lan Yuanzi's storage ring from his finger, then scoured his spiritual sense over Lan Yuanzi's entire body to ensure that he wasn't hiding anything, following which he withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis, and all of the nearby golden ripples immediately faded away.

The ball of blue light conjured up by Lan Yuanzi also quickly vanished, and his body began to plummet out of the sky, but Han Li caught him before slowly descending to the ground.

At this point, Lan Yan had already fled out of his spiritual sensory range, and some of her residual aura was still left behind, but the chances of catching up to her were rather slim.

Even though this place didn't seem to be all that dangerous, it struck him with a sense of foreboding for some reason, so he didn't forge ahead recklessly.

"What a powerful sealing technique. No wonder you've been able to evade the Heavenly Court for so long. I've been defeated fair and square," Lan Yuanzi grinned.

"You're quite a brave man to still be able to smile at a time like this," Han Li remarked.

"I am completely at your mercy right now, and I doubt that you'll be more inclined to spare me if I act all miserable, so I may as well keep up a good mood in what could quite possibly be my final moments," Lan Yuanzi replied in a nonchalant manner.

A hint of approval toward Lan Yuanzi welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this, but his expression remained unchanged as he said in a cold voice, "I have a few questions for you. If you don't want me to search your soul, then answer them truthfully."

"Go ahead," Lan Yuanzi replied in a very cooperative manner.

"Why were you and your sister sent to the Golden Origin Immortal Region? To capture me?" Han Li asked.

"We did indeed come here to capture you under orders from Immortal Lord Miao Fa, and at the same time, we were tasked with recovering a treasure from you that originally belonged to our Nine Origins Temple. I've heard that it's a time-attribute immortal treasure in the form of a small, green vial," Lan Yuanzi replied without any hesitation, and Han Li's heart immediately jolted slightly upon hearing this.

The Heaven Controlling Vial had always been his deepest secret, yet it seemed like he wasn't going to be able to keep this secret hidden any longer.

"How does the Nine Origins Temple know that I'm in possession of this vial?" Han Li asked.

"I'm not sure about the exact details, but I heard that they extrapolated that from a Creation Crystal that came from you," Lan Yuanzi replied.

A look of realization instantly appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this, following which he continued, "Did the Vast Golden Immortal Palace send anyone else after me aside from you and your sister?"

"No, we were the only two sent by Immortal Lord Miao Fa. Our combined powers are comparable to those of a Great Encompassment cultivator, so we had thought that we would be able to easily defeat you, but we've truly been humbled," Lan Yuanzi replied with a wry smile.

Han Li was slightly reassured upon hearing this, and he asked a few more questions, all of which Lan Yuanzi answered without any hesitation.

After asking all of the questions that he wanted to ask, Han Li stood in silence as he cast his gaze into the distance, seemingly contemplating something.

Lan Yuanzi stood silently off the side, making no attempt to interrupt him.

All of a sudden, Han Li raised a hand before tapping a finger against Lan Yuanzi's glabella, and a burst of translucent light shot out of his fingertip, knocking Lan Yuanzi unconscious before he had a chance to react.

After that, Han Li turned to the space beside him and asked, "Did he tell any lies just now, Weeping Soul?"

"No. I detected no abnormalities in his soul fluctuations while he was answering your questions, so he was telling the truth," Weeping Soul replied, and Han Li nodded in response.

Even though he had developed a fondness for Lan Yuanzi for his character, if he had been caught lying just now, then Han Li would've killed him and searched his soul without any hesitation.

"Wouldn't it have been much easier to just let me search his soul? Why did you go to the trouble of interrogating him?" Weeping Soul asked as she emerged from the door of silver light.

"It's clear that he and Lan Yan are extremely close, so I'm sure she'll come back for him, and once that happens, I'll be able to use him to my advantage," Han Li replied as he tossed the unconscious Lan Yuanzi into the Flower Branch domain.

"Even the two of them combined were no match for you. Now that Lan Yan's on her own, she doesn't pose any threat at all! If she dares to come back, then we'll capture her as well," Weeping Soul said as she raised her delicate fist.

"Don't get complacent. It's true that Lan Yan poses no threat to me, but right now, Qi Mozi is also in this immortal manor, and both of them are from the Heavenly Court, so we could be in some trouble if they join forces with each other," Han Li said.

"That's true," Weeping Soul replied with a contemplative nod, while Han Li began to inspect the surrounding area.

He had pursued the Lan siblings deep into the crimson desert, and he was currently in an area that was riddled with massive sand dunes that resembled short mountains.

Furthermore, there were countless thorny red plants growing on the sand dunes, and there were also some living creatures here, like lizards and scorpions, but none of them were demon beasts.

Weeping Soul also began to scour the surrounding area, and all of a sudden, a hint of surprise appeared in her eyes.

"Have you detected something?" Han Li asked.

Given Weeping Soul's special physical constitution, she was prone to making some interesting discoveries at times.

"There's a very strong aura of death and resentment here, so make sure to proceed with caution from here onward, Master," Weeping Soul replied with a solemn expression.

"I've also been getting a sense of foreboding from this place. The stone plaque next to the gate that we passed through earlier had the number 'two' written on it. Could it be that this is the second level of the Eon Pagoda?" Han Li speculated.

"That's very likely. From the outside, it doesn't appear as if the Eon Pagoda is segment into levels, but my observation tells me that the pagoda is, in fact, split up into seven levels. I wonder why Immortal Lord Tai Sui constructed this pagoda," Weeping Soul mused.

"In any case, let's do some scouting for now," Han Li said as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, smoothing out the signs of battle in the nearby area before flying away in a certain direction.

As for Weeping Soul, he decided to have her remain by his side instead of sending her back into the Flower Branch domain.

Close to half a day flew by in a flash.

The crimson desert was astonishingly massive, and Han Li was still flying through it with no end in sight.

All of a sudden, Weeping Soul called out to him before descending in a certain direction, and Han Li immediately followed along.

The two of them quickly landed in front of a sand dune, and Weeping Soul swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of black light that sliced the sand dune into two, revealing the skeletal remains of what appeared to have been a giant lizard..

The skeleton was several dozen feet in size, and it was riddled with cracks from wind erosion, looking as if it could shatter at any moment.

Han Li had already discovered this skeleton with his spiritual sense, but he hadn't noticed anything amiss about it, so he asked, "Is there something special about this skeleton?"

"How many years do you think this skeleton has been here for, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"The lizards here aren't demon beasts, but they still possess bodies far more resilient than those of normal lizards. The fact that the skeleton has been eroded to such an extent tells me that it has to have already been here for at least several hundred years," Han Li analyzed.

"This lizard has only been dead for no more than a decade," Weeping Soul said with a shake of her head.

"What? How do you know that?" Han Li asked with an incredulous expression.

"All living beings possess souls, and these souls will dissipate once something is dead, but some residual soul power will cling to their remains and only completely fade once enough time has passed. The soul power clinging to this skeleton is still quite abundant, so from that, I can determine that it died quite recently," Weeping Soul explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with an intrigued expression.

Even with his tremendous spiritual sense, he was unable to detect the soul power clinging to this skeleton, so it was clear that Weeping Soul had far superior sensitivity to souls than he did.

"In that case, how has its body already been eroded to this extent?" Han Li asked.

Chapter 1052: Running Away First

"I don't know the answer to that, I just felt like this skeleton was rather strange, so I thought I'd have you take a look at it," Weeping Soul replied.

Han Li nodded in response as he observed the skeleton in silence.

Right at this moment, he suddenly turned to a certain direction, then swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light as he said, "Su Anqian and the others are coming, so stay in the Flower Branch domain for now."

Weeping Soul gave an affirmative response before flying into the door of silver light, following which Han Li sped away in a certain direction.

Moments later, several dozen streaks of light of different colors appeared on the distant horizon, traveling in a slightly different direction from Han Li.

Han Li immediately began approaching the streaks of light, and they also changed directions to meet him.

Before long, the two parties met, and Han Li found himself face to face with Su Anqian, Jin Liu, and around thirty to forty other people.

Valley Master Fu and all of the High Zenith cultivators were still among them, but all of them were carrying injuries and looking rather worse for wear.

"You're Fellow Daoist Shi, right? You were with Fellow Daoist Yu, weren't you? How are you still alive? Where's everyone else?" Su Anqian asked.

"We encountered many powerful metal beasts beyond the stone gate, and everyone was killed by those metal beasts. I was fortunate enough to escape with several other fellow daoists, but we've all been split up since then. Thank heavens I managed to run into all of you," Han Li replied as he feigned an expression of lingering fear.

Everyone had already guessed that this would be the case, but grim looks still appeared on their faces upon hearing this.

A hint of derision flashed through Jin Liu's eyes at the sight of Han Li's fearful display, and he sneered, "You really are lucky, aren't you?"

Han Li pretended to not have heard the mockery in Jin Liu's voice as he gave an earnest nod and replied, "Indeed, Fellow Daoist, I've always had very good luck. Otherwise, I would've surely perished to those metal beasts as well."

Jin Liu was momentarily rendered speechless by Han Li's clueless response, following which he asked, "There must've been treasures inside that golden area, right, Fellow Daoist Shi? What were they, and who's in possession of them right now?"

A look of greed flashed through his eyes as he raised this question.

"There were no treasures at all in that area. On top of that, as soon as we went in, we were attacked by the metal beasts, and I was only just barely able to escape by the skin of my teeth," Han Li replied.

"Is that right?" Jin Liu asked as he raised an eyebrow, making his suspicion abundantly clear.

"Did we not agree that everyone gets to keep the treasures that they secure from that area? Why are you interrogating Fellow Daoist Shi all of a sudden?" Valley Master Fu suddenly interjected.

"Please don't misunderstand, Valley Master Fu, I have no intention of taking his treasures from him. Instead, I just wanted to make a deal with him. If there was nothing inside, then I suppose there's no deal to be made," Jin Liu replied.

"Any deals can wait until after we've all left the Eon Pagoda. Fellow Daoist Shi, you arrived on this second level ahead of all of us, have you discovered anything?" Su Anqian asked.

"I'm afraid not. I've been stumbling around in here for quite some time already, but there seems to be nothing but sand here," Han Li replied.

Su Anqian's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"In that case, let's keep forging ahead."

No one raised any objections to this, and the group continued to fly onward.

Close to another day flew by in the blink of an eye.

The monotonous desert scenery down below was finally beginning to display some changes, and some large rocks had begun to come into view, along with some rocky hills.

Han Li was trailing along at the very back of the group, and along the way, he spotted more and more of those strange, eroded skeletons, instilling within him a sense of growing unease.

Su Anqian and the others had also noticed the skeletons on the ground below, but they paid them no heed, merely regarding them as ordinary sets of remains.

All of a sudden, a burst of rumbling rang out in the sky up ahead, and initially, it was very quiet, but it then rapidly swelled to a deafening crescendo.

"What's going on?"

Everyone stopped in their tracks before examining the area up ahead with their spiritual sense, upon which all of them instantly turned deathly pale.

As it turned out, there was an enormous dark red cloud up ahead in the distance, and it was currently rapidly approaching them.

The crimson cloud was formed by an unfathomable number of tiny, dark red insects, all of which had red flames burning over their bodies.

Those are Fire Age Fireflies!

Upon catching sight of the crimson cloud, Han Li was immediately able to identify its constituents as Fire Age Fireflies, which he had previously encountered in the ruins of the True Mantra Sect.

At the same time, it occurred to him that all of the skeletal remains that they had encountered up to this point had to have belonged to creatures that had been killed by Fire Age Fireflies, thereby explaining the unreasonably advanced degree of erosion.

With that in mind, Han Li immediately flew away into the distance as a streak of golden light.

Back in the True Mantra Sect, Chi Rong had only released fewer than ten thousand Fire Age Fireflies, and that had already been a huge pain to deal with, so there was no way that they would be able to oppose such an enormous swarm of them.

The other people in the group didn't recognize the Fire Age Fireflies, but it was clear that this vast swarm of insects was not something that they could hope to oppose, so all of them immediately fled in a panic as well.

Han Li had been trailing along at the very back of the group this entire time, and he was also the first to run at the first sign of danger, putting on a cowardly display that earned him much derision from everyone else.

The swarm of Fire Age Fireflies seemed to have also detected the presence of Han Li's group, and they began screeching in excitement as they sped through the air like sharks that had caught a whiff of blood.

The swarm of insects was traveling at an alarming speed, seemingly completely unaffected by the time-attribute restriction in this place, and even though everyone was fleeing as quickly as they could, the gap between them was still slowly closing.

It didn't take long for the swarm of insects to catch up to the group of itinerant Golden Immortals flying at the very back of the group, and one of them, a crimson-faced man abruptly stopped in his tracks as he roared, "What's there to be scared of? It's just a few little bugs!"

At the same time, a burst of crimson flames emerged over his body, then rapidly spread outward, forming a sea of crimson fire that was several thousand feet in size.

Bursts of intense heat surged out of the sea of flames, causing the nearby space to tremble and warp, as if it were about to be set alight.

The sea of fire then rose up to form a giant fiery wave that was over a thousand feet tall at the man's behest, and it swept toward the swarm of insects, swallowing up thousands of Fire Age Fireflies in the blink of an eye.

The Fire Age Fireflies that had been swept up by the crimson flames were immediately thrown into a state of disarray, tumbling end over end as if they had lost control of their own bodies.

An elated look appeared on the man's face upon seeing this, but it only lingered for a moment before vanishing without a trace.

After briefly stumbling around within the crimson flames, the Fire Age Fireflies spread their wings to stabilize themselves, then continued flying toward the red-faced man, seemingly completely unharmed by his fire.

A look of alarm and fury appeared on the man's face upon seeing this, and he let loose a thunderous roar as he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a fiery red scroll that gave off tremendous fire law power fluctuations, clearly indicating that it was an immortal treasure of a very high caliber.

He cast a rapid string of incantation seals into the scroll, which immediately unfurled to form a radiant fiery barrier around him.

In the next instant, countless Fire Age Fireflies swarmed over the red-faced man and the fiery crimson barrier around him, forming an enormous cocoon.

One Fire Age Firefly flew into the fiery barrier after another, rapidly whittling it down at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye, and in the blink of an eye, the fiery barrier had been completely snuffed out, reverting it back to a crimson scroll.

However, the scroll currently resembled an uncared for artifact from countless years past, and it was riddled with creases and tears and completely devoid of spiritual nature.

Countless Fire Age Fireflies converged around the red-faced man like an enormous swarm of mosquitoes, burrowing their way through the protective spiritual light around his body with ease.

The man screamed in horror and agony as he struggled with all his might, frantically trying to swat away the Fire Age Fireflies, but to no avail.

He began to age rapidly right before everyone's eyes, and in no more than the blink of an eye, he had been reduced to a severely eroded skeleton, while his clothes had also been eroded into nothingness.

Following his demise, the swarm of insects lost all interest in him, allowing his remains to fall to the ground while they set off in pursuit of other targets.

It didn't take long before the other Golden Immortals at the very back of the group were also caught by the swarm of insects, and a string of bloodcurdling howls rang out, only to then instantly trail off into silence.

All of a sudden, a look of recognition appeared in Jin Liu's eyes, and he yelled in a horrified manner, "I remember what those things are now, they're Fire Age Fireflies! They're born with time law powers in their bodies, and they can release flames of time that can incinerate the lifespans of other living beings! How are there so many of them here?!"

Everyone else's expressions changed drastically upon hearing this, and they hurriedly unleashed some secret techniques to enhance their own speed, ensuring that they were able to at least maintain the same speed as the swarm of insects behind them.

"Fire Age Fireflies are extremely sensitive to living, physical bodies, so conceal your physical auras and fly to the side to avoid directly facing the swarm!" Su Anqian yelled.

Everyone hurriedly did as they were told, concealing their physical auras before flying collectively flying away to the left.

Han Li also heeded this advice, channeling his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique to conceal his own physical aura.

As a result, the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies was instantly thrown into a state of directionless disarray, as if they had suddenly lost track of everyone.

This naturally came as a huge relief, but with the horrific fates suffered by the red-faced man and the others still fresh in everyone's minds, no one dared to let their guards down as they continued to flee with all their might.

Chapter 1053: Indecision

Only after flying for close to half a day did everyone finally escape from the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies, and they descended onto a nearby hill to regroup.

Even though everyone had concealed their own physical auras under Su Anqian's instructions, some people were still caught by the Fire Age Fireflies during this time, and everyone else could only look on helplessly as those unfortunate individuals were incinerated by the flames of time.

Up to this point, the crisis had been avoided, but everyone still had looks of lingering fear on their faces from the close call.

At this moment, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on his own, while Su Anqian was standing on an elevated vantage point, looking back at the distant horizon.

The vast swarm of Fire Age Fireflies was slowly flying away in that direction, and only upon seeing this did she allow herself a sigh of relief.

"Thank heavens Celestial Maiden Su is familiar with the properties of these Fire Age Fireflies. Otherwise, this place may have become everyone's final resting place," Valley Master Fu said as he turned to Su Anqian with a grateful expression.

"You're far too kind, Valley Master Fu," Su Anqian replied in an indifferent manner.

"There really is peril at every turn in this pagoda. I shudder to imagine what else could possibly be waiting for us up ahead," Valley Master Fu said with a wry smile.

"Come to think of it, Fellow Daoist Shi, you were the first one to run away after spotting the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies. Could it be that you've already encountered those things before?" Su Anqian suddenly asked as she turned to Han Li.

Everyone else also turned to Han Li with accusatory looks of derision upon hearing this.

"If you knew, then why didn't you warn us, Fellow Daoist Shi? Were you trying to get all of us killed?" Jin Liu asked in a cold voice as he glowered intently at Han Li, and looks of animosity appeared on everyone else's faces as well upon hearing this.

"No, no, I only recognize those Fire Age Fireflies because I encountered them in another secret area, and I almost lost my life on that occasion," Han Li hurriedly explained as he feigned a panicked expression.

"Is that right?" Jin Liu harrumphed coldly.

"Fellow Daoist Shi just so happened to be at the very back of the group when we ran into those Fire Age Fireflies, so I suppose it makes sense that he was the first to run," Valley Master Fu said, and everyone immediately lost interest in Han Li upon hearing this.

Su Anqian's gaze lingered on Han Li for a moment longer, following which she also directed her attention elsewhere.

Han Li didn't care about how he was regarded anyway, so it suited him just fine to have everyone look down on him.

He could’ve easily taken advantage of the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies to split off from the group and go off on his own, but he chose not to do so for now. After all, he knew very little about this pagoda, so his plan was to remain with the group for some time before deciding on his next course of action.

Right at this moment, a hunch-backed elderly man stepped forward. He was an early-High Zenith cultivator and the master of a small sect, and he proposed, "Alright, let's discuss how we're going to proceed from here. Are we going to continue onward?"

At this point, only a handful of High Zenith cultivators remained in the group.

The Heavenly Water Sect originally had four High Zenith cultivators, one of whom had perished to the metal beasts on the first level, so there were only three left.

The rest of the High Zenith cultivators in the group consisted of Valley Master Gu, the Ink Fragrance Pavilion Master, the hunch-backed elderly man who had just spoken, and a brawny man with a coarse beard, amounting to a total of only seven High Zenith cultivators.

The Ink Fragrance Pavilion Master was a young woman in a pink dress by the name of Yan Ying, and there was an uneasy look on her face as she said, "Up to this point, the Eon Pagoda has been completely devoid of treasures. We've encountered nothing but peril in this place, and at this point, I think our numbers have been whittled down far too much for us to safely continue onward."

Many of the other people in the group nodded in agreement upon hearing this, including the hunch-backed elderly man.

"So are you suggesting that we turn around here?" Su Anqian asked.

"Celestial Maiden Su, the fact of the matter is that this place is far too dangerous. We were already almost completely wiped out by those metal beasts, and there's no telling what more perils beside these Fire Age Fireflies could lie beyond this point. With our powers, it would be too risky to continue," the hunch-backed elderly man said, and Su Anqian fell silent upon hearing this.

"There's no need to be so pessimistic. This is Immortal Lord Tai Sui's former cave abode, so there will surely be some treasures in here, and perhaps they're just up ahead. Those Fire Age Fireflies may be troublesome to deal with, but they're also quite easy to fool, so as long as we remain vigilant and don't end up being surrounded by them, we'll be fine.

“It wasn't easy making it this far, will you really be content with leaving without reaping any rewards?" Jin Liu asked.

At the moment, morale was at an all-time low, so if Yan Ying and the hunch-backed elderly man were to back out now, then the entire group would fall apart.

Both Yan Ying and the hunch-backed elderly man were still harboring some hopes for the Eon Pagoda, so hesitant looks immediately appeared on their faces after hearing what Jin Liu had to say.

"If we encounter those insects again, then follow my instructions on how to proceed. I believe I have a way to help us shake them off," Su Anqian said.

Yan Ying and the hunch-backed elderly man exchanged a glance with each other upon hearing this, following which the former nodded and said, "Alright, in that case, let's go in a little further before we make a decision."

"Risk and reward have always come hand in hand. This pagoda has already been sealed for countless years, and I'm sure it won't disappoint us," Jin Liu said.

"In that case, let's keep going," Su Anqian decided, and the group soon set off again.

Han Li naturally had no objections to this. If everyone had chosen to retreat here, then his plan would've been to continue onward on his own.

Hence, he rose to his feet and continued to trail along at the very back of the group.

Everyone was very disdainful of Han Li for this, but no one said anything. However, they had all decided in their hearts that if any treasures were discovered in this pagoda, then they would do everything within reason to ensure that none of it went to Han Li.

Given what had happened earlier, everyone was proceeding with a lot more caution, so they were traveling far slower than before.

After close to an hour of uneventful travel, Han Li suddenly took a subtle glance to the right, but didn't say anything.

Moments later, Su Anqian suddenly stopped in her tracks at the very front of the group, then yelled, "The Fire Age Fireflies are back! Come with me!"

After that, she immediately began flying toward the left.

Han Li was rather taken aback by the fact that she was able to detect the Fire Age Fireflies so quickly, and it told him that her spiritual sense wasn't inferior to his own by much.

Everyone hurriedly concealed their own physical auras before following along behind her, and before long, the entire group had descended onto the ground below, hiding behind a rocky hill.

Su Anqian swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a small yellow flag, which transformed into a large cloud of yellow mist that encompassed everyone, following which the cloud of mist vanished amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

The group had only just concealed itself behind the hill when the sound of buzzing rang out in the distant sky, following which a swarm of Fire Age Fireflies that was even larger than the previous one flew rapidly over the horizon.

Everyone looked on with tense and fearful expressions as the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies flew past, but thankfully, Su Anqian's immortal treasure was able to successfully keep them hidden, and the swarm quickly flew away into the distance, much to everyone's relief.

Meanwhile, Han Li was observing the departing insect swarm with a contemplative look on his face.

This swarm and the previous one struck him with the feeling that they seemed to be on patrol.

Once the swarm had completely vanished into the distance, everyone immediately set off again.

From that point onward, they encountered several more swarms of Fire Age Fireflies, but the crisis was successfully averted each time.

After advancing for close to another day, the terrain up ahead changed once again, and a long stretch of crimson mountains appeared up ahead.

There were countless volcanoes of different sizes dotted throughout the mountains, ranging from hundreds of feet to hundreds of thousands of feet tall.

Most of the volcanoes were still active, spewing pillars of molten lava up into the air amid bursts of thunderous rumbling.

There was a dense blanket of fiery, dark red clouds in the sky, and an acrid, sulfurous odor hanging in the air. The temperatures here were several times hotter than before, and there was a vast abundance of fire-attribute spiritual qi in the entire area.

Everyone immediately picked up the pace upon seeing this, and before long, an itinerant Golden Immortal's eyes lit up as he descended upon a volcanic crater to pick up a golden rock that was giving off fiery golden light, which Han Li was able to identify as a Golden Flame Holy Stone.

Shortly thereafter, someone else found a piece of crimson jade called Profound Flame Spirit Jade, and that was quickly followed by more treasures being discovered.

......

There was a large number of precious fire-attribute materials littered throughout this area, and everyone was eager to reap the rewards.

Han Li had no interest in these materials, but he also collected some in order to blend in with everyone else.

This was the first haul of treasures that everyone had secured in the Eon Pagoda, and it provided a much-needed boost in morale. Under Su Anqian's leadership, everyone quickly arrived deep in the mountainous area.

"Look out, there are more Fire Age Fireflies coming!" Su Anqian suddenly called out.

At this point, everyone had become much more accustomed to this occurrence, and they were much calmer than before as they gathered together in an orderly fashion to conceal themselves.

Before long, an enormous swarm of Fire Age Fireflies that was over ten times the size of the initial one that they had encountered came flying in from afar, resembling a vast cloud that obscured the entire sky.

Even under the concealment of Su Anqian's immortal treasure, everyone still couldn't help but feel a little fearful.

Chapter 1054: Parting Ways

The swarm of insects was rapidly approaching, and all of a sudden, it stopped above everyone before circling around in the air above.

Everyone concealed within the cloud of yellow mist was extremely alarmed by this, and even Han Li couldn't help but feel a little apprehensive.

Thankfully, after circling around in the air for a while, the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies suddenly split up into several smaller swarms that scattered in different directions.

Some molten lava erupted out of the volcanoes into the swarms of fireflies, causing them to screech with joy, and they quickly vanished into the distance, much to everyone's relief.

"Looks like this is where the Fire Age Fireflies reside. That makes sense. Even though their flames of time contain time law powers, they're technically a type of fire-attribute spirit insect, so they enjoy environments like this one," Jin Liu said.

"Let's go in a little further," Su Anqian said before leading the way onward, and everyone quickly followed along.

After flying for close to an hour, two giant mountains that extended all the way up into the clouds appeared up ahead, between which was a valley that was completely filled with a downright absurd number of Fire Age Fireflies, easily dwarfing all of the swarms that everyone had encountered prior to this.

The mountain faces on either side of the valley was riddled with countless small holes, making it resemble a beehive, and countless Fire Age Fireflies were constantly flying in and out of these holes.

Deep in the valley was a dark cave that was filled with a type of special energy that kept out spiritual sense, but bursts of formidable time law power fluctuations that were interspersed with hints of spatial fluctuations could be detected coming from inside.

At this moment, Han Li's group was hiding behind a hill far away from the valley.

"It looks like there are quite a few treasures that contain time law powers in that cave. On top of that, these spatial fluctuations are very similar to those from the spatial door from earlier, so it seems like the entrance to the third level of the pagoda is also in there," Su Anqian said in an excited manner, and Han Li was also looking at the valley in the distance with an eager expression.

Even though he had reached a very lofty cultivation base, he was rather lacking in time law threads. Otherwise, he wouldn't have been at such a disadvantage in his battle against Qi Mozi. If he could obtain some treasures that contained time law powers and refine them into time law threads, then that would undoubtedly significantly enhance his powers.

However, everyone else was clearly rather hesitant to proceed at the sight of such a vast number of Fire Age Fireflies.

Su Anqian could see the hesitance in everyone's eyes, and she declared, "Rest assured, everyone, I have a way to deal with these Fire Age Fireflies."

After a brief silence, Yan Ying shook her head as she said, "Perhaps you have a way to sneak past all of these Fire Age Fireflies, but my Ink Fragrance Pavilion is only a small sect with limited power, and this is far too risky an endeavor for us to undertake, so please forgive me, but the cultivators of our Ink Fragrance Pavilion won't be accompanying you any further, Celestial Maiden Su."

This volcanic area was extremely abundant with natural treasures, and much of it was still unexplored, so as opposed to venturing into the lair of the Fire Age Fireflies, it was much more appealing for Yan Ying to go searching elsewhere.

Those fire-attribute spirit materials naturally weren't as precious as whatever was inside the cave, but they were also comparatively much safer to acquire.

Su Anqian and Jin Liu's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but before they had a chance to say anything, the hunch-backed elderly man suddenly strode over to Yan Ying's side and said, "This is where we part ways as well, Celestial Maiden Su. I wish you the best of luck."

Before long, other people began to join them, and in the end, around two dozen people had joined Yan Ying and the hunch-backed elderly man, leaving only the three Heavenly Water Sect cultivators, Han Li, Valley Master Fu, the man with the coarse beard, and seven or eight itinerant Golden Immortals.

"You're all just going to turn back at the first sign of difficulty? How disappointing," Jin Liu sneered.

Yan Ying and the others paid no heed to the mocking tone in Jin Liu's as they turned to depart, while Han Li observed from the side.

Even though this was a slightly cowardly display, it was not an unwise decision.

There was an astounding number of Fire Age Fireflies up ahead, so venturing into the valley was going to be an extremely risky endeavor. If it wasn't for the fact that Han Li had mastered the laws of time, thereby granting him the confidence to ensure self-preservation, he would've also chosen to turn back here.

All of a sudden, Su Anqian appeared in Yan Ying's path.

"Hold on a second, fellow daoists."

"What is the meaning of this, Celestial Maiden Su? Are you trying to keep us here by force?" Yan Ying asked as her brows furrowed slightly.

"Please don't misunderstand, fellow daoists. All of you are free to leave, but prior to that, I would like to beg a favor from all of you," Su Anqian said.

"How can we help you?" Yan Ying asked as her expression eased slightly.

"As you can all see, there's a huge number of Fire Age Fireflies, so it's going to be very difficult to sneak into the cave. Hence, I would like all of you to lure some of the Fire Age Fireflies here away with you as you leave," Su Anqian replied.

"You want us to lure away Fire Age Fireflies for you? Is that supposed to be a joke, Celestial Maiden Su?" the hunch-backed elderly man sneered.

"Rest assured, everyone, I have several Flying Illusion Talismans that can enhance the user's speed by at least 30% for a short time while also granting an aura concealment effect, so you'll definitely be able to get away from the Fire Age Fireflies," Su Anqian said as she flipped a hand over to produce five azure talismans that gave off formidable wind law power fluctuations.

The hunch-backed elderly man raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, but remained silent.

"Of course, I'm not asking all of you to do this for me free of charge. These immortal treasures are all prized items from my collection, and anyone willing to help me can take one," Su Anqian continued as she swept a sleeve through the air to release five or six water-attribute immortal treasures, all of which were giving off tremendous law power fluctuations.

A hint of elation flashed through the hunch-backed elderly man's eyes upon seeing this, and he immediately claimed a Flying Illusion Talisman and a blue bowl immortal treasure as he said, "In that case, I would be happy to help, Celestial Maiden Su. What exactly would you like us to do?"

Yan Ying and the others were also rather tempted by this offer.

"I have five Blood Cloud Jewels here that can be detonated to produce massive blood clouds. Fire Age Fireflies are extremely sensitive to blood, so if you strategically detonate these jewels, then you should be able to lure away most of the Fire Age Fireflies in the valley. I'm going to require the assistance of five fellow daoists for this," Su Anqian replied as she summoned five egg-sized crimson jewels, all of which were flashing with translucent crimson light.

An intrigued look appeared in Han Li's eyes at the sight of the jewels.

They contained a vast abundance of bloodline power, as well as a hint of blood law powers, making them similar to blood lightning.

"Looks like you have this all thought out, Celestial Maiden Su. You can count on me," the hunch-backed elderly man promised as he drew one of the Blood Cloud Jewels into his grasp, displaying a completely different attitude from before.

As soon as those immortal treasures were revealed, the hunch-backed elderly man had immediately begun sucking up to Su Anqian, and that had attracted him much derision from his companions.

After a brief hesitation, Yan Ying stepped forward and claimed a Blood Cloud Jewel, a Flying Illusion Talisman, and an immortal treasure, quickly followed by three itinerant Golden Immortals who were evidently quite confident in their own speed.

Meanwhile, everyone else in the group had already departed, leaving behind only the five people who had agreed to help Su Anqian.

"I'll be counting on all of you then," Su Anqian said to the five of them as they turned to depart.

"Allow me to lead by example, Celestial Maiden Su," the hunch-backed elderly man said as he flew away into the distance, and several seconds later, a resounding explosion rang out near the valley up ahead, following which an enormous, viscous blood cloud emerged.

The Fire Age Fireflies in the valley were immediately swept up into a frenzy, and within mere moments, the entire blood cloud had been devoured.

The hunch-backed elderly man appeared near the valley, then flew away as a streak of azure light, displaying far superior speed to before.

Some of the Fire Age Fireflies near the valley immediately set off in pursuit, and with that, roughly 10% of the Fire Age Fireflies in the valley had been diverted away.

An elated look appeared on Su Anqian's face upon seeing this, and she immediately turned to the other four.

Yan Ying didn't say anything as she rose up into the air and replicated what the hunch-backed elderly man had just done, luring away yet another large swarm of Fire Age Fireflies.

"Next! Hurry!" Su Anqian hurriedly urged.

The five people who had agreed to help Su Anqian had to go one after the other in quick succession. Otherwise, if the Fire Age Fireflies up ahead were to double back around, then all of the prior efforts would've been for nought.

"I'll be going on ahead, everyone!"

An itinerant Golden Immortal flew away as a ball of white light, quickly luring away a third swarm of Fire Age Fireflies, and the remaining two Golden Immortals immediately followed suit as well.

In the wake of their departure, the number of Fire Age Fireflies in the valley had been reduced by more than half.

"Now!" Su Anqian yelled as she summoned that yellow flag once again, conjuring up a yellow cloud around everyone, and the cloud vanished into the ground before rapidly approaching the valley.

Chapter 1055: Each Man for Himself

It didn't take long before everyone arrived in front of the valley, and that was where they drew to a halt.

There were even more Fire Age Fireflies nesting beneath the valley than on the surface, so they couldn't advance any further beyond this point.

"I'm very grateful that all of you have chosen to stay, but this is as far as I can take all of you. From this point onward, all of you will have to fend for yourselves," Su Anqian said as she stowed her yellow flag away.

All those who had chosen to stay were confident in their ability to deal with the Fire Age Fireflies on their own, so they calmly accepted this arrangement.

"Good luck, everyone."

The three Heavenly Water Sect cultivators began to chant an incantation together, and they transformed into three blue shadows that flew out of the ground before flying rapidly into the valley.

Valley Master Fu flipped a hand over to produce an azure talisman that he adhered to his own body, and countless azure runes instantly appeared around him, following which his body turned semi-transparent as he flew out behind the Heavenly Water Sect trio.

Meanwhile, a thick layer of yellow stone armor appeared over the body of the bearded man, and as soon as he was encased in this suit of armor, his aura completely faded away, making him resemble an inanimate stone statue.

Instead of flying up to the surface, he continued to advance into the valley while remaining underground.

The remaining seven or eight itinerant Golden Immortals seemed to be a group of acquaintances, and they formed a circle together, following which a golden-haired young man swept a sleeve through the air to release a golden wooden plaque.

The plaque was over a hundred feet in size, and it was radiating bright golden light that gave off bursts of time law power fluctuations.

All of the Golden Immortals placed their hands onto the wooden plaque, and the golden light radiating from it instantly swelled up to encompass them all.

The plaque then began to revolve rapidly on the spot, and all of a sudden, it vanished into the thin air along with the group of Golden Immortals, then transformed into a golden shadow that flew deeper into the valley.

That plaque was crafted from Divine Sun Wood!

Divine Sun Wood came from the Divine Sun Tree, which contained time law powers just like the Twin Birth Tree, and they were extremely rare, so Han Li certainly wasn't expecting to see such a thing here.

Following everyone's departure, Han Li also promptly set off, trailing along behind the group of itinerant Golden Immortals as an indistinct golden shadow.

Even though everyone had concealed their own auras, there were so many Fire Age Fireflies in the valley that it was inevitable for them to run into some.

Those Fire Age Fireflies were instantly alerted to their presence and began swarming them from all directions.

These Fire Age Fireflies were truly extremely difficult to deal with, and in particular, their flames of time were able to rapidly wear down any defenses that were raised to try and keep them at bay.

Before long, Han Li also found himself swarmed by countless Fire Age Fireflies, and the protective spiritual light around him was rapidly fading away.

Right at this moment, he raised both hands to release countless arcs of golden lightning that formed a dense net of golden lightning around him.

Bursts of formidable lightning law power fluctuations erupted out of the net, causing the nearby space to tremble violently.

However, the lightning didn't have much effect on the Fire Age Fireflies, and the net of golden lightning quickly began to thin out from the ravages of the flames of time.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and more golden lightning erupted out of his hands to bolster the net of lightning around him.

As more and more lightning continued to pour out of the palms of his hands, he also incorporated a hint of time law powers into the golden lightning, and as a result, the net of golden lightning became much more resistant to the flames of time.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this, and instead of trying to force back the nearby Fire Age Fireflies, he simply flew deeper into the valley with the Fire Age Fireflies continuing to cling to him.

Everyone else was also doing the same, carrying large balls of Fire Age Fireflies as they flew deeper into the valley, and it didn't take long before they arrived in front of the dark cave.

At this point, each person was surrounded by a dense cocoon of Fire Age Fireflies that was over a hundred feet in size, and their speed was greatly hampered as a result.

Flames of time were converging from all directions, and the immortal spiritual power expenditure required to ward off the flames of time was enormous, but thankfully, they had already reached the cave.

Han Li let loose a low roar as he thrust both palms forward, and four radiant, golden lightning dragons suddenly erupted out of the golden lightning around his body.

The lightning dragons weren't particularly large, but they were all giving off far more formidable lightning law power fluctuations than the net of golden lightning, and they had also been injected with time law powers.

The four lightning dragons struck the cocoon of Fire Age Fireflies around Han Li with a resounding boom, blowing them apart amid a violent explosion of golden lightning, while Han Li flew out of the masses of scattered Fire Age Fireflies and into the cave.

The walls of the cave were riddled with countless small holes, and more Fire Age Fireflies were flying out of them before swarming him from all directions, but there were far fewer Fire Age Fireflies in here than outside, and he was able to keep them at bay with relative ease.

He had channeled his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique and time law powers to conceal his own aura, so he had been attacked by the least number of Fire Age Fireflies out of everyone, and that was why he had been able to enter the cave first.

However, instead of advancing further into the cave on his own, he stopped in his tracks before looking outside.

A glacial aura erupted forth from outside the cave, and all of the Fire Age Fireflies around the Heavenly Water Sect trio were encased in blue ice before dropping to the ground.

The blue ice was giving off astonishing glacial qi and law power fluctuations, and even the flames of time released by the Fire Age Fireflies had been frozen solid.

However, these Fire Age Fireflies hadn't perished, and the blue ice around them was being melted away by their flames of time, but at a very slow rate.

The three Heavenly Water Sect cultivators took advantage of this opportunity to fly into the cave, and a surprised look appeared on Su Anqian's face at the sight of Han Li.

"How did you get in here so quickly, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

Jin Liu and the other Heavenly Water Sect cultivator, a handsome young man, were both also very surprised to see Han Li in the cave before them.

However, they had no time to wait for a response from Han Li as they were forced to contend with the Fire Age Fireflies that had swarmed out of the holes that dotted the walls of the cave.

At the same time, another cocoon of Fire Age Fireflies bulged violently over a thousand feet away from the entrance of the cave, then exploded as a rapidly revolving azure tornado emerged, forcing back all of the nearby Fire Age Fireflies.

The tornado resembled a living creature that made a beeline straight for the cave, and Valley Master Fu flew out of the tornado before rushing into the cave.

Immediately thereafter, a rift appeared in another cocoon of Fire Age Fireflies beside him, and a burst of piercing golden light erupted out from within before also flying into the cave, containing the group of itinerant Golden Immortals.

They possessed the lowliest cultivation bases out of everyone, and at this moment, their complexions were already deathly pale from excessive immortal spiritual power expenditure.

As soon as they flew into the cave, a burst of blue light flashed over its entrance, and the cave was completely sealed shut by a thick layer of blue ice.

At this moment, there was a fist-sized blue bead hovering above Su Anqian's head, giving off astonishing glacial qi and law power fluctuations.

The Fire Age Fireflies outside were furious to see Han Li and the others in the cave, and they screeched loudly as they blasted forth plumes of flames of time, while countless Fire Age Fireflies flew through the air collectively like a flying battering ram before crashing repeatedly into the blue ice barrier.

The blue ice barrier was trembling violently while rapidly melting away, and it looked as if it could shatter at any moment.

Su Anqian gritted her teeth as she made a hand seal upon seeing this, and the blue bead above her head immediately flew into the ice barrier in a flash.

A layer of translucent blue light appeared over the ice barrier, instantly stabilizing it, but the flames of time were simply too much to ward off, and the ice was still rapidly melting away.

A concerned look appeared on Su Anqian's face upon seeing this, but there was nothing more that she could do.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly appeared in front of the blue ice barrier, then pressed a palm against it, releasing a burst of radiant golden light into the ice.

A layer of golden light instantly appeared over the ice barrier's surface, and it immediately became far less susceptible to the effects of the flames of time.

"You're using time law powers!" Su Anqian exclaimed upon seeing this, and everyone else also turned to Han Li with incredulous expressions.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but he heaved a resigned internal sigh.

He didn't want to expose his own powers, but the top priority at the moment was to keep out the Fire Age Fireflies, so he had no choice in the matter.

Of course, he wasn't going to explain to anyone how he had mastered the laws of time or how he had managed to enter the cave before everyone else.

Chapter 1056: Firefly Nests

Right at this moment, a yellow figure sprang out of the ground, and it was the bearded man who had been traveling underground this entire time.

His stone armor was riddled with countless holes, but he remained unscathed. However, he was panting heavily, and it was clear that this had not been an easy journey for him.

Su Anqian took a long glance at Han Li, then declared, "The ice wall won't be able to keep out those Fire Age Fireflies for long, so we need to go deeper into the cave right away!"

Everyone hurriedly did as they were told, making their way deeper into the cave behind her, and Han Li did the same while observing the Fire Age Fireflies outside with a contemplative look in his eyes.

There had to be a reason why the Fire Age Fireflies outside had suddenly become so aggressive and agitated, it was just a pity that he didn't know enough about these creatures to guess at the reason why.

The cave was very dark, severely limiting visibility, but with the threat of the army of Fire Age Fireflies looming behind them, no one dared to delay as they forged ahead in silence.

Su Anqian and Han Li were leading the way, warding off the occasional small swarms of Fire Age Fireflies that emerged around them, and they didn't dare to travel too quickly.

Thankfully, the deeper they went into the cave, the fewer holes there were on the walls, resulting in fewer and fewer Fire Age Fireflies in the surrounding area.

Before long, everyone arrived in a massive cavern.

All of the Fire Age Fireflies that were pursuing them suddenly stopped here, and not a single one dared to enter the cavern, much to everyone's befuddlement and relief.

Han Li took a glance at the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies outside the cave, then began to inspect his surroundings.

The cave was tens of thousands of feet in size, and one half of it was a crimson lava lake that was bubbling incessantly, releasing waves of scorching heat through the air.

The molten lava in the lake illuminated the entire cave a bright crimson color.

Above the lava lake was a red platform that was connected to another path, beyond which was another dark space that had faint specks of dark red light gleaming within.

The other half of the cave was a vacant area that was riddled with sharp, crimson stone pillars that resembled a forest of stone bamboo shoots.

Everyone's attention was immediately drawn to those stone bamboo shoots as there were three dark red hives that were several dozen feet tall hanging from the three largest stone bamboo shoots, and all of them were giving off a fiery glow and bursts of time law power fluctuations.

The three bursts of time law power fluctuations were all extremely vast, but they weren't condensed at all, instead swirling around in the cave in a haphazard fashion.

The lava in the lake rippled in the face of the three bursts of time law power fluctuations, while the entire space was also buzzing in a rhythmic manner.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly at the sight of the three hives.

If he wasn't mistaken, then those hives were most likely where all of the Fire Age Fireflies had been born. It seemed that the Fire Age Fireflies outside were restricted from entering this place, perhaps regarding it as some type of sacred area.

The area appeared to be quite safe and peaceful, but it definitely wasn't going to be completely unguarded.

Having already been here for countless years, the three hives had transformed into a type of extremely rare time-attribute spirit material.

While Han Li was examining the three hives, everyone else was also doing the same with greed in their eyes, but no one dared to make any rash moves.

However, it didn't take long before someone gave in to the temptation, and three figures shot forward at once, pouncing at the three hives in unison.

Two of them were from the group of itinerant Golden Immortals, namely a gray-haired young man and a black-robed young woman, and they were joined by the bearded man.

"Fellow Daoist Qi, Fellow Daoist Lu, don't be reckless!" the golden-haired young man exclaimed, but it was already too late.

The gray-haired young man and the black-robed young man each flew over to a hive before releasing a burst of light to envelop the hives and hoist them upward.

Meanwhile, the bearded man descended onto the ground close to two hundred feet away from the third hive before stomping a foot down onto the ground.

A burst of yellow light flashed over the ground, following which a crimson stone giant that was over a hundred feet tall emerged from the earth before grabbing onto the hive.

To their surprise, they were able to hoist the three hives upward without any difficulty.

Looks of surprise and elation appeared on their faces as they prepared to stow the hives away, but right at this moment, the hives began to glow with radiant crimson light, and the time law power fluctuations permeating throughout the entire cave abruptly converged around them.

In the blink of an eye, a dark red vortex of light took shape around the three hives, encompassing the trio within it.

The three of them were already prepared for this, but before they could do anything, their movements suddenly became extremely slow, as if they were moving through quicksand.

From the perspective of Han Li and the others, it appeared as if the three of them were moving in slow motion within the dark red vortex.

Right at this moment, a millstone-sized outline suddenly appeared on a previously unremarkable-looking spot on the ceiling above.

Alarmed looks appeared in the eyes of Han Li and the others as they discovered that the millstone-sized object was a giant Fire Age Firefly that was identical in bodily structure to the ones outside, except this one had some flame patterns on its exoskeleton.

Prior to this, the giant firefly seemed to have completely fused as one with this place, allowing it to escape everyone's detection.

The giant firefly opened its mouth, and three streaks of crimson fire shot out from within, hurtling toward the trio at an astonishing speed.

The gray-haired young man and the black-robed young woman didn't even have a chance to react before they were set alight by the crimson flames, and their bodies were reduced to ashes in the blink of an eye.

The bearded man was far more powerful than those two, and he was able to conjure up a yellow spirit domain that was around five feet in diameter, allowing him to dart back in retreat, although he was still significantly slowed down by the surrounding time law powers.

As a result, he was unable to completely evade the streak of fire shooting at him, and his left arm was pierced through.

A ball of crimson fire appeared over his arm, instantly reducing half of the arm to ashes.

The crimson flames continued to rapidly spread, threatening to spread to the rest of his body along his arm, and his expression changed drastically upon seeing this as he continued to rush back in retreat while swinging his other hand down upon his own shoulder in a chopping motion.

However, his movements were still extremely sluggish, and it was clear that he wasn't going to be able to amputate his own arm in time.

Right at this moment, a golden flying sword flashed through the air, slicing off the rest of the bearded man's left arm cleanly at the shoulder.

As soon as the arm was amputated, it was immediately devoured by crimson flames and incinerated into ashes.

Meanwhile, Han Li slowly withdrew his finger from several thousand feet away.

A relieved look appeared on the bearded man's face as the yellow light emanating from his body brightened even further, and his speed was drastically enhanced, allowing him to instantly fly out of the dark red vortex.

He gave Han Li a grateful nod, then promptly devoured some pills, and it didn't take long before a new arm began to regrow to replace the amputated one.

The giant firefly turned to Han Li with a furious screech, then crashed down from the ceiling of the cave to land on the stone giant that had been summoned by the bearded man.

With a sweep of its front legs, several crescent-shaped blades of crimson light were released, all of which were giving off formidable time law power fluctuations, and the stone giant was instantly sliced into pieces and reduced to a large pile of rubble, while the three hives fell back to their original spots.

The giant firefly was glowering intently at Han Li while perched atop the remains of the stone giant, and Su Anqian's eyes narrowed slightly as she yelled, "That appears to be a Fire Age Firefly Queen. It can freely wield time law powers, and it's countless times more powerful than the average Fire Age Fireflies!"

The Fire Age Firefly Queen instantly turned its gaze to Su Anqian, as if it could understand what she was saying, and it launched itself at her as a rapid crimson shadow.

At the same time, it swept its two front legs through the air, releasing two crescent-shaped streaks of red light that hurtled toward Su Anqian and Han Li.

The two streaks of light were extraordinarily fast, reaching their two targets in the blink of an eye.

Han Li immediately vanished from the spot before reappearing over a thousand feet away in the blink of an eye, leaving the Fire Age Firefly Queen momentarily stunned.

Su Anqian didn't possess the speed to match Han Li, and she was only able to fly back in retreat while sweeping a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of rippling blue light that formed a rapidly revolving blue vortex in front of her.

The streak of crimson light was momentarily stopped in its tracks by the blue vortex, but was then able to instantly slice through the vortex before continuing onward.

However, the blue vortex had managed to somewhat divert the streak of crimson light away from its original trajectory, and it glanced right past Su Anqian before slicing into the ground, creating an immeasurably deep rift.

Everyone's expressions changed drastically upon seeing this, and they all frantically rushed back in retreat to distance themselves from the Fire Age Firefly Queen.

"Everyone, attack at once!" Su Anqian yelled.

With the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies waiting outside the cave, retreat was no longer an option, so everyone immediately heeded Su Anqian's call, launching a barrage of attacks upon the Fire Age Firefly Queen.

Chapter 1057: No Retreat

Han Li had summoned twelve blue flying daggers that were racing through the air while giving off a formidable glacial aura.

The flying daggers were threatening to freeze the very space around them as they hurtled directly toward the Fire Age Firefly Queen.

He had found this set of twelve flying daggers from Dongfang Bai's storage tool, and they were quite formidable, so he had decided to keep them.

A mocking sneer flashed through the Fire Age Firefly Queen's eyes as a vast expanse of flames of time erupted out of its body, instantly forming a sea of crimson flames around itself.

Everyone hurriedly attempted to withdraw their immortal treasures upon seeing this, but it was already too late.

As soon as all of the immortal treasures plunged into the sea of crimson fire, everyone's spiritual connections with those immortal treasures were instantly severed.

Su Anqian and Jin Liu exchanged a glance with each other, and it was clear that both of them were contemplating a retreat.

Those three hives were extremely valuable objects, but they couldn't benefit from the hives in their cultivation, so even if they could obtain them, they would only be able to sell those hives at a later date.

Even if they could defeat this Fire Age Firefly Queen, it was clearly going to have to come at a huge cost, perhaps even losing their lives in the process, and that was not a wise course of action.

Everyone else was thinking the same thing, and only Han Li and the golden-haired young man in possession of the Divine Sun Wooden plaque were determined to stay.

However, right at this moment, the sea of crimson fire suddenly shrank down rapidly to the size of a house, then flew away in a certain direction.

Upon seeing the direction that the crimson fireball was traveling toward, Han Li immediately realized what the Fire Age Firefly Queen was attempting to do, but he made no effort to stop it.

Everyone else was feeling rather perplexed, and the people standing in the path of the fireball hurriedly took evasive measures, only for the fireball to fly right past them before landing on the entrance of the passageway above the lava lake.

"It's trying to seal the passageway!" Su Anqian yelled in an alarmed manner, and sure enough, the crimson fireball had transformed into a fiery barrier that sealed the entrance of the passageway.

The Fire Age Firefly Queen turned to everyone with a mocking sneer in its eyes, much like a sadistic hunter cornering its prey, and looks of despair instantly appeared on some people's faces upon seeing this.

"You think you can take us on all at once? What a joke! Fellow daoists, don't tell me that all of you are scared of a little bug!" the bearded man roared as he stomped a foot heavily down onto the ground, and a yellow spirit domain instantly erupted out of his body to encompass the entire cave.

A burst of tremendous gravitational force acted upon the Fire Age Firefly Queen within the spirit domain, causing it to sink to its haunches.

"As long as we combine our powers, this thing is no match for us!" Jin Liu yelled as he also released a blue spirit domain to encompass the Fire Age Firefly Queen.

The flames of time around the Fire Age Firefly Queen instantly began to ripple slightly, and it was unclear what effect Jin Liu's spirit domain had upon it.

Everyone else also released their spirit domains upon seeing this, and in the blink of an eye, the Fire Age Firefly Queen was enshrouded within around a dozen spirit domains.

A furious look appeared in its eyes as it launched itself through the air, racing toward the bearded man as a red shadow.

It was still extraordinarily fast, but its speed had been greatly hampered by the multitude of spirit domains acting upon it, and the bearded man was able to keep his distance from it as he made a grabbing motion with both hands.

The ground in the cave abruptly split open, and countless loose rocks flew out from within before rapidly forming a cage of earth around the Fire Age Firefly Queen.

Immediately thereafter, several immortal treasures flew through the gaps in the cage to strike the Fire Age Firefly Queen.

A string of loud clangs rang out, and to everyone's shock and dismay, the immortal treasures merely bounced off the Fire Age Firefly Queen's body without being able to leave even a single mark behind.

Right at this moment, a blue paper crane that was around the size of a human head appeared in front of the cage, and it flew inside before pecking down onto the Fire Age Firefly Queen's body.

Meanwhile, Su Anqian was making a strange hand seal while chanting an incantation, and one blue paper crane flew out after another before revolving around her.

A dull thump rang out as a hole was pecked into the Fire Age Firefly Queen's body, and blood came spurting out.

The Fire Age Firefly Queen let loose a furious screech as a layer of crimson light appeared over its exoskeleton, while its body swelled slightly in size.

It swept its front legs through the air, and several crescent-shaped streaks of light that were around twice the size of the previous ones erupted forth in all directions, slicing the surrounding cage of earth apart with ease.

After freeing itself from the cage, the Fire Age Firefly Queen immediately launched itself at Su Anqian, displaying far superior speed even compared to its peak speed from earlier, as if it were suddenly no longer affected by the surrounding spirit domains.

Su Anqian hurriedly shot back in retreat upon seeing this, and at the same time, the blue paper cranes circling around her pounced at the Fire Age Firefly Queen in unison.

However, the blue paper cranes were simply far too slow, and the Fire Age Firefly Queen was able ot fly past them with ease, appearing in front of Su Anqian in the blink of an eye before preparing to lash out with its front legs.

Right at this moment, a golden fist projection emerged out of thin air beside the Fire Age Firefly Queen amid a burst of spatial fluctuations, and it sent the Fire Age Firefly Queen tumbling away through the air upon contact.

Meanwhile, Han Li silently withdrew his fist from nearby.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Shi," Su Anqian said to Han Li with a slightly pale complexion while summoning her blue paper cranes back to herself.

After stabilizing itself, the Fire Age Firefly Queen turned to Han Li with a furious expression, then launched itself at him as a crimson shadow.

However, it then suddenly let loose a furious screech before veering off its original trajectory, flying toward the three hives instead.

As it turned out, the golden-haired young man and another itinerant Golden Immortal had snuck over the hives to try and claim them while the Fire Age Firefly Queen was occupied by Han Li and the others.

Their expressions changed drastically at the sight of the rapidly approaching Fire Age Firefly Queen, and they immediately shot back in retreat, but the Fire Age Firefly Queen seemed to have been completely infuriated by their sneaky maneuver.

Its entire exoskeleton instantly turned bright red, and the flames of time around it also became far darker in color as it accelerated even further, reaching the two men in the blink of an eye before sweeping its front legs through the air like lightning.

Two streaks of crimson light flashed through the air, and the other itinerant Golden Immortal was instantly sliced into two from head to toe, with his nascent soul also destroyed on the spot.

The golden-haired young man raised his wooden plaque to protect himself, and it was also sliced into two.

A pained look appeared on his face upon seeing this, but he had no time to grieve over his ruined treasure as he hurriedly sprang back in retreat to avoid the same fate as his companion, but a large gash was still sliced into his chest, causing him to stumble in his retreat.

The Fire Age Firefly Queen opened its mouth to release a burst of crimson flames, which instantly caught up to the golden-haired young man and reduced him to ashes in the blink of an eye.

Right at this moment, a ball of radiant blue light appeared above the Fire Age Firefly Queen, and the ball of light descended upon it right after it killed the pair of Golden Immortals.

Three thick chains shot out of the blue light to bind the Fire Age Firefly Queen, and even though all three chains were blue, they were giving off completely different law powers that worked together seamlessly to render the Fire Age Firefly Queen completely immobile.

The three Heavenly Water Sect cultivators were standing in a triangular formation in the distance, and each of them was holding onto the end of one of the blue chains.

The Fire Age Firefly Queen let loose a furious screech, and the flames of time around it reared up to scorch the three chains.

Before long, the chains had been severely eroded, but they were constantly being injected with bursts of law powers from the surrounding blue spirit domain, allowing them to remain intact despite the ravages of the flames of time.

Keeping the Fire Age Firefly Queen restrained was no easy feat for the three Heavenly Water Sect cultivators, and Su Anqian's arms were trembling incessantly as she yelled, "We can't keep this up for long, so all of you need to kill this thing now!"

Everyone else hurriedly began unleashing a barrage of attacks upon the Fire Age Firefly Queen, and a hint of panic flashed through its eyes as it let loose a loud screech, upon which all of the Fire Age Fireflies outside the cave immediately rushed in, as if they had just been given permission to do so.

However, right at this moment, Han Li appeared at the entrance of the cave before sweeping his sleeve through the air to release a streak of blue light.

It was a blue jade slab, which rapidly expanded to form a blue stone gate that sealed the entrance tightly shut.

This was an immortal treasure refined from Cerulean Crystalline Jade, and he had acquired it from Dongfang Bai's storage tool.

The stone gate immediately began trembling violently in the face of the collective assault unleashed by the Fire Age Fireflies outside, and Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this.

He immediately pressed his hands against the stone slab, and a layer of golden light appeared over its surface.

Even so, the stone slab was still trembling incessantly, and the Fire Age Fireflies outside would immediately swarm into the cave if he were to release the stone slab for even a split second.

Chapter 1058: Prison Pagoda

Valley Master Fu flew over to Han Li, then also pressed his hands against the stone slab as he said, "Leave that to me, Fellow Daoist Shi. You go help Celestial Maiden Su and the others."

Han Li nodded in response, then removed his hands from the stone slab before flying toward the Fire Age Firefly Queen.

The bearded man and the others were attacking the Fire Age Firefly Queen with all their might, but all of their attacks were kept out by its flames of time.

All of a sudden, Han Li appeared directly above the Fire Age Firefly Queen, and right as he was about to do something, the bearded man yelled, "I'll help you, Fellow Daoist Shi!"

At the same time, he also pounced at the Fire Age Firefly Queen while chanting an incantation and making a string of hand seals.

"Get back!" Han Li yelled, but the words had only just left his mouth when the flames of time around the Fire Age Firefly Queen reared up to form a blazing sun.

In the next instant, countless bursts of fire erupted toward Han Li and the bearded man, and the latter hurriedly sprang back in retreat, but it was already too late.

Bursts of fire pierced straight through his body, instantly setting him alight.

A cold gleam flashed through Han Li's eyes as a layer of golden light appeared over his body, and his speed was abruptly enhanced by severalfold. It was as if he no longer even possessed a physical body as he passed through the bursts of fire in a wraith-like manner, appearing before the Fire Age Firefly Queen in the blink of an eye.

A hint of panic flashed through the Fire Age Firefly Queen's eyes, yet before it had a chance to do anything, a cold harrumph rang out beside its ears, followed which a burst of sharp pain speared through its head.

Right at this moment, an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword with numerous time law threads wrapped around it appeared in Han Li's grasp, and Han Li swung it forcefully through the air.

The time law threads ensured that the sword was able to slice through the flames of time around the Fire Age Firefly Queen with ease, and it was decapitated in one fell swoop.

A look of relief appeared on Jin Liu's face upon seeing this, and he immediately released the chain in his hand before flying toward the three hives below.

Han Li quickly followed suit, stowing his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword away before also pouncing at the hives.

With a sweep of his sleeve, he released a streak of golden light to claim one hive, right as Jin Liu claimed another hive.

Immediately thereafter, the spiritual light released by the two of them latched onto the third hive in unison, and a tug of war ensued.

"You've already taken one hive, isn't it too greedy of you to be going after a second one, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Jin Liu asked in a cold voice.

"What right do you have to say that, Fellow Daoist Jin? You barely made any contribution at all in the battle just now, yet you want to claim two hives for yourself? Have you no shame?" Han Li sneered, displaying no intention of backing down.

Jin Liu was furious to hear this, and he protested, "There's no way you could've slain that Fire Age Firefly Queen if the three of us hadn't trapped it first! Besides, I'm claiming this second hive for Celestial Maiden Su. Surely she's made sufficient contributions to deserve a hive."

"In that case, please get Celestial Maiden Su to claim this hive herself. Who knows if someone as shameless as yourself would actually pass the hive onto Celestial Maiden Su instead of keeping it?" Han Li sneered.

A furious look appeared in Jin Liu's eyes upon hearing this.

"What did you just say?! I..."

"Give the hive to Fellow Daoist Shi," Su Anqian suddenly interjected.

At this moment, she was standing in front of the stone slab at the entrance of the cave, releasing bursts of blue light out of her hands to bolster the stone slab against the swarm of Fire Age Fireflies outside.

"What are you saying, Celestial Maiden Su?" Jin Liu asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"Fellow Daoist Shi made the most significant contribution of all during the battle just now, so he's definitely worthy of claiming two hives, and he also saved my life, so I would like to repay the favor," Su Anqian said.

Han Li turned to Su Anqian with a surprised look in his eyes upon hearing this.

"Fine!" Jin Liu snapped as he withdrew his spiritual light from the third hive, and Han Li immediately stowed it away without any hesitation, then rushed over to the entrance of the cave before casting a string of incantation seals into the stone slab.

A thick, golden light barrier quickly took shape, giving off bursts of formidable time law power fluctuations, and the stone slab was stabilized even further, falling completely still as it kept the Fire Age Fireflies outside at bay.

"Let's go!" Su Anqian said as she flew toward the passageway above the lava lake.

In the wake of the Fire Age Firefly Queen's demise, the fiery barrier over the entrance of the passageway had also faded away, and everyone rushed into it one after another.

After everyone had come through, Su Anqian swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of blue light, which formed a thick layer of blue ice to seal the entrance of the passageway shut.

Everyone else also cast some restrictions to bolster the seal on the entrance, and only then did they continue onward.

The passageway wasn't very long, so they quickly reached the end, arriving in a small stone chamber, at the very center of which was a dark red door of light.

Beside the door of light was a stone plaque that read "prison gate" and "do not enter".

Everyone exchanged a few glances with one another upon seeing this.

"Prison gate? Could it be that this Eon Pagoda once served as a prison?" Valley Master Fu speculated.

"Does that mean that the metal beasts on the first level and the Fire Age Fireflies on the second level were all prison guards? Now that I think about it, that doesn't seem all that implausible to me," Han Li mused.

Earlier, he had made the observation that the Fire Age Fireflies looked as if they were patrolling the second level of the pagoda, so this would certainly make a lot of sense.

"As opposed to speculating among ourselves, let's just go to the third level and find some answers there," Su Anqian said, and everyone turned to the door of light.

At this moment, the doorway was enshrouded under a red light barrier with rings of rippling golden patterns on its surface.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as his gaze fell upon the door of light, and he was struck by an inexplicable feeling that told him that this was no ordinary light barrier.

Jin Liu's gaze also fell upon the door of light, but he didn't seem to have noticed anything amiss, and he stepped forward to unravel the restriction.

Han Li opened his mouth to say something to stop him, but then decided against it.

"What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Valley Master Fu asked.

"I'm not sure, but I was struck by a sense of foreboding just now," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

Apprehensive looks immediately appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this, and even Jin Liu had stopped what he was doing to turn around and look at Han Li.

However, he then gave a cold harrumph before turning back to face the stone gate, and he began working on the restriction.

Shortly thereafter, a burst of red light flashed over the stone gate, and the golden patterns on the light barrier flashed a few times before fading away.

"Alright, the restriction has been opened, you can all go in now," Jin Liu declared as he turned to Valley Master Fu and the others, but all of them seemed very reluctant to go through.

"Are you going to turn back after coming all this way? Why don't you lead by example, Valley Master Fu?" Jin Liu suggested.

Valley Master Fu's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he offered no response.

A cold sneer appeared on Su Anqian's face as she stepped into the door of light, and Jin Liu could only follow her inside.

Everyone else turned to Valley Master Fu upon seeing this, and after a brief hesitation, he declared, "Let's go. No reward can be reaped without first incurring some risk."

With that, he stepped into the door of light, followed immediately by Han Li.

Upon stepping into the door of light, Han Li felt the entire world spin around him, but thankfully, this sensation only lasted a brief moment before he found himself back on stable footing, having arrived on a giant, black stone plaza.

The sky above the plaza was filled with dark clouds, and the entire surrounding area reeked of rot and decay.

Han Li noticed that all of the people who had already come through the gate were looking back at the gate with tightly furrowed brows, and he heaved a forlorn internal sigh at the realization that his fears had been confirmed.

Behind him was a giant stone gate that was around a thousand feet tall, and engraved onto each side of the gate was a golden armored warrior, while the lintel was riddled with all types of complex runes.

"Why is there such a complex restriction on this gate? Su Anqian asked with a perplexed expression."

"There are a total of seventy-two runes on this gate, of which there are as many as thirty-six varieties. It seems like these runes were inscribed in order to bolster the seal on this place," Jin Liu mused with tightly furrowed brows.

"Why is it that the gate was so easy to pass through, but the restriction on the other side is so much more complex? Is it trying to trap all those who enter?" Valley Master Fu asked.

"I'm thinking that perhaps the restriction on this gate was designed to keep something else in here," Han Li mused as he cast his gaze into the distance.

Valley Master Fu followed the direction of his gaze to discover a cluster of black buildings that were shrouded in black mist on the distant horizon.

Chapter 1059: Level Eighteen

"What have we gotten ourselves into?" Jin Liu sighed with a wry smile.

"It seems like the higher up we go in this pagoda, the more our spiritual sense becomes restricted," Valley Master Fu observed with tightly furrowed brows.

"Let's go. It's too late to turn back now," Su Anqian said in a calm manner, then led the way forward, and Jin Liu hurriedly followed along.

Meanwhile, Valley Master Fu and the others were still looking back at the giant gate behind them with hesitant expressions.

As Han Li passed Valley Master Fu by, he advised, "The restriction on this gate is not inferior to the protective array of a large sect, so it definitely won't be easy to bypass. My suggestion would be to look for another way out."

Immediately thereafter, he also set off for the cluster of black buildings.

Valley Master Fu and the others were still very hesitant, but they ultimately followed after Han Li as well.

As the group approached that cluster of black buildings, they began to detect an increasing abundance of baleful qi in the air, to the point that even the surrounding air temperature had dropped significantly, and everyone was able to see their own breaths as clouds of white mist.

Only upon arriving before the cluster of black buildings did everyone discover that it was an abandoned Buddhist temple.

The entrance of the temple was extremely dilapidated. Wild grass was growing rampant in the gaps in the brick walls, and even the two wooden doors were covered in moss, while the knockers on the doors were covered in rust and only just barely hanging on.

There was a plaque hanging above the doors, and it read "Level Eighteen".

Perplexed looks appeared on everyone's faces upon seeing this.

"Level eighteen? Isn't this supposed to be level three? How did we suddenly arrive on level eighteen?" Valley Master Fu exclaimed.

"Don't get so worked up, maybe this temple is called Level Eighteen," Jin Liu said in a derisive manner.

"This doesn't look like a very safe place... I think we should stay out of here," an itinerant Golden Immortal said in a fearful voice.

Right as his voice trailed off, the wooden doors of the temple swung open on their own.

Everyone waited for a moment with tense looks on their faces, but nothing else happened, and that left everyone at a slight loss for how to proceed.

Jin Liu and Su Anqian exchanged a glance and a nod with each other, following which both of them stepped into the temple.

Han Li raised an eyebrow before following along, and Valley Master Fu and the others were still feeling very hesitant, but decided to proceed, nonetheless.

As soon as everyone entered the temple, a grating creak rang out as the wooden doors swung shut again.

Han Li turned to discover two balls of ghostly green flames emerging from behind the doors, then drift through the air to arrive in front of everyone, hovering in mid-air like a pair of lanterns to guide them.

Everyone was quite startled by this, and only after a long hesitation did they follow the two balls of ghostly flames deeper into the temple.

Beyond the wooden doors was a large, white plaza that was rather uneven, and it would occasionally creak and groan underfoot.

Han Li looked down to discover that the plaza was paved with pieces of white bones, and not only was it very bumpy and uneven, there were occasionally specks of green fire rising up from it.

Everyone cautiously made their way over the plaza, but thankfully, they encountered no hazards, and before long, they had arrived at the Hall of Heavenly Kings. [1]

Inside the hall were two heavenly king statues that were hundreds of feet in height, almost as tall as the hall itself.

Both were clad in suits of dilapidated golden armor, and one was holding a vajra pestle, while the other was carrying a bloody human head. In contrast with the heavenly kings that one would expect to find in a normal Buddhist temple, these two were far more sinister and demonic in appearance.

After passing through the Hall of Heavenly Kings, everyone arrived on an even larger plaza.

There were nine elevated platforms constructed on each side of the plaza, and there were countless figures on the platforms, while agonized howls could be heard ringing out incessantly.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze toward the first platform on the left, upon which was a demon with green and purple skin, holding a pair of black metal tongs that it had extended into an elderly woman's mouth to slowly pull out her tongue.

The woman had an agonized look on her face, but was unable to make any sound aside from a quiet whimper.

On the first platform on the right, a beautiful woman was laid out completely bare while strapped to a stone bed, and two green-haired demons were snipping away at her body with a pair of giant scissors, causing the woman to shriek and wail in agony.

Similar horrific scenes were on display on all of the elevated platforms.

On one of them was a giant stone mill that was being pushed by a muscular demon, and a man's body was being crushed within the mill, but his head remained intact, and it was howling in agony.

On another platform was a giant metal pot that was filled with bubbling oil, and a horrified man was thrown into the pot by several demons.

......

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed at the sight of these terrifying scenes, and he finally understood why this place was called Level Eighteen.

It was said that hell had eighteen levels, and this was a legend that Han Li had heard many times in his formative years.

"What the hell is this place?" Valley Master Fu yelled in a grim voice.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a burst of red light appeared over the plaza up ahead, and ten figures slowly descended out of the sky.

It was a collection of ten ghostly beings that were dressed in bright red official robes with jade belts around their waists.

These ghostly creatures all had horrific, inhuman appearances, and their leader seemed to be a deathly pale figure with a large red flower on the front of his robe, as if he were a celebrated scholar who had excelled in the imperial examination.

"What are all of you supposed to be?" Jin Liu sneered.

"We are the Ten Kings of Hell! Kneel down and repent for your crimes!" the man with the scholarly appearance yelled as he pointed a finger at Han Li's group while placing his other hand on his hip.

His voice was very high-pitched, and that, in conjunction with the rather effeminate pose that he had just struck, immediately made him resemble a eunuch more than a scholar.

"You claim to be the Ten Kings of Hell? What a joke!" Su Anqian sneered.

"For your insolence, all of you will be subjected to eternal torture in this eighteenth level of hell with no chance for reincarnation!" the pale ghostly man yelled in a furious voice as he rose up into the air, followed immediately by the other nine ghostly creatures.

At the same time, gusts of yin wind swept through the air as huge plumes of black mist rose up from the ground, and countless fearsome demons that were wielding bone weapons were rushing toward the center of the plaza.

There were so many of these demonic creatures that were trampling over one another as they rushed onto the plaza, which was rumbling incessantly beneath their feet.

"Where did all of these things come from?" Valley Master Fu asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"Don't be alarmed, everyone, these are just ordinary yin beings that can be destroyed with ease. Our Heavenly Water Sect will deal with those ten ghostly generals, while all of you can take care of the rest of these ghostly creatures," Jin Liu said in a calm manner, following which he flipped a hand over to produce a miniature octagonal pagoda that was giving off radiant silver light.

Han Li was immediately able to identify the pagoda as a spatial immortal treasure, which was extremely rare, but unfortunately, it wasn't an immortal treasure of a very high caliber.

Immediately thereafter, around a dozen figures flew out of the entrance of the pagoda, and it was quickly revealed that they were all elders of the Heavenly Water Sect.

The group of elders was led by an early-High Zenith cultivator, while the rest were all at the late and peak-Golden Immortal Stages.

"Elder Lu Qiu, we'll be counting on you to help everyone deal with these ghostly creatures," Jin Liu said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

The leader of the group of Heavenly Water Sect elders was a thin elderly man with a head of white hair, and he waved a hand as he replied, "There's no need for formalities, Fellow Daoist Jin. We came here with you precisely so we could help out in scenarios like this."

Valley Master Fu and the others were feeling slightly more confident upon seeing this, and they summoned their treasures as they prepared to face the enemy.

Jin Liu and Su Anqian exchanged a glance with each other, then rose up into the air with all of the Heavenly Water Sect elders to oppose the self-proclaimed Ten Kings of Hell.

Following the departure of the Heavenly Water Sect cultivators, Valley Master Fu yelled, "None of these ghostly creatures are particularly powerful, but there are far too many of them, so if we all split up and fight on our own, we'll eventually all be worn down and killed. Hence, I propose that we establish an Azure Dragon Origin Array together, and perhaps that'll allow us to survive until the Heavenly Water Sect cultivators return victorious."

"But the Azure Dragon Origin Array is a secret array of your Azure Lock Valley, so none of us are familiar with it," an itinerant Golden Immortal said with a hesitant expression.

"The key to this array is a certain treasure. All you need to do is follow my instructions, and the array can be set up very easily," Valley Master Fu said, then quickly issued some instructions to everyone through voice transmission.

Immediately thereafter, he flipped a hand over to produce a dragon-shaped jade pendant, which he tossed up into the air, and everyone immediately sprang into action, following his instructions as they formed a circle while making hand seals and chanting a collective incantation.

Han Li was also standing nearby, but he didn't do anything.

Everyone was too busy setting up the array to reprimand him, but it was clear that they weren't very pleased with his lack of participation.

[1]. The Hall of Heavenly Kings is a significant structure that serves as an entry point to the sacred space in a Buddhist temple.

[Back]

Chapter 1060: Divine Lightning to the Rescue

Right as the ghostly creatures reached roughly a thousand feet away from everyone, an azure light barrier rose up from the bodies of Valley Master Fu and the others amid a loud draconic roar.

A series of azure dragon projections were roaming over the light barrier, which was releasing dazzling radiance that pierced straight into the dark clouds above.

As soon as the ghostly creatures crashed into the azure light barrier, a chorus of bloodcurdling howls instantly rang out.

The light barrier was flashing incessantly as the ghostly creatures that crashed into it began to disintegrate into plumes of black smoke amid a loud sizzling sound.

However, these ghostly creatures hadn't tasted living human flesh for countless years, and they had already been driven completely insane, so they continued to throw themselves at the azure light barrier without any regard for self-preservation.

Meanwhile, Han Li continued to act as a passive observer.

Jin Liu was furious to see this, and he yelled, "What are you doing? If you're not going to help, then don't expect us to protect you!"

Han Li paid no heed to Jin Liu as he remained standing still on the spot, looking up at the dark clouds above with a contemplative expression.

High up in the sky, the Heavenly Water Sect cultivators were locked in battle against the ten ghostly generals.

In contrast with all of the ghostly creatures down below, these ghostly generals possessed astonishing cultivation bases. Most of them possessed peak-Golden Immortal Stage powers, and their cultivation arts were extremely obscure and peculiar, granting a wide range of unpredictable abilities.

The scholarly man was the most powerful one among them, possessing mid-High Zenith Stage power, and his robe was extremely peculiar, seeming with two entire worlds contained within its sleeves.

Right at this moment, a vast expanse of black light erupted out of his left sleeve before crashing down upon Su Anqian, who was wielding an intricate blue fan, which she waved through the air to release a burst of light that created an enormous rift in the space before her.

At the same time, there was a green river embroidered onto the fan, and it abruptly vanished without any warning.

The sound of turbulent, flowing water rang out from the spatial rift as an enormous river came gushing out from within, crashing toward the scholarly man.

In response, a mocking sneer appeared on the scholarly man's face, and the black light surging out of his sleeve transformed into an enormous black vortex that began devouring the flowing river.

There seemed to be no end to the river that was gushing out of the spatial rift, but there also seemed to be no end to the black vortex's voracious appetite, resembling a bottomless abyss that could never be filled.

As the river flowed into the scholarly man's left sleeve, it came gushing back out of his right sleeve toward Su Anqian, but in the process, it had become severely contaminated with blood and floating corpses.

Su Anqian's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and the spatial rift began releasing a burst of tremendous suction force at her behest, sucking in the river that the scholarly man was using against her.

Moments later, the entire river had been sucked back into the spatial rift, following which the spatial rift itself also faded away.

The embroidered river then reappeared on the fan in Su Anqian's hand, but it had become contaminated with filth and was looking nowhere near as clear and pure as before.

At the same time, wisps of black baleful qi began rising up from the fan.

All of a sudden, a hint of alarm appeared in her eyes as a burst of glacial qi erupted out of the fan, and the river on the fan was also enshrouded in a layer of white light before freezing solid.

"That's a nice fan. It'll be even better once I take it from you and cast a hundred thousand yin souls into that river to refine it into an infernal river. On top of that, I'm also missing a concubine, and a pretty little lady like you will do just fine," the scholarly man chuckled in a sinister manner.

A hint of killing intent flashed through Su Anqian's eyes upon hearing this, and a blue longsword appeared in her other hand amid a flash of blue light, following which she launched herself at the scholarly man.

A cold sneer appeared on the scholarly man's face upon seeing this, and their battle recommenced.

On the other side, Jin Liu was wielding a pair of dragon spears as he fought against two of the ghostly generals.

One of them had the body of a human, but the head of a cow, and they were holding a crimson spirit beckoning banner. With each wave of the banner, gusts of yin wind were released, and whenever the yin wind came into contact with Jin Liu, he would feel wisps of soul power being sucked out of his body.

The other ghostly general also had a human body, but the hideous face of a horse, and they were holding a black chain with unintelligible yin runes engraved upon it. Bursts of green flames that were filled with tremendous baleful qi were rising up from the chain, capable of rapidly decaying flesh and bone upon contact.

These two ghostly generals were both at the early-High Zenith Stage, and one was attacking from afar, while the other engaged Jin Liu in close quarters combat, forming a very troublesome duo that even Jin Liu was struggling to deal with.

This entire third level resembled a giant spirit domain for these ghostly creatures, so everyone was at an innate disadvantage here, and the Heavenly Water Sect cultivators were clearly struggling despite their numbers advantage.

Meanwhile, Han Li was standing in the Azure Dragon Origin Array with a hesitant look on his face.

He knew that the longer this battle wore on, the more detrimental the situation would become for everyone.

On top of that, as soon as he entered this place, he had been struck by the feeling that he was being watched by a pair of eyes high up within the dark clouds above.

These ten ghostly generals proclaimed themselves to be the Ten Kings of Hell, but they weren't the most powerful beings in this space. Instead, the biggest threat here was lurking up above, and for some reason, they refused to show themselves.

With that in mind, Han Li also decided to refrain from taking part in the battle, choosing to observe the unfolding situation for now.

Right at this moment, a burst of thunderous rumbling suddenly rang out from the Hall of Heavenly Kings, and the entire roof of the hall was flung up into the air.

As it turned out, the two heavenly king statues inside had sprung to life, and they tore their way out of the hall before marching toward the plaza.

One of the heavenly king statues hurled the bloody head in its hand through the air, sending it crashing down onto the Azure Dragon Origin Array like a giant boulder.

A burst of mountainous force instantly came crashing down upon the array, almost shattering it instantly.

Everyone that was powering the array instantly shuddered as they each threw up a mouthful of blood, while the array itself began to sway unsteadily, and the azure dragon projections roaming over its surface also took on a more illusory appearance.

All of the ghostly creatures swarming onto the array instantly erupted into an excited frenzy upon seeing this, and at this rate, the array wasn't going to be able to hold itself intact for much longer.

Han Li could see that the other heavenly statue had already raised the vajra pestle in its hand, motioning as if it were going to hurl the pestle at the array as well.

In its current condition, there was no way that the array would be able to withstand another heavy blow, and with that in mind, Han Li heaved an internal sigh as he swept a sleeve through the air.

If you're not going to reveal yourself, then I'll just have to force your hand!

Eighteen streaks of golden light flew out of his sleeve in rapid succession, then pierced into the ground surrounding the Azure Dragon Origin Array, revealing themselves to be eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Valley Master Fu and the others immediately turned to Han Li with bewildered expressions upon seeing this, and they were even more perplexed by the fact that nothing else happened after the flying swords pierced into the ground.

The ghostly creatures outside the array paid no heed to this at all as they continued to converge from all directions, quickly burying the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords beneath them.

The weakened array wasn't able to eradicate these ghostly creatures as quickly as before, and they piled up higher and higher, finally inundating the entire array.

The heavenly king statue lowered its vajra pestle upon seeing this, seemingly deeming it no longer necessary to hurl the pestle at the array.

Su Anqian heaved a forlorn sigh upon seeing this.

"Don't worry about them, we need to focus on the task at hand," Jin Liu yelled with a grim expression.

All of a sudden, eighteen extraordinarily thick pillars of lightning erupted into the heavens from the plaza below, sending countless arcs of lightning flashing through the air in all directions.

Huge clouds of black mist rose up into the air as countless ghostly creatures were eradicated by the golden lightning, and a stunned look appeared in Su Anqian's eyes as she exclaimed, "This is Divine Devilbane Lightning!"

Chapter 1061: Great Encompassment Stage Ghost King

The ghostly creatures on the plaza had displayed no fear toward the Azure Dragon Origin Array, but all of them instinctively fled in horror in the face of Han Li's Divine Devilbane Lightning.

However, the golden lightning was far too fast for them to run from, and close to half of them were swallowed up in the blink of an eye before disintegrating into black mist, while everyone in the array looked on with ecstatic expressions.

In particular, Valley Master Fu was staring at Han Li with irrepressible shock and elation on his face.

Could it be that he's actually a High Zenith cultivator?

Jin Liu and Su Anqian exchanged a glance with each other, and both of them could see their own astonishment mirrored in one another's eyes.

Meanwhile, Han Li's gaze remained focused on the dark clouds in the sky above.

Su Anqian had also noticed Han Li's peculiar fixation on the dark clouds overhead, and a perplexed look flashed through her eyes, following which she suddenly yelled, "Look out, Fellow Daoist Shi!"

Right as her voice trailed off, a giant vajra pestle came crashing down from above.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he stomped both feet down into the ground, launching himself directly up at the vajra pestle without displaying any intention of taking evasive measures.

He was extremely fast, reaching the vajra pestle in an instant, but instead of engaging it in a direct collision, he wrapped his arms around the rapidly descending pestle before twisting around forcefully, altering its trajectory to send it flying back at the heavenly king statue that it had come from.

The heavenly king statue hurriedly threw a punch in retaliation, and Han Li launched himself at the statue without pause while channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, giving the vajra pestle a further boost.

A resounding boom rang out as the pestle smashed through the heavenly king statue's fist before barreling straight through its chest, following which a burst of radiant starlight erupted out of its body, causing it to explode into smithereens.

The other heavenly king statue stormed at Han Li while swinging a massive fist through the air, but Han Li was able to easily evade its attack before rushing along the length of its arm to arrive on its shoulder.

After that, he sprang up into the air before grabbing onto the edge of the heavenly king statue's helmet like an agile ape, then threw an almighty punch into the statue's face, pulverizing it with a resounding thump.

A massive hole was punched into the statue's face, revealing a ball of extremely condensed baleful qi, upon which were two flashing specks of ghostly flames.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he reached into the hole, and a ghastly wail rang out as the ghostly creature lurking within the heavenly king statue was forcibly dragged out.

Han Li jumped onto the top of the statue's head with the ghostly creature locked firmly in his grasp, and he looked up at the sky as he challenged, "Are you still not going to show yourself?"

A burst of golden lightning erupted out of his hand as he spoke, instantly eradicating the ghostly creature.

The dark clouds in the sky remained completely still, but the ten ghostly generals were infuriated upon seeing this, and some of them immediately began launching themselves in Han Li's direction, but they were stopped in their tracks by the Heavenly Water Sect cultivators.

"If you insist on hiding like a cowardly turtle, then I'll have no choice but to force you out of your shell!" Han Li roared.

Immediately thereafter, he made a beckoning motion, and the eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that had pierced into the ground below rose up into the air to revolve around him.

Immediately thereafter, eighteen more Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords appeared around him, amounting to a total of thirty-six.

The flying swords were trembling and buzzing incessantly as arcs of golden lightning flashed over its surface, and they sped up toward the dark clouds in the sky at Han Li's behest.

Countless streaks of azure swordlight erupted out of the thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, forming a radiant, azure sword dragon that plunged headfirst into the dark clouds overhead.

A draconic roar rang out as the azure sword dragon plunged into the sea of clouds, vanishing without a trace.

There was a brief moment of silence, followed by an earth-shattering boom.

A vast expanse of radiant golden lightning erupted out of the sea of clouds in all directions, forming countless giant golden lightning whips that lashed through the air with devastating power.

All of the ghostly creatures on the plaza were looking up at the sky while whimpering in horror, and fearful looks had also appeared on the faces of the ten ghostly generals.

At this moment, the natural dominance that Divine Devilbane Lightning had over all ghostly creatures was put on a full display.

Both Su Anqian and Jin Liu were astonished to witness this incredible display of power from Han Li.

They had always thought that Han Li was nothing more than a Golden Immortal who was very fortunate to have survived to this point, but the power that he was currently displaying was already far beyond that of the average Jade Immortal.

Han Li paid no heed to everyone's astonished reactions as he continued to look up at the sky with slightly furrowed brows, and right at this moment, a burst of sinister cackling rang out from within the dark clouds above.

All of the ghostly creatures instantly erupted into a frenzy, while the ten ghostly generals greeted in unison, "We pay our respects to Ghost King Wu Chao."

Both Su Anqian and Jin Liu were astonished to hear this.

"Ghost King Wu Chao? What is he doing here?"

Everyone else, including the other Heavenly Water Sect cultivators, turned to the two of them with perplexed expressions, and it seemed that none of them had heard this name before.

"Isn't he supposed to be in the Immortal Prison? Why is he here?" Han Li murmured to himself with a puzzled expression.

The name of Ghost King Wu Chao was not an unfamiliar one to him. Upon learning that Qi Mozi was the chief warden of the Immortal Prison, Han Li had gathered some information on the Immortal Prison through the Reincarnation Palace, and in the process, he had learned that Ghost King Wu Chao was one of the most notorious prisoners held captive there.

At this moment, the dark clouds in the sky were churning violently, and they began to rapidly condense, forming a cloud of black mist.

The cloud of mist was so dark that it was impossible to see anything within it, and as Han Li gazed upon it, he felt as if his soul were about to be sucked out of his body.

He hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, and that unsettling sensation quickly faded away.

"I must say, I'm very impressed with you. It's a pity that you're not dead yet. Otherwise, I would be more than happy to make you one of my Ten Kings of Hell. Having said that, it's still not entirely out of the question. Who's to say that you won't end up dead soon?"

A raspy voice rang out as a figure emerged from the cloud of black mist, and it was a tall, middle-aged man with a scholarly appearance.

He was quite unremarkable in appearance, and there wasn't any baleful qi emanating from his body. Anyone who looked at him could easily be forgiven for thinking that he was just a harmless scholar, and he looked worlds apart from a fearsome ghost king.

However, Han Li knew that this man was most certainly Ghost King Wu Chao.

It was said that back when Ghost King Wu Chao was still alive, he wasn't even a cultivator. Instead, he was just a Confucian scholar from a mortal empire, and he gradually began to develop resentment for the empire after his repeated failures in the imperial examination.

The empire was already in a state of decline, and its woes were compounded even further by the onset of a natural disaster. Wu Chao took advantage of this opportunity to spark a rebellion, and his rebel army quickly conquered most of the empire.

However, as more and more people joined his rebel army, they began to experience a food shortage, and in order to resolve this problem, Wu Chao turned to the horrific solution of cannibalism.

Before long, close to half of the empire's population had been eaten by the rebel army, and dozens of cities had been completely wiped out.

The immortal sects in the area were all forbidden from interfering with mortal affairs, but this was simply far too heinous a crime for them to tolerate, and they made an exception on that occasion to wipe out the rebel army. Otherwise, even the neighboring nations were eventually going to be completely wiped out by Wu Chao and his army of cannibals.

Following Wu Chao's demise, his soul refused to dissipate, and after devouring countless other souls, he became an extremely formidable malicious spirit, quickly reaching the Deity Transformation Stage. Somehow, he was able to transcend countless tribulations and progress all the way to the Grand Ascension Stage.

After that, he was blessed by a range of fortunate circumstances, allowing him to become a ghostly immortal, and he cultivated all the way to the Great Encompassment Stage. Due to his violent and bloodthirsty personality, he became extremely notorious in the Immortal Realm, and in the end, he was captured by the Heavenly Court and thrown into the Immortal Prison.

However, it seemed that he had already escaped from the Immortal Prison long ago, but it was unclear why he was being held captive here.

Chapter 1062: Inevitable Death

Ghost King Wu Chao made a grabbing motion with one hand, and a palm-sized black cage appeared over the palm of his hand, within which arcs of golden lightning were flashing incessantly.

Han Li's thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were currently confined in the cage, and they were struggling to free themselves with all their might, but to no avail.

"You finally decided to show up," Han Li scoffed.

"Earlier, I had sensed something that posed somewhat of a threat to me, but I was unable to ascertain exactly what it was. I had thought that it would be something in the possession of one of those two, but it seems like you're the hidden threat here," Ghost King Wu Chao chuckled.

"Are you referring to my Divine Devilbane Lightning? Haven't you already captured it?" Han Li asked as he feigned a surprised expression.

"This lightning is indeed a pain to deal with, but it's not enough to pose a threat to me. I've been faced with countless tribulations over the course of my cultivation journey, and I've even lost count of how many immortal envoys I've killed," Ghost King Wu Chao sneered, and right as his voice trailed off, a long spatial rift suddenly appeared behind Han Li without any warning.

A cloud of incredibly dense black mist surged out from within, and countless ghostly feelers and claws emerged from the cloud of mist, grabbing at Han Li while cutting off all avenues for retreat and evasion.

Han remained completely still on the spot as countless arcs of golden lightning erupted out of his body, making it appear as if he had donned a suit of golden armor.

As soon as these ghost claws and feelers came into contact with the golden lightning, they immediately recoiled as plumes of black smoke began to rise up from them.

Han Li swiveled around as he threw a punch into the cloud of mist, and clusters of profound acupoints lit up over his body as a burst of radiant starlight erupted out of his fist, illuminating the entire cloud of black mist.

All of the feelers and claws immediately shrank back into the mist as if they had been scorched by the starlight.

Ghost King Wu Chao was completely unfazed by this, and he continued to control the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords with one hand while making a grabbing motion with the other.

The spatial rift was instantly torn wide open, and black mist came gushing out from within like floodwaters. At the same time, Ghost King Wu Chao abruptly vanished from the spot.

Encompassed within the cloud of black mist, Han Li felt as if he had been plunged into the darkest of nights. Not only was he unable to see anything, he was also no longer able to hear the sounds of the battle taking place between the Heavenly Water Sect cultivators and the ten ghostly generals.

His brows furrowed slightly as he hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique and released his spiritual sense to examine his surroundings.

Right at this moment, Ghost King Wu Chao's voice rang out, but it was rather ethereal, and it was impossible to track down where his voice was coming from.

"So not only do you possess Divine Devilbane Lightning, you've also cultivated the Spirit Refinement Technique to a very advanced level. It's a pity that's not going to work on me, but I must admit that I'm getting more and more intrigued by you by the second.

Sure enough, to Han Li's surprise and dismay, he was unable to ascertain Ghost King Wu Chao's precise location even with his Spirit Refinement Technique.

Right at this moment, numerous bursts of red light appeared in the surrounding area, and every single one of which took on a humanoid form that was identical to Ghost King Wu Chao.

Han Li swept his spiritual sense over these Ghost King Wu Chaos to discover that their auras were completely identical, and all of them were giving off Great Encompassment Stage aura fluctuations.

All of a sudden, Han Li found himself surrounded by dozens of Ghost King Wu Chaos, all of whom began to make hand seals while chanting an incantation.

Balls of crimson light began to appear in the space around Han Li, forming a series of strange symbols that resembled both images and antiquated runes.

These symbols surrounded Han Li from all directions, and each of them manifested a ghostly head, all of which opened their mouths up wide to roar silently at Han Li.

A burst of dark red light surged out of the mouth of each ghostly head, and they enveloped Han Li from all directions.

As a result, Han Li instantly felt his own body completely stiffen. It was as if his blood had abruptly congealed, and his immortal spiritual power and starpower circulation had also become stagnant.

At the same time, a burst of crimson light appeared in his consciousness, and it also took on the form of Ghost King Wu Chao, who began slowly making his way deeper into Han Li's consciousness.

Han Li was astonished to see this. Given his mastery of the Spirit Refinement Technique, it came as a huge shock to him that Ghost King Wu Chao was able to breach the defenses of his consciousness so easily.

He immediately channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might, manifesting a mighty city wall to oppose Ghost King Wu Chao.

"Cease your futile struggles. This soul locking technique of mine is something that even Great Encompassment cultivators can't hope to withstand, so you're only prolonging your own suffering. Your fate is already sealed, so why not accept a swift and painless death?" Ghost King Wu Chao persuaded.

"Ghost King Wu Chao, there's one question that I would like you to answer for me so that I can at least die with closure," Han Li said.

"If anyone else were in your shoes, I would refuse without any hesitation, but given that you've intrigued me so, I'm going to make an exception and humor you," Ghost King Wu Chao said.

"I've heard that you're supposed to be held captive in the Heavenly Court's Immortal Prison, so why are you suddenly here?" Han Li asked.

"I thought you were going to ask me why your Spirit Refinement Technique isn't able to withstand my soul locking technique. So be it, I can answer that question for you. Back when I was held captive in the Immortal Prison, Immortal Lord Tai Sui was the chief warden. After that, he betrayed the Heavenly Court, and he promised me freedom in exchange for helping him escape, but he tricked me and imprisoned me here," Ghost King Wu Chao replied.

"I see. No wonder this Eon Pagoda is so fraught with peril. We came here to search for treasures, but it seems like we've been rushing toward an inevitable demise this entire time," Han Li said with a wry smile, but at the same time, he was making a string of hand seals with his hands concealed up his sleeves.

"Indeed, you've ventured into a place of no return. Even if I don't kill you here, you're never going to be able to escape from this pagoda, so you may as well let me put you out of your misery. At the very least, you'll have a chance to enter the cycle of reincarnation," Ghost King Wu Chao said.

All of a sudden, a faint smile appeared on Han Li's face, and he said, "I have another question: would you soul be able to withstand Divine Devilbane Lightning?"

As soon as Han Li's voice trailed off, countless arcs of golden lightning instantly surged into his consciousness.

A string of loud explosions rang out within Han Li's consciousness as Ghost King Wu Chao was completely inundated by golden lightning, and he instantly vanished from the spot.

Even though Han Li had managed to force Ghost King Wu Chao out of his own consciousness, his own soul was also severely ravaged by the Divine Devilbane Lightning, sending bursts of sharp, tearing pain spearing through his consciousness.

All of a the ghostly souls around him were instantly eradicated, and Han Li gritted his teeth through the excruciating pain in his head as he swept his gaze over the surrounding area, upon which he discovered that one of the dozens of Ghost King Wu Chaos had a burst of golden light glowing over the palms of his hands.

He immediately swept a sleeve through the air in that direction to conjure up a door of silver light, and Weeping Soul sprang out from within before immediately adopting her true Xing Beast form without any hesitation.

Her eyes became pupilless and bright red, and her body swelled rapidly as she transformed into a giant black ape that was over a thousand feet tall.

Tufts of needle-like fur appeared over her entire body, while a fearsome horn appeared on her head. At the same time, the skin and flesh on her glabella split open to reveal a third crimson, demonic eye, while three black bone spikes had emerged on her back.

Ghost King Wu Chao was furious after having his spiritual sense struck by Han Li's Divine Devilbane Lightning. He failed to anticipate that Han Li was harboring such formidable Divine Devilbane Lightning in his body, and he certainly didn't think that Han Li would release the Divine Devilbane Lightning in his own consciousness in such a reckless fashion.

He had only just steadied himself when he found himself face to face with a Xing Beast, and he couldn't help but feel a little panicked in the wake of such a hectic sequence of events.

Han Li immediately pounced on this opportunity, making a hand seal to summon his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords back to himself, and the flying swords instantly tore their way out of the Ghost King Wu Chao's black cage before racing back to Han Li's side.

Han Li could see that the golden light emanating from the flying swords had become noticeably dimmer than before, and he hurriedly sent them back into the Profound Heavenly Gourd to be nurtured.

After that, he turned his gaze to Weeping Soul, who was already locked in battle against Ghost King Wu Chao, and his vision suddenly blurred as he stumbled unsteadily on his feet.

Looks like the damage is even more severe than I imagined it would be...

Han Li heaved an internal sigh as he sat down with his legs crossed, then promptly devoured a pill that could aid in the recovery of spiritual damage.

Even though Weeping Soul had a natural advantage over all ghostly entities, there was a huge disparity in power between her and the Great Encompassment Stage Ghost King Wu Chao, so the outcome of their battle was very difficult to predict.

The space that they were currently situated in appeared to be Ghost King Wu Chao's spirit domain, so he had to stabilize his own soul as quickly as possible and assist Weeping Soul in her battle against Ghost King Wu Chao.

With that in mind, Han Li began to focus on recovery and pill digestion.

Chapter 1063: Second Battle Against Qi Mozi

While Han Li was engaged in seated meditation, Weeping Soul was locked in a fierce battle against Ghost King Wu Chao.

After evading a vast expanse of fearsome claw projections, she opened her mouth to let loose a deafening roar, and at the same time, her body swelled drastically in size, while numerous golden and silver runes appeared over her skin, giving off formidable law power fluctuations.

Simultaneously, a thick pillar of crimson light erupted out of her third demonic eye, hurtling directly toward Ghost King Wu Chao.

A hint of wariness flashed through Ghost King Wu Chao's eyes, and he made a beckoning motion with both hands, upon which the dozens of Ghost King Wu Chaos around him converged toward him before vanishing into his body.

Immediately thereafter, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a vast cloud of black mist, and a white bone claw extended out from within.

A burst of red light appeared over the palm of the bone claw, and it took on the form of a giant ghostly head with fearsome fangs protruding out of its mouth, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

The ghostly head opened its mouth up wide, and a swirling black vortex appeared within it.

The pillar of crimson light shooting out of Weeping Soul's glabella was devoured by the black vortex, and an impasse ensued.

At the same time, Ghost King Wu Chao made a strange hand seal with his other hand, then pressed his palm down toward the ground below.

A crimson seal flew out of the palm of his hand before vanishing into the ground in a flash ,and immediately thereafter, a pool of blood appeared beneath Weeping Soul before rapidly spreading in all directions.

Weeping Soul immediately attempted to take evasive measures upon seeing this, but a burst of tremendous suction force erupted out of the ground below, locking her firmly into place.

Before she had a chance to do anything else, the blood from the pool below began to climb its way up her legs.

The putrid blood in the pool was bubbling incessantly, as if it had been brought to a boil, and the blood was rapidly rising, almost inundating the entirety of Weeping Soul's lower body in the blink of an eye.

A chorus of ghostly wails rang out within the pool as countless crimson ghostly creatures emerged, resembling people who had been skinned alive, and they also began climbing their way up Weeping Soul's body.

The parts of her body that came into contact with these horrific creatures immediately began to release plumes of black smoke, as if she were being scorched by flames.

Thankfully, Weeping Soul's body was extremely resilient in her Xing Beast form, so she was able to hold her own just fine for now, but she was clearly already on the back foot.

All of a sudden, Han Li's eyes sprang open as he rose up into the air, and thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords reappeared around him as he cast his gaze toward Ghost King Wu Chao, but he had only just launched himself in Ghost King Wu Chao's direction when a burst of violent spatial fluctuations erupted beside him.

All of a sudden, it was as if a gash had been torn open in the night, and a figure emerged from within before reaching for Han Li.

The figure had appeared without any warning, and Han Li was caught completely off guard.

His pupils contracted drastically as he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, vanishing from the spot in a flash.

However, as he reappeared several thousand feet away, he discovered that the hand that was reaching for him was still right beside him.

A burst of radiant golden light appeared over the palm of the hand, and a burst of golden flames surged out from within, forming a hemispherical cage of fire that descended upon Han Li.

"Qi Mozi!" Han Li exclaimed upon catching a clear glimpse of his assailant.

Indeed, it was none other than Qi Mozi.

Han Li could sense that a change was currently taking place in the flow of time around him, and he hurriedly summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which began releasing waves of golden ripples at his behest.

The golden ripples clashed against the oncoming golden flames, and a clear divide took shape between them.

The flow of time in the area where the two met had become almost completely stagnant, and the golden ripples were rapidly dissipating, while the golden flames were dissipating at a much slower rate.

Meanwhile, close to half of Weeping Soul's body had already sunken into the pool of blood, but a ring of black light had appeared around her waist, preventing the blood in the pool from rising up any further.

A frantic look appeared in her eyes as she attempted to rush to Han Li's side to aid him against Qi Mozi, but she was unable to free herself from the pool of blood.

"You've made further progress in your cultivation base since we last met! If I don't get rid of you today, you're surely going to develop into a formidable threat in the future," Qi Mozi harrumphed coldly, and all the while, his golden flames continued to force back the golden ripples released by Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis.

Han Li let loose a loud roar as all of his profound acupoints lit up in unison, and he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might as he threw a punch directly forward.

A burst of radiant starlight erupted out of his fist, forming a screen of light that swept toward Qi Mozi, causing the space up ahead to compress upon itself in layers, resulting in the emergence of countless fractured spatial rifts.

The spatial rifts devoured much of Qi Mozi's golden flames, thereby significantly lessening the pressure on the golden ripples, and Han Li immediately pounced on this opportunity, sweeping a sleeve through the air to disperse his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, all of which abruptly vanished into the surrounding space.

However, mere moments later, all of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords came flying back from afar with their tips aimed directly at Qi Mozi's back.

However, before they were able to get close to Qi Mozi, a vast expanse of golden flames appeared behind him, and all of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly fell completely still upon piercing into the golden flames.

Immediately thereafter, Qi Mozi swept a sleeve through the air, and a lit torch appeared before him.

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he hurriedly withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis back into his body.

Immediately thereafter, the torch began to release rings of fiery spiritual light, and everything that was caught within the rings of light instantly fell completely still.

Han Li had immediately released his time spirit domain and channeled his Reversal True Axis ability as soon as he caught sight of the golden torch, but he was still unable to get away from the fiery spiritual light.

As soon as he was encompassed within the spiritual light, his movements instantly slowed down to a crawl. Even though he wasn't rendered completely immobile like last time, he was slowed down so drastically that it hardly made a meaningful difference.

On top of that, he didn't have a lightning array set up like last time, so even if he could temporarily free himself, there would be no way for him to get away.

However, that didn't mean that he was completely powerless, in the next instant, a layer of silver flames appeared over his body like a suit of silver armor, giving off formidable fire law power fluctuations.

As soon as the layer of silver flames appeared, the space around Han Li immediately began to shimmer and warp, and the fiery spiritual light around him also began to ripple slightly in an unsteady fashion.

"Impossible! How could mere fire law powers possibly oppose one of the three paramount laws?" Qi Mozi exclaimed with an incredulous expression.

Despite his astonishment, he was still very quick to react, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release the same black hatchet as last time, which hurtled directly toward Han Li as a streak of black light.

Without the golden ripples released by his Mantra Treasured Axis to protect him, the black hatchet was able to quickly reach him.

The silver flames on Han Li's body were torn apart by the tremendous force behind the hatchet, yet right as it was about to strike him, a layer of golden light formed by golden sand particles surged out of a golden hourglass hovering beside Han Li to oppose the hatchet.

At the same time, a golden vial appeared above him, and a layer of liquid-like golden spiritual light poured out of the mouth of the vial before wrapping itself around the hilt of the hatchet.

Upon striking the golden sand particles, it was as if the hatchet had fallen into a time vortex, and it was constantly sinking, but was unable to break through the sand particles to strike Han Li.

Meanwhile, spots of decay began to appear on the hilt of the hatchet from the effects of the water of time that had poured out of the Clear Time Vial, and even though the decay was only limited to the hatchet's surface, this was still an astonishing sight, given that the hatchet was an immortal treasure of a very high caliber.

A dark look appeared on Qi Mozi's face upon seeing this, and he sprang up into the air before closing in on rapidly on Han Li, seemingly completely unaffected by Han Li's spirit domain.

As he drew closer, the golden torch that was hovering in front of him also inched closer and closer to Han Li, and the fiery spiritual light that it was releasing became more and more potent as a result.

The silver flames on Han Li's body were beginning to waver, clearly struggling to contend against Qi Mozi's Time Severing Flowing Fire.

Right at this moment, Han Li drew upon all of the immortal spiritual power in his body and channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra with all his might.

A vast expanse of radiant golden light erupted out of his body as all five of his time-attribute law treasures appeared in unison, with each of them giving off its own unique time law power fluctuations.

However, on this occasion, even though the five time-attribute law treasures were resonating with one another, they didn't fuse as one to form that golden ring.

Hence, the five bursts of time law powers were still in a scattered state, and they were unable to keep Qi Mozi at bay.

However, right at his moment, an astonishing turn of events ensued.

Chapter 1064: Illusion

The Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis lit up one after another, then began to drift out of the axis before fusing as one with the surrounding spirit domain.

At the same time, the Mantra Treasured Axis itself also rose up into the air, hanging above Han Li like a full moon while giving off rays of golden light.

Immediately thereafter, the golden hourglass descended to the ground, and all of the golden sand particles inside rapidly spilled out, reaching Qi Mozi in the blink of an eye.

Qi Mozi was naturally rather taken aback by this turn of events, and he clearly had some reservations about setting foot onto the golden sand particles below.

However, after a brief hesitation, he stepped down onto the Illusory Dawn Sand, and in doing so, he felt his own movements become a little more sluggish, but he was still quickly approaching Han Li.

However, right at this moment, the three remaining time-attribute law treasures also began to display some changes.

The golden liquid within the Clear Time Vial came pouring out as a radiant golden river, while the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree planted itself into the golden sand on the ground before manifesting an entire forest, and at the same time, the Time Severing Torch rose up into the air before scattering into countless specks of fire that resembled stars in a night sky.

An astonished look appeared in Qi Mozi's eyes upon seeing this, and he reflexively stopped in his tracks.

Even Han Li himself was feeling quite startled by all of this. It seemed that his five time-attribute law treasures had fused as one with his time spirit domain to elevate the latter into a Creation Tier spirit domain.

All of a sudden, the time law power fluctuations in his spirit domain became several times more formidable than before, and golden ripples surging throughout the spirit domain were more evenly matched against Qi Mozi's Time Severing Flowing Fire, but ultimately Qi Mozi still held the upper hand thanks to his cultivation base advantage.

"I knew it! You really did inherit Master's Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, and you've already cultivated it to the point that it can resonate with your spirit domain! No matter what happens, I'm not letting you get away this time!" Qi Mozi said as the astonishment on his face turned to excitement.

Immediately thereafter, he drew his black hatchet back into his grasp before swinging it down upon Han Li's head.

At this moment, Han Li was still barely able to move, and all he could do was channel his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and true spirit bloodlines in unison, preparing to adopt his devilish deity form to withstand the oncoming attack.

However, right at this moment, numerous time law threads suddenly began flying out of the manifestations of Han Li's five time-attribute law treasures, and they quickly fused as one to form a ball of radiant five-colored light.

Qi Mozi's expression changed drastically at the sight of the ball of five-colored light, and all of a sudden, his entire body abruptly stiffened, as if he had become completely immobilized.

A bewildered look appeared in Han Li's eyes, and he could see layers upon layers of projections beginning to emerge from Qi Mozi's body under the ball of five-colored light, as countless avatars of himself were springing out of his body.

As more and more of these projections continued to emerge, the projections that had appeared first began to dissipate before disintegrating into clouds of gray smoke.

As these projections vanished one after another, some minute changes began to take place in Qi Mozi's body, and his aura was also displaying a change.

Han Li didn't know what set of circumstances had led to all of this, and he was terrified that any casual gesture from him could ruin everything.

Hence, all he could do was continue to channel his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra without even the slightest deviation.

At the same time, his gaze remained fixed firmly upon Qi Mozi.

After some observation, he was astonished to discover that with the dissipation of each projection, Qi Mozi's cultivation base would diminish slightly. To put it more accurately, it was his age that was gradually reversing.

Every single one of those projections seemed to be a manifestation of countless years of Qi Mozi's life, and as they dissipated one after another, Qi Mozi was rapidly aging in reverse.

After no more than twenty seconds, Qi Mozi's aura had plummeted to the point that he was no longer even able to maintain an early-Great Encompassment Stage cultivation base.

Qi Mozi was struggling with all his might, but to no avail, and he yelled in an alarmed voice, "How is this possible? These are all just illusory manifestations, how are they capable of doing this to me?"

Han Li gritted his teeth tightly as he continued to channel his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra with all his might.

He was confident that if he could persevere another twenty seconds or so, then Qi Mozi would age several more million years in reverse, and by then, he most likely wouldn't even be able to maintain a peak-High Zenith Stage cultivation base.

Unfortunately, things were not going according to plan. As time passed, the ball of five-colored light hovering above Qi Mozi was rapidly becoming dimmer and dimmer, and before long, it was on the verge of collapse.

A little more... Just a little more...

Han Li was persevering with all his might, but in the next instant, a dull thump rang out, and the ball of five-colored light finally faded away.

All of the time law threads within it had been exhausted of their time law powers, reducing them to translucent, attributeless threads.

Immediately thereafter, the moon in the spirit domain descended out of the sky, the stars faded, the mountains were smoothed out, the rivers ran dry, and the forest disappeared as all of the illusory manifestations vanished one after another.

The five time-attribute law treasures reverted back to their original forms, and they were all completely devoid of luster as they flew back into Han Li's body.

Before Qi Mozi had a chance to do anything, Han Li let loose a thunderous roar as he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and true spirit bloodlines in unison, transforming into a devilish deity with three heads and six arms.

Immediately thereafter, he threw a giant fist at Qi Mozi while also reaching toward him with a dragon claw that was covered in golden scales.

As soon as Qi Mozi was freed from the ball of five-colored light, he immediately made a hand seal before thrusting a palm forward, and the golden flame on his Time Severing Torch instantly reared up before pouncing at Han Li as a fiery dragon.

The fiery dragon was imbued with tremendous time law powers, and it passed through Han Li's fist and draconic claw at an inconceivable speed before hurtling directly toward his body.

The flow of time in the wake of the fiery dragon instantly fell stagnant, and the time-slowing effect was no less potent than when Qi Mozi possessed Great Encompassment Stage powers, so if Han Li were to be struck by this fiery dragon, then he would undoubtedly be completely immobilized.

However, Han Li was already prepared for such a scenario, and as soon as the fiery dragon appeared, his Profound Heavenly Gourd instantly appeared over his chest amid a flash of green light.

There was a rapidly revolving green vortex at the mouth of the vial, and its revolution also began to slow down as the fiery dragon drew closer, it didn't come to a complete stop.

Upon reaching the green vortex, the fiery dragon was sucked straight into the gourd, following which the mouth of the gourd was closed on its own, but the gourd itself continued to tremble incessantly.

Han Li had no time to examine the Profound Heavenly Gourd's condition as he pounced on this opportunity to lash out with his claw and fist with all his might.

Qi Mozi's cultivation base was currently very unstable due to the effects of the ball of five-colored light, and the abrupt disappearance of his fiery dragon into Han Li's Profound Heavenly Gourd had caught him completely off guard, so he wasn't able to react or retaliate at all before a wall of tremendous force crashed into his body.

A vast expanse of starlight erupted in all directions as Qi Mozi was sent flying back through the air.

The bones in his body were cracking and popping audibly as he threw up a mouthful of blood while glowering at Han Li with intense resentment in his eyes, and he flew all the way out of Ghost King Wu Chao's spirit domain before plummeting to the ground.

Han Li immediately prepared to set off in pursuit, only for Qi Mozi to rush away into the distance and vanish out of sight in the blink of an eye.

The ten ghostly generals and the Heavenly Water Sect cultivators locked in battle outside weren't even able to catch a clear glimpse of Qi Mozi before he vanished into the distant sky.

Han Li briefly considered going after Qi Mozi, but then quickly decided against that idea as he summoned his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and his Essence Fire Raven back to himself.

After that, he turned his attention to the battle taking place between Weeping Soul and Ghost King Wu Chao. At this point, the former's body was already riddled with wounds, and it was clear that she was very much on the back foot.

At this point, Ghost King Wu Chao had also already adopted his true form, which was a giant ghostly behemoth that was several thousand feet tall and clad in a suit of crimson armor, draped over which was a crimson robe.

There were sharp horns growing on his head and jagged fangs in his mouth, and whenever he exhaled, two plumes of putrid blood mist would surge out of his nostrils.

At this moment, he was holding a giant bone trident that was riddled with crimson runes, and there was black mist swirling around its three tips as he plunged it down at Weeping Soul's glabella.

A pillar of crimson light was blasting out of the vertical eye on Weeping Soul's glabella to clash against the trident and keep it at bay.

"Go!" Han Li yelled as he swept a sleeve through the air, and his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords shot forth before releasing countless streaks of swordlight that came raining down upon Ghost King Wu Chao like a torrential storm of golden swords.

Chapter 1065: Outsmarting the Enemy

A vast expanse of golden lightning erupted out of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in a frenzy before descending upon Ghost King Wu Chao along with the storm of sword qi.

Ghost King Wu Chao let loose a thunderous roar, and a burst of crimson light rose up from his body alongside a cloud of black smoke as he turned to the oncoming Han Li.

Immediately thereafter, he opened his mouth to release a burst of fearsome black flames, which swept toward Han Li as a wall of black fire.

Han Li continued to charge onward without pause as a giant, silver fire raven with a wingspan that was tens of thousands of feet in length erupted out of his body, and it swept a wing through the air like a huge silver blade to slice the fiery black wall into two.

Immediately thereafter, the silver fire raven flew straight through the wall of fire, and silver flames surging out of its wings forced back the surrounding black flames to forcibly create a wide passageway right down the center of the fiery wall.

Han Li was able to fly through the wall of fire behind the Essence Fire Raven, and he channeled his Lightning Bird bloodline power, instantly vanishing from the spot, only to immediately reappear beside Ghost King Wu Chao before throwing an almighty punch.

A resounding thump rang out as Ghost King Wu Chao's enormous body swayed involuntarily to the left from the force of Han Li's punch, and his trident also veered away to the side as a result.

Without the trident in place to oppose the pillar of crimson light blasting out of Weeping Soul's third eye, the latter immediately pierced straight through Ghost King Wu Chao's shoulder.

Ghost King Wu Chao let loose an agonized roar as large volumes of black fluid began to pour out of the huge hole that had just been blasted into his shoulder.

Immediately thereafter, a vast expanse of black light rose up over his body, and countless malicious spirits flew out from within before pouncing at Han Li and Weeping Soul.

These malicious spirits seemed to be capable of phasing in and out of reality at will, and whenever Han Li attempted to strike them with his fists, they would merely dissipate like clouds of mist. Hence, Han Li could only summon his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords back to himself and continually release Divine Devilbane Lightning to keep the malicious spirits at bay.

However, these ghostly beings didn't fear Han Li's Divine Devilbane Lightning, and after being struck, they would dissipate for a short time, only to quickly reform again.

On top of that, whenever they drew close to him, Han Li would feel a burst of malicious power infiltrate his body.

As the spirits pounced at him over and over again, more and more of this malicious power accumulated in his body, striking him with a bone-chilling sensation.

Weeping Soul was faring even worse than he was. At this point, her movements had already become noticeably slower, and she was beginning to struggle to keep up with Ghost King Wu Chao's speed.

If things were to continue like this, the two of them were undoubtedly going to be defeated.

Right at this moment, a thought suddenly occurred to Han Li, and he made a beckoning motion toward the Essence Fire Raven.

At this moment, the Essence Fire Raven was in the process of devouring the wall of black flames, and it immediately flew back into his body at his behest.

A surge of warmth instantly spread through his entire body, alleviating much of the bone-chilling sensation, and at the same time, he abruptly appeared directly in front of Ghost King Wu Chao amid a flash of silver lightning.

Ghost King Wu Chao immediately lashed out at Han Li with his bone trident, but right at this moment, Han Li flipped a hand over to summon his Profound Heavenly Gourd, and he pointed the mouth of the gourd directly at Ghost King Wu Chao before thrusting a palm into its underside.

A burst of thunderous rumbling rang out as a green vortex appeared at the mouth of the vial, following which a fiery golden dragon erupted out from within.

This was the fiery dragon that had been unleashed by Qi Mozi earlier, but following its rampage in the Profound Heavenly Gourd, it had become significantly smaller and slower than before. Even so, it was still giving off formidable time law power fluctuations that drastically slowed down everything around it.

Ghost King Wu Chao hurriedly raised his bone trident before hurling it at the fiery dragon upon seeing this, but the fiery dragon was extraordinarily fast, and the bone trident wasn't able to fly very far at all before the two clashed with a resounding boom.

The fiery dragon instantly exploded upon contact, releasing a wave of golden flames that washed over Ghost King Wu Chao, and he was instantly rooted to the spot, while even his thoughts had temporarily become completely stagnant.

Moments later, the wave of golden flames released by the fiery dragon's explosion began to fade away, and Ghost King Wu Chao was able to regain his cognitive functions, but by then, Han Li was already upon him.

Han Li was channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might, and he combined his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords into a single sword that he swung through the air with tremendous power.

A loud crack rang out amid an eruption of Divine Devilbane Lightning, and Ghost King Wu Chao's head flew up into the sky with its eyes still wide open before falling to the ground.

No blood came flowing out of his severed neck. Instead, countless ghostly shadows came gushing out from within.

As soon as these ghostly shadows began pouring out Ghost King Wu Chao's body, the baleful qi in the surrounding area instantly became dozens of times more potent.

Han Li was just about to release his Essence Fire Raven to incinerate all of the ghostly shadows when he spotted Weeping Soul rushing onto the scene.

With a loud snort, a burst of yellow light erupted out of her nostrils to capture all of the ghostly shadows surging out of Ghost King Wu Chao's neck.

Immediately thereafter, all of the ghostly shadows within the yellow light disintegrated into a burst of viscous black light that flowed into her nostrils.

As the burst of black light surged into Weeping Soul's body, the surrounding spirit domain began to fall apart bit by bit.

A relieved look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he began to inspect his surroundings.

The battle between the ghostly generals and the Heavenly Water Sect cultivators was still ongoing, and at this point, the ancient temple had already been completely destroyed, with the exception of a round archway that remained standing in a resilient fashion.

At this point, only three of the ten ghostly generals still remained, namely the pale-faced scholar, and the cow-headed and horse-faced duo.

As for the Heavenly Water Sect cultivators, all that remained were Su Anqian and Jin Liu.

There were only seven or eight bodies on the ground, and it was unclear if the rest had been completely devoured by the ghostly generals or if they had been sent back into that pagoda spatial treasure of his.

At this point, Valley Master Fu and the four itinerant Golden Immortals had already been reduced to sets of skeletons. There were still throngs of ghostly creatures around them, but without any prey to target, all of them were stumbling around in an aimless manner.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a gust of fierce wind that scattered all of the nearby ghostly creatures, then swept up some of the loose rocks on the ground to bury the remains of Valley Master Fu and the others.

At this point, the three ghostly generals finally realized that Ghost King Wu Chao had met his demise, and the scholarly ghostly general let loose a guttural shriek before throwing himself at Weeping Soul as if he had lost his mind.

Han Li appeared in his path before slashing his combined Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword down in one swift motion.

The scholarly man ran straight into the sword without taking any evasive measures, and his body was instantly sliced into two lengthwise.

Even as his body began to dissipate into black smoke, he was still calling out Ghost King Wu Chao's name in a dazed and grief-stricken manner.

The other two ghostly generals could see that the battle was already lost, and they immediately split up and fled the scene, while Jin Liu and Su Anqian set off after them in pursuit.

Han Li paid no heed to them as he took a glance at his surroundings, then sat down with his legs crossed to meditate.

The spiritual damage that he had suffered earlier and the subsequent overexertion of his time law powers had left him feeling very exhausted.

Around fifteen minutes later, he reopened his eyes as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

He didn't know how his five time-attribute law treasures had fused with his time spirit domain earlier, but judging from Qi Mozi's reaction, it seemed that this was something that was supposed to happen once one cultivated the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra to a certain level.

Unfortunately, he was completely self-taught when it came to this cultivation art, so he had no one to turn to for answers.

At the moment, he was unable to use any of his time-attribute law treasures as he had overexerted his own time law powers, and that was certainly a concern.

With that in mind, he heaved a faint sigh as he rose to his feet.

At this point, Weeping Soul had fully devoured Ghost King Wu Chao, and she reverted back to her human form before descending toward him.

As soon as she landed on the ground, she immediately let loose an involuntary burp.

"I had a little too much to eat," she said in an embarrassed manner.

"You were telling me that you've been constantly feeling hungry lately, so I'm glad you were able to have a good meal. You should return to the domain to rest," Han Li said with a smile.

"I do indeed need to go into seclusion for some time. Once I've digested all of this power, I'll be much more helpful to you in battle, Master," Weeping Soul replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light, and Weeping Soul immediately stepped into it.

Chapter 1066: Inevitable Battle

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to close the door of light, then flew over to the archway that was all that remained of the temple.

At the center of the archway was a pair of dilapidated wooden doors that looked as if they were only just barely hanging on for dear life, and on each door was a pixiu-shaped brass knocker, which bore some resemblance to Xiao Bai.

Judging from the array patterns on the doors, the restriction on them didn't appear to be particularly profound, but they were giving off the same type of energy fluctuations as the entrance to the third level, so it was clear that the fourth level was also going to be easy to enter, but almost impossible to leave.

After observing the archway for a short while, Han Li began working on unraveling the restriction.

Before long, two streaks of light arrived on the scene, and they were none other than Jin Liu and Su Anqian.

After a brief hesitation, Jin Liu cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li with a complex look on his face, while Su Anqian was observing Han Li with a wary look in her eyes, clearly unsure of what to make of him.

"Did you catch them?" Han Li asked in a casual manner as he continued what he was doing.

"Those two ghostly generals took the lives of two of our sect's elders, so we weren't going to let them get away," Jin Liu replied.

"I'll go bury their remains," Su Anqian said to Jin Liu before promptly departing, and Jin Liu looked on at her departing figure for a moment before turning his gaze back to Han Li.

After a long hesitation, he asked, "Fellow Daoist Shi, why is it that you've hidden your true power all this time? Are you facing some difficult circumstances?"

"No, I'm just used to proceeding with caution as an itinerant cultivator. There's no need to be overly wary of me, Fellow Daoist Jin. I am nor your enemy, and I don't plan to change that," Han Li replied.

"My apologies for the rudeness that I displayed to you earlier, Fellow Daoist Shi. The fact that you were willing to help Valley Master Fu and the others tells that you're definitely not the type to hold grudges. Hence, I'm not worried that you could be a potential enemy of mine. Instead, I would like to propose an alliance," Jin Liu said.

"I'm used to working on my own, so I'll have to pass. On top of that, there's no foundation of trust between us, so how can we expect one another to truly commit to an alliance?" Han Li replied with a smile, and a hesitant look appeared on Jin Liu's face upon hearing this.

"We've come all this way together, so I'll be sure to lend you my assistance in your time of need, as long as it's within reason, but don't expect anything more out of me. Once the time is right, we can all part ways and go off on our own," Han Li continued.

Right as his voice trailed off, the restriction was unraveled, and he took a step back as he clapped his hands together.

A burst of clanging rang out from within the archway, and the two wooden doors slowly opened outward to reveal a door of dark red light.

Before long, Su Anqian had also returned, and the three of them conversed briefly with each other before stepping into the door of light together.

......

Elsewhere in the Eon Pagoda.

There was a lonesome black and white archway standing in a barren area that was littered with loose rocks.

Leaning against the foot of one of the archway's pillars was none other than Qi Mozi, who had just fled from his battle against Han Li.

His palms were joined in front of his chest, and he was hovering slightly in mid-air while waves of rippling golden light were constantly emanating from his body.

Moments later, his eyes sprang open as an enraged look appeared on his face, and he spat through gritted teeth, "Even if I cultivate the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome for ten million more years, it still won't amount to anything! Who did you pass your Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra down to, Patriarch Miro? Could it be that Han Li really was your final disciple?"

He then fell silent for a moment before speculating to himself, "Alternatively, could it be that he also eavesdropped on your lecture like that rat did?"

However, he then immediately shook his head to deny the idea.

If one could glean the secrets of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra just by eavesdropping on Patriarch Miro's lectures, then he and his martial brothers would have to be complete idiots to have not been able to glean those same secrets.

The good thing is that he only seems to have just begun mastering the cultivation art. The effects caused by the Five Elemental Illusory World won't linger for too long, and once my cultivation base is restored, I won't let him get away again! Even if I can't secure the cultivation art from him, I have to at least kill him. Otherwise, he's going to develop into a major threat in the future.

With that in mind, he joined his palms again and continued to cultivate.

......

Meanwhile, Han Li's trio had arrived in a vast icescape.

At this moment, the three of them were standing on an extremely thick block of ice, and there were many mountains of ice in the distance in all directions, giving off vibrant rays of light.

Fierce glacial winds were howling over the icescape, sending shards and chunks of ice flying in all directions.

Several thousand feet behind the three of them was an enormous mountain of ice, embedded into which was a spatial door that was flashing with crimson light.

Beside the spatial door stood a stone plaque with the character for "four" engraved upon it.

At the moment, the three of them were carefully inspecting the surrounding environment with wary expressions.

The first thing that Han Li noticed was that the time-attribute restriction on this level was more formidable than on the previous one, and spiritual sense was also even more severely restricted here, with his spiritual sensory range reduced to roughly half of what he had been able to muster up on the third level.

"Let's do some exploring," Su Anqian proposed as she rose up into the air, and Han Li and Jin Liu did the same, following which each of them flew away in a different direction.

As Han Li flew through the air, he discovered that his speed was significantly hampered, also reduced to only around half of what he had been able to reach on the third level.

Of course, the three of them weren't flying at full speed. Instead, they were proceeding with great caution, making sure to constantly survey their surroundings as they went.

Han Li appeared quite calm and relaxed on the surface, but in reality, he was treading very carefully while releasing his spiritual sense as far as it would go.

Even though he had already predicted that Qi Mozi would've already entered the Eon Pagoda, he was still stunned by their latest run-in.

He had thought that with the large strides he had made in his own cultivation base, he should've at least been able to ensure self-preservation against Qi Mozi, but that was not the case.

What was even more troublesome now was that he was currently unable to use any of his time-attribute law treasures, thereby making him very vulnerable, and he didn't know if or when Qi Mozi was going to suddenly show up again.

As he continued deeper into the Eon Pagoda, the two of them were eventually going to have another encounter, and that would most likely be a fight to the death.

It seemed that he had unwittingly used some type of secret technique in the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra to save himself, but now that Qi Mozi knew what to expect, Han Li didn't know if he was going to be so lucky in their next run-in.

With that in mind, Han Li heaved a faint sigh as he promptly devoured a pair of pills to replenish his immortal spiritual power reserves.

In the wake of the recent string of intense battles, he had been forced to expend a great deal of immortal spiritual power.

To his surprise, as the pills began to replenish his immortal spiritual power reserves, all of his time-attribute law treasures also began to stir and display signs of awakening.

This was naturally a very encouraging sign for Han Li, and he felt a lot more reassured as he focused on digesting the pills that he had just taken.

Close to a day flew by in the blink of an eye.

To the surprise of Han Li's trio, the three of them didn't encounter anything during this time. There were no treasures, nor were they attacked by any metal beasts or Fire Age Fireflies.

Everything on the fourth level had been very peaceful thus far, almost eerily so.

"I'm starting to become a little unsettled by how quiet it is here," Jin Liu murmured to himself.

Han Li's brows were also slightly furrowed in apprehension. Even after traveling for such a long time on the fourth level, they had encountered nothing but the same monotonous icescapes.

"This place is indeed rather strange. Having said that, it's definitely not a bad thing that we haven't encountered any danger thus far. Hopefully, we can find the spatial entrance to the next level without encountering any conflict," Su Anqian mused.

With that, the three of them fell silent as they continued to advance while scouring their surroundings with their spiritual sense.

The trio continued onward for half a day without making any discoveries, and it was only upon arriving before an enormous mountain of ice that they finally came upon something different.

At the bottom of the mountain of ice was a cluster of palaces that had been constructed from some type of blue, jade-like material, and they were laid out in a similar fashion to the buildings in the ancient temple on the third level, except they were far less ominous in appearance.

However, most of the palaces had already collapsed, and many places had been frozen solid.

Han Li's trio exchanged a few glances with one another upon seeing this.

"The layout of these buildings is very similar to the ones on the third level. According to Ghost King Wu Chao, there's a fugitive being held captive on each level of the Eon Pagoda, so we can most likely expect some type of formidable being to be residing here as well. With that in mind, let's be a bit more careful," Su Anqian said with a solemn expression.

Chapter 1067: Coincidental Encounter

Both Han Li and Jin Liu nodded in agreement with this sentiment.

The three of them released their spiritual sense to scour the surrounding area for a while, and upon verifying that there were no hazards nearby, they jumped down and began to carefully examine the area, but they weren't able to make any noteworthy discoveries.

There were no signs of any living beings in the area, only more ice and freezing winds.

Before long, the three of them arrived before a large palace deep within the cluster of palaces.

This deep within the cluster of palaces, they were no longer able to feel the freezing winds outside, and as soon as Han Li set foot in the palace, a peculiar look immediately appeared on his face.

This minute change in expression didn't escape Su Anqian's attention, and she immediately asked, "Have you noticed something, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

At this point, Jin Liu was also taking Han Li much more seriously than before, and he immediately stopped in his tracks to hear what Han Li had to say.

Instead of answering Su Anqian's question, Han Li quickly made his way over to a corner of the palace before picking up several strands of semi-transparent white fur.

The strands of fur were extremely soft and around half a foot in length. On top of that, they were extremely thin and barely visible, and even Han Li would've most likely failed to notice them had it not been for his formidable spiritual sense.

"That looks like some type of beast fur," Su Anqian remarked.

"Perhaps there really is some type of beast residing in this area," Han Li speculated as he stowed the strands of fur away before casting his gaze deeper into the palace.

Thanks to the multitude of true spirit bloodlines in his body, he was extremely sensitive to the auras of true spirits, and he had detected a faint true spirit aura from these strands of fur, one that was rather similar to his own Azure Luan Bird bloodline.

Su Anqian and Jin Liu exchanged a wary glance with each other.

After a brief hesitation, Jin Liu swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a streak of green land that landed on the ground before him.

The green light then faded to reveal a small, green, fox-like beast with a remarkably long nose and a pair of spritely green eyes.

As soon as the fox-like creature appeared, it began sniffing vigorously at the ground before rushing forward.

"That's a Green-Eyed Spirit Fox!" Han Li exclaimed.

"Looks like you're quite knowledgeable when it comes to spirit beasts, Fellow Daoist Shi," Jin Liu remarked with a hint of surprise in his eyes.

"I just so happened to read about these things in a scripture that I had browsed in the past," Han Li explained in an ambiguous fashion.

Green-Eyed Spirit Foxes weren't particularly formidable in battle, but their eyes and noses were extremely sensitive, making them exceptional at tracking down treasures, but they were exceedingly rare creatures.

"With this Green-Eyed Spirit Fox leading the way, we should be a lot safer. Let's go," Jin Liu said, and before long, the three of them had followed the Green-Eyed Spirit Fox through several large palaces.

All of a sudden, the buildings up ahead became much sparser, and a long corridor came into view.

After passing through the corridor, Han Li's trio arrived in a dark hall that was around two hundred to three hundred feet in size, and to their elation, deep within the hall stood a stone gate.

A dark red door of light was embedded into the stone gate, and it was none other than a spatial door.

However, there were no restrictions on the spatial door, perhaps indicating that they had already been undone by someone else.

"This spatial door was much easier to track down than the previous ones!" Su Anqian remarked with an elated expression, but at the same time, she refrained from approaching the spatial door right away as she carefully examined her surroundings with her spiritual sense.

The more tantalizing the circumstances, the higher the likelihood of the presence of a trap, so she remained very cautious and alert.

Han Li and Jin Liu were also scouring the hall with their spiritual sense, while the Green-Eyed Spirit Fox was darting its way around the hall.

Even after a thorough examination of the entire hall, the three of them weren't able to find any traps or hazards, and that left them feeling rather perplexed.

"It looks like something must've happened that caused the collapse of all of those palaces. Whatever was held captive here must've either already perished or fled. Let's go to the fifth level," Su Anqian said before leading the way into the spatial door, and sure enough, she was able to pass through without any incident.

Han Li and Jin Liu followed along upon seeing this, and the two of them found themselves standing on a barren desert.

Fierce winds were howling over the desert, throwing up large volumes of sand into the air, and there was nothing but desert as far as the eyes could see in all directions.

On top of that, there were also some dirt hills in the surrounding area that had been contorted into all types of strange shapes from wind erosion, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

At this moment, Su Anqian was hovering in mid-air, scouring the surrounding area from up high.

The time-attribute restriction on this level was even more formidable, and Han Li discovered that his own spiritual sensory range had shrunk down to only around a tenth of its normal level.

Not only was the time-attribute restriction present in the area severely hampering spiritual sense, it also weighed down upon their souls like a heavy rock, and it was beginning to affect the accuracy of their spiritual sense.

"Let's go. If this pagoda really does have a total of seven levels, then there are only three levels left. Hopefully, this level will be just as uneventful as the last one," Su Anqian said.

With that, the three of them continued onward, but as they did so, they discovered that the winds were becoming stronger and stronger, sweeping up countless loose rocks of different sizes to severely impact visibility.

All of a sudden, Han Li stopped in his tracks as he cast his gaze directly forward.

"What is it, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Su Anqian asked as she and Jin Liu also stopped in their tracks.

"This wind is rather strange. It's not formed naturally. Instead, someone's controlling it," Han Li replied.

Su Anqian and Jin Liu faltered slightly upon hearing this, then began to carefully examine the surrounding environment, upon which they discovered that there were traces of spiritual qi fluctuation interspersed throughout the wind, indicating that someone was indeed controlling it.

"Looks like we won't be able to pass through this level as easily as the previous one. What should we do now? Should we go and take a look?" Jin Liu asked.

It had to take an extremely formidable being to conjure up a wind storm of such an enormous scale, and there was a good chance that it was the being imprisoned on this level.

"Judging from past experience, the spatial doors are always somewhere near the beings held captive on the levels, so I'm afraid that we may have no choice but to confront whatever it is," Su Anqian mused.

"I agree," Han Li replied with a nod.

Jin Liu was a little hesitant, but he ultimately raised no objections, and the three of them continued onward, tracking the spiritual qi fluctuations in the air as they went.

The further they went, the stronger the winds became, and the spiritual qi fluctuations in the air wind also became stronger, so it was a simple task for them to track down the source of these winds.

As they continued onward, the dirt hills up ahead also increased in number and size, and they were gradually beginning to form some yellow mountain ranges.

After close to an hour of travel, the three of them finally found the source of the spiritual qi in the wind.

The trio descended onto an obscure location near a canyon that was several hundred kilometers in size, and they concealed their own auras as they cast their eyes forward.

At this moment, there were dozens of thick, white tornadoes wreaking havoc within the canyon. Each of them was over a thousand feet in diameter and dozens of kilometers tall, stretching all the way up into the clouds.

These tornadoes were imbued with extremely formidable spiritual power and law powers, and they were sweeping through the area with unmatched ferocity, easily shredding and devouring everything that they came into contact with.

There was a white figure that could just barely be made out within the largest of the tornadoes, but it was impossible to see them clearly through the tornado, and the violent law powers within the tornado also kept out all prying spiritual sense.

There was also a group of around five or six cultivators present in the canyon, and they were doing everything in their power to ward off the surrounding tornadoes.

"It's them!"

The group consisted of Lei Yuce, Wen Zhong, a young man and woman duo who were both dressed in black, and the young man who had previously appeared together with Qi Mozi.

In addition to them, there was also Lan Yan, who had managed to flee from Han Li.

Surprised looks had also appeared on the faces of Su Anqian and Jin Liu at the sight of the six people up ahead.

The tornadoes were extremely formidable, and even though the six of them were resisting with all their might, it was clear that they were fighting a losing battle.

What was even more alarming to Han Li was that he could sense at the figure within the tornado wasn't using their full power. Instead, they seemed to be merely toying with Lei Yuce and the others.

Right at his moment, a burst of high-pitched cackling rang out from within the tornado.

"You were hoping to get to the sixth level with your pathetic powers? What a joke! You should all just stay here and entertain me."

As soon as the voice trailed off, all of the tornadoes instantly fused as one, forming an incredibly massive tornado that swept up Lei Yuce's group within it.

The unfathomably enormous tornado stood like a pillar that was supporting the heavens, sweeping up winds that were several times more ferocious than before.

The immortal treasures summoned by Lei Yuce and the others were being blown around like severed kites, and all of them were trapped within the tornado, unable to escape.

Su Anqian and Jin Liu's expressions changed drastically upon seeing this.

Lei Yuce was certainly no slouch, and the people with him appeared to be quite powerful as well, yet they had been trapped like a bunch of helpless children.

Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly upon seeing this. The tornado didn't appear to be remarkable in any way, and it was only imbued with wind law powers, so he didn't understand how it could be this formidable.

He activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes for a closer look, and only then was he able to discover the secret to the tornado's power.

As it turned out, there were two different types of wind law powers within the tornado, but they were perfectly fused together and barely distinguishable from one another.

Chapter 1068: Decision

So these white tornadoes are formed by the fusion of two types of law powers. No wonder they're so powerful.

The fusion of law powers could produce power that far exceeded the sum of the individual law powers.

However, this type of fusion was extremely rare and difficult to achieve, and Han Li had barely seen any instances of it during all his time in the True Immortal Realm. The only examples that he could think of were Gongshu Tian and his immortal envoy companion, Lan Yan and Lan Yuanzi, and Wyrm 3 and himself.

However, those instances of law fusion were all very surface-level compared with these tornadoes, the law powers within which were fused to a far higher degree.

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he tried to think of a way to counteract that fusion of law powers, but to no avail.

Secret techniques that facilitated the fusion of law powers were extremely rare, and it was even rarer for people to put such secret techniques into writing. Even if scriptures containing these secret techniques existed, they were most likely in the possession of a very small number of people.

Han Li had been able to enjoy a great deal of freedom cultivating on his own for all these years, but the downside was that with no mentor to guide him, he was very much lacking in cultivation experience.

With that in mind, he decided that once he left this secret area, he would have to find someone to instruct him in the cultivation of law powers and spirit domains. As a Reincarnation Disciple, he was certain that he would be able to find suitable mentors in the Reincarnation Palace as long as he was willing to spend the Immortal Origin Stones.

Right at this moment, the white figure within the tornado heaved a forlorn sigh.

"Is that all you've got? This is pathetic! How disappointing!"

Furious looks instantly appeared on the face of Lei Yuce and the others upon hearing this, and all of them unleashed their spirit domains, which stacked on top of one another.

Lei Yuce's golden spirit domain was the largest of them all, and the area encompassed within the spirit domain was riddled with golden mountains that were, in turn, riddled with bright, golden swords that were giving off tremendous sword intent.

As soon as his spirit domain was unfurled, everyone was instantly stabilized, no longer involuntarily being swept up by the tornado around them.

A solemn look appeared on Lei Yuce's as he chanted an incantation while making a rapid string of hand seals, and around fifty to sixty translucent golden law threads shot out of his body, giving off immense law power fluctuations.

All of the golden swords within his spirit domain instantly converged toward the golden law threads before fusing into them, and before long, the law threads had transformed into dozens of giant golden swords of all types of different shapes and sizes.

Despite the disparities in the appearances of these giant swords, every single one of them was giving off an almighty aura!

The dozens of giant golden swords circled around within the spirit domain, and all of them were releasing formidable sword intent, but they didn't conflict with one another at all, and they had formed a peculiar sword array.

As soon as the array took shape, the sword qi released by all of the giant swords instantly shot forth to fill the entire surrounding space.

At the same time, Lei Yuce let loose a thunderous roar, and each of the giant swords released a burst of enormous sword qi that struck the surrounding tornado.

The sound of tearing fabric rang out as the tornado bulged outward, while a series of gashes were torn into it, with rays of blinding, golden light shining through.

Even Han Li couldn't help but be stunned by the sight of the sword array.

His Azure Coil Sword Array and Horned Dragon Sword Array were both top-tier sword arrays, but even they were slightly inferior to the one that Lei Yuce was currently putting on display.

It seemed that the Almighty Sword Sect's title of number one sword sect in the Golden Origin Immortal Region was well-deserved.

On top of that, Han Li was also very intrigued by Lei Yuce's ability to manifest flying swords using his law threads to unleash the sword array, as opposed to using actual flying swords.

A hint of envy flashed through Wen Zhong's eyes at the sight of the sword array unleashed by Lei Yuce, and he also sprang into action as four huge streaks of golden swordlight erupted out of his spirit domain.

Each streak of swordlight was around a thousand feet in size, and designs of the Azure Dragon, the White Tiger, the Vermilion Bird, and the Xuanwu Turtle had been engraved upon them. These streaks of swordlight were also giving off tremendous sword qi, but far less so than Lei Yuce's sword array.

Wen Zhong thrust a palm forward, and the four streaks of swordlight shot forth through the air to strike the white tornado in unison.

Meanwhile, Lan Yan had conjured up a blue spirit domain and summoned that blue sickle of hers before unleashing her Origin Water Slash, sending an arc of blue light that was several hundred feet in length sweeping toward the white tornado.

Xiong Shan had also summoned his spirit domain, and in this dire situation, he wasn't holding back, either, sweeping a sleeve through the air to release hundreds of flying swords, forming a circular, golden sword array that was around an acre in size.

A deafening roar rang out as a golden sword dragon formed by swordlight emerged from the center of the golden array, then pounced at the tornado with unstoppable might.

As for the black-robed duo, each of them had only summoned an immortal treasure, and it was unclear if this was because they were still yet to attain spirit domains.

The black-robed woman had summoned a large, white bead that was etched with radiant, golden patterns and was filled with immense law powers, while the black-robed young man had summoned a tree-branch-like immortal treasure that was several feet in length.

The branch had seven sub-branches, at the tips of which were specks of menacing, black light that was giving off a bloody odor, indicating that it was some type of sinister artifact.

As soon as the two immortal treasures left their hands, they immediately transformed into two streaks of light, one black and one white, before crashing into the tornado with astounding power.

Thanks to everyone's combined efforts, the rifts on the surrounding tornado had widened even further, and it was beginning to display signs of serious strain.

"The Almighty Sword Array truly does live up to its name, but unfortunately, you haven't attained a sufficient number of law threads to fully realize the array's power, so it's not going to be enough to break my Heavenly Gale Pillar," the white-robed man in the other tornado cackled.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a white spirit domain appeared within the tornado before rapidly proliferating outward in all directions.

The spirit domain was filled with countless clouds and gusts of fierce wind, making one feel as if it had encompassed the entire heavens.

Furthermore, it was significantly larger than the spirit domains of Lei Yuce and the others, and it swallowed up all of them at once.

Lei Yuce and the others instantly felt a burst of tremendous force weigh down upon them, as if they had sunken into a bottomless pit of mud, making it very difficult to move. At the same time, a burst of formidable law power surged into their spirit domains, throwing them into a state of violent disarray.

Meanwhile, close to a hundred white law threads shot out of the white spirit domain before fusing into the tornado in a flash, and the gashes that had appeared on its surface were instantly sealed.

On top of that, it had become even denser and sturdier than before.

Grim looks appeared on the faces of Han Li's trio upon seeing this, and in particular, Su Anqian's lips were tightly pursed with concern, but it was unclear whom her concern was directed toward.

"It looks like Lei Yuce and the others are no match for their assailant. Should we help them?" Jin Liu asked.

"We don't have any close ties with Lei Yuce and the others, but we're still technically allies, so I think we should help them. Besides, if we stand by and let them die, then the three of us most likely won't be able to fare much better on our own," Su Anqian said as she turned her gaze to Han Li.

At this point, she had already been thoroughly won over by the power and judgment displayed by Han Li, and she was beginning to regard her as the spiritual leader of their group, particularly when important decisions had to be made.

Jin Liu was rather reluctant to comply, but he also reflexively turned to Han Li.

"I think Fellow Daoist Su is right. Right now, all of us are in the same boat, so we have to stick together and help one another as much as possible," Han Li decided.

With their minds made up, the three of them instantly vanished from the spot.

At this moment, Lei Yuce was standing within the enormous, white tornado with a grim look on his face, and all of a sudden, he let loose a loud roar as his face suddenly turned bright red.

At the same time, he made a hand seal, and a golden nascent soul that was around a foot in size flew out of the top of his head amid a flash of golden light.

The nascent soul opened its mouth to release a ball of shimmering, golden blood essence that contained astonishingly formidable law powers, and the ball of blood essence vanished into the surrounding golden spirit domain in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, all of the color was drained from Lei Yuce's face, and even his skin had become wizened and wrinkled, as if he had just aged significantly.

However, the golden spirit domain around him was significantly bolstered, managing to stabilize itself again.

The Almighty Sword Array within the spirit domain also lit up as all of the giant swords flew back to Lei Yuce's side before circling rapidly around him.

A burst of terrifying sword intent that was several times more formidable than that of the sword array erupted out of Lei Yuce's body, and a giant, illusory, golden sword appeared around, threatening to pierce through the very heavens.

The space near the illusory sword was quivering incessantly, and with a sweep of Lei Yuce's sleeve, the giant sword projection was sent flying toward the surrounding tornado, slicing through the space in its path with ease.

"I'll admit that your mastery of the Almighty Sword Array is very impressive, but once again, your cultivation base is the limiting factor here," the white figure remarked, but this time, a more serious tone had crept into his voice.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a white hoof projection that the size of a house emerged within the tornado.

Immediately thereafter, over a hundred white law threads appeared within the white spirit domain, all of which vanished into the hoof projection in a flash.

The hazy hoof projection instantly became much clearer and more substantial before stomping down with ferocious might.

Chapter 1069: Lekima

The space beneath the hoof projection rippled like the surface of a disturbed lake before exploding to create a massive spatial hole.

The hoof projection continued onward without pause, stomping straight through the spatial hole and onto the tip of the giant, illusory sword.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the two clashed, causing the entire surrounding space to tremble and ripple.

The hoof projection exploded upon contact, but the illusory sword was also shattered before disintegrating into countless pecks of golden light.

The white tornado shuddered violently from the resulting shockwaves, and a series of gashes appeared over its surface.

In the wake of the hoof projection's implosion, all of the white law threads reappeared, glowing just as brightly as before.

However, right as the law threads were about to fade back into the white spirit domain, two blue spirit domains abruptly appeared without any warning to capture them.

At the same time, a blue ice sword that was over a thousand feet in length and a blue fist the size of a small mountain appeared in unison before the tornado before crashing into it with astonishing power.

The tornado shuddered violently once more, and the gashes on its surface widened even further, but it remained intact.

"Did you think I hadn't noticed the two of you sneaking around this entire time? You could've perhaps lived a little longer had you remained hidden, but seeing as you two are so eager to rush to your graves, I'd be more than happy to send you on your way!" the white figure chortled, following which a giant, white hand appeared in his spirit domain before grabbing down onto what appeared to be nothing but empty air.

A resounding boom rang out as a ball of piercing blue light abruptly appeared in the giant hand's grasp, following which Su Anqian and Jin Liu stumbled out of thin air before being captured.

However, right at this moment, a golden finger projection that was over a hundred feet in length and as thick as a water vat descended suddenly out of the sky, giving off an aura that suggested it was capable of piercing through anything in its path.

The surrounding space was so severely warped by the finger projection's aura that countless golden spars had appeared around it, and the white tornado was only able to pose some brief resistance before a huge hole was pierced into its surface, following which it exploded with a deafening boom.

Lei Yuce and the others were both astonished and ecstatic to see this, and they hurriedly combined their powers to force their way out of the white spirit domain.

"Who's there? Come out, you coward!" the white figure yelled in a bewildered voice as he frantically scoured his surroundings.

Han Li appeared within the white spirit domain amid a flash of golden light, and there was a smile on his face as he said, "I've been standing here this entire time, it's just that you failed to notice me."

After close to a day of rest, all of his time-attribute law treasures had recovered somewhat, allowing him to use both the Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique and the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra to conceal himself. In doing so, he was able to sneak over to the white tornado completely undetected before destroying it with his Heaven Piercing Figure.

The white figure was very much taken aback by the fact that Han Li had managed to completely avoid the detection of his spiritual sense, and taking advantage of his momentary lapse in concentration, Su Anqian and Jin Liu were able to force their way out of the giant hand projection around them before flying to Han Li's side.

The white figure was furious to see this, and he lashed out without any hesitation.

The giant, white hand shot forth through the air at his behest, reaching Su Anqian and Jin Liu in the blink of an eye before grabbing down on them once again.

At the same time, it was giving off a terrifying aura that threatened to crush the very space beneath it, and Su Anqian and Jin Liu were instantly slowed down in their escape as a result.

However, right at this moment, a mountainous, golden fist projection appeared out of thin air, releasing waves of rippling, golden light as it crashed into the huge, white hand.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the fist and hand projections were shattered in unison, and the resulting shockwaves created countless spatial rifts in the surrounding area.

Han Li shuddered violently as he took an involuntary step backward, while the white figure within the tornado also swayed slightly.

With the giant hand destroyed, Su Anqian and Jin Liu were freed from the restrictive force it had exerted upon them, and they hurriedly flew over to Han Li.

At the same time, they were also joined by Lei Yuce and the others.

At this point, some color had returned to Lei Yuce's face, and he cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li's trio as he said, "Thank you for your help in our time of need, fellow daoists."

Even though he was addressing the three of them at once, his gaze was fixed solely on Su Anqian with a look of affection in his eyes.

Su Anqian averted her eyes from Lei Yuce's affectionate gaze as she said, "There's no need to thank me or Jin Liu. Fellow Daoist Shi was the one who saved all of you, so if you want someone to thank, then thank him."

A hint of surprise flashed through Lei Yuce's eyes upon hearing this, and he turned to Han Li before extending another grateful salute.

Everyone else was also quite surprised to hear this, but they still offered their gratitude to Han Li, nonetheless.

In contrast, Lan Yan was already aware of Han Li's power, so she wasn't surprised at all, and at this moment, there was a combination of panic, resentment, and wariness in her eyes as she glowered at Han Li.

Han Li paid no heed to Lan Yan's hostile gaze as his eyes remained fixed on the white figure.

Even though he had managed to catch the white figure off guard and destroy the tornado, it was clear that this was an extremely formidable opponent, and he couldn't afford to get distracted.

Thankfully, Lei Yuce and the others had been freed, so everyone was able to join forces and put up a concerted resistance.

"Finally, a worthy opponent. Looks like this won't be a complete waste of time, after all," the white figure chortled with glee, and all of the scattered white law threads around him instantly vanished into his body.

At the same time, the tornado around him faded away, revealing a majestic, white horse with a pristine, white mane.

At this moment, the horse was standing on its hindlegs, and it was resting one of its front hooves against its waist in a very humanized gesture, while an azure pipe that it was smoking out of was held in its other hoof.

Han Li and the others were all stunned to see this.

Han Li took a moment to compose himself, then asked, "May I ask your name, Fellow Daoist?"

"You don't know who I am? What rock have you been living under all this time? Listen up, my name is Lekima! [1] You're a pretty strong little brat. You've mastered the laws of time, and your physical body is also very powerful. Come, let's have a fight!"

Fierce battle intent was glowing in Lekima's eyes as it set down its pipe before approaching Han Li, but all of a sudden, it stopped in its tracks as a peculiar look appeared on its face.

Immediately thereafter, the white spirit domain around it faded away, and it flew away into the distance as a streak of white light, traveling at an astonishing speed.

Han Li was already prepared for a grueling battle, so it felt rather anticlimactic that Lekima had suddenly departed without any warning, and everyone else was also exchanging perplexed looks with one another.

However, Lekima's abrupt departure was certainly good news for them.

In particular, Lei Yuce's group was suffering from severe immortal spiritual power depletion in the wake of their battle against Lekima, and they eagerly took this opportunity to take some pills and recover.

"When did the three of you get here, Fellow Daoist Su?" Lei Yuce asked after taking some pills.

Su Anqian was looking into the distance, completely ignoring Lei Yuce, while Han Li offered no reply, either, seemingly lost in thought.

Jin Liu stepped in to respond to Lei Yuce's questions, giving him a brief recount of their journey up to this point. However, he made sure to omit certain details, such as the firefly hives that they had obtained and the Heavenly Water Sect elders that he had concealed within that spatial pagoda of his .

Han Li turned to Jin Liu with an intrigued look in his eyes upon seeing this.

He could understand Jin Liu keeping the matter of the firefly hives a secret, but it felt to him like Jin Liu had some type of ulterior motive for refraining to mention the elders in the spatial pagoda.

Jin Liu noticed Han Li's gaze, and he immediately looked back at Han Li with a hint of warning in his eyes.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, but ultimately looked away without exposing Jin Liu's omission.

Jin Liu was quite relieved to see this, and he continued chatting with Lei Yuce, asking him about his journey up to this point.

As it turned out, the experiences of Lei Yuce's group were quite similar to those of Han Li's group. They had also encountered many perils on the way here, gradually losing members as they went, and all that remained was this group of five.

With retreat no longer an option, they continued onward, searching for both a way out and potential opportunities.

Close to a day ago, they encountered Lan Yan, who was traveling on her own, and she joined their group, shortly following which they were attacked by Lekima.

Jin Liu was also rather skeptical about Lei Yuce's recount of events, but seeing as he had also kept many secrets from Lei Yuce, he was in no position to say anything.

A forlorn look appeared on his face as he sighed, "It looks like the Eon Pagoda is fraught with peril regardless of which path we chose. We entered the pagoda with hundreds of fellow daoists, yet there are fewer than ten of us left now."

Sullen looks also appeared on the faces of Lei Yuce and the others upon hearing this.

[1]. This is a play on words involving Typhoon Lekima, the fourth costliest typhoon in Chinese history. Its Chinese name (利奇马) ends in the character 马, which translates to horse, so this thing is basically a typhoon horse.

[Back]

Chapter 1070: Onward

"Fellow Daoist Lei, that Lekima has a very strange and unpredictable personality. Just because it's gone now doesn't mean that it won't suddenly come back to attack us again later. Hence, I think we should join forces and explore this Eon Pagoda together. What do you say?" Jin Liu proposed.

Lei Yuce was very happy to oblige with this suggestion, and he took an excited glance at Su Anqian as he immediately replied, "That would be fantastic! I'll be in your care then, Fellow Daoist Jin."

Everyone else in Lei Yuce's group had just witnessed the power of Jin Liu's trio, particularly the incredible power displayed by Han Li, so they naturally raised no objections to this, either.

Even though Lan Yan didn't want to travel with Han Li, she was only going to turn everyone against her by objecting to the proposal, so she chose to remain silent.

"In that case, let's set off right away, Fellow Daoist Lei," Jin Liu said with a smile.

Having had some time to rest and recuperate, everyone had already recovered somewhat, and thus, they continued onward.

In the wake of Lekima's departure, the howling winds sweeping through the area had already mostly subsided, so everyone was able to fly onward without much trouble.

However, everyone was rather apprehensive of another potential attack from Lekima, so they didn't dare to travel at full speed.

"Fellow Daoist Lei, you reached this level before us, have you managed to find the spatial door leading to the next level?" Su Anqian suddenly asked.

"Truth be told, we only arrived on this level not long ago, and we didn't get a chance to do much exploring before we encountered Lekima, so I'm afraid I know next to nothing about the layout of this level," Lei Yuce hurriedly replied, and Su Anqian fell silent upon hearing this.

Lei Yuce was ecstatic that Su Anqian had struck up a conversation with him, and he was just about to speak to her again when Han Li suddenly approached him and interjected, "Do you know anything about that Lekima from just now, Fellow Daoist Lei?"

Lei Yuce was rather displeased by Han Li's interjection, but he made sure not to display his displeasure as he asked, "What are you referring to specifically, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

"I'm sure you've also discovered at this point that this Eon Pagoda is a place where Immortal Lord Tai Sui kept certain powerful beings captive. Could it be that Lekima is the creature being held captive on this level? You fought it for quite some time, and it seemed very talkative, so I was thinking that perhaps you had managed to gather some useful information from it," Han Li replied.

"We were indeed locked in battle against Lekima for quite some time, and some conversation did take place between us, but it never spoke about its identity. However, judging from its immense powers, it most likely is the creature being held captive on this level," Lei Yuce replied as a hint of frustration welled up in his heart.

During their battle against Lekima, it had attempted to converse with them on multiple occasions, but they had ignored it in order to focus on the battle. If someone could've had the foresight to entertain its attempts at making conversation, then perhaps they would've been able to gather some useful information.

Of course, Lei Yuce certainly wasn't going to reveal this and make a fool out of himself in Su Anqian's presence.

Han Li nodded in response and didn't speak any further on the topic, and the group continued onward in silence.

Moments later, Su Anqian approached Han Li before asking through voice transmission, "What do you think of Lei Yuce's assessment of the situation, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

"Do you still recall those strands of white fur that we found on the fourth level?" Han Li asked.

A flash of recollection appeared in Su Anqian's eyes upon hearing this, and she immediately realized what Han Li was implying.

"Those strands of fur were quite similar to the hairs in Lekima's mane."

"They're not just similar, I'm certain that they're one and the same. I don't know why its fur appeared on the fourth level, but I think we should be prepared for the possibility that there's more than one powerful creature on this level," Han Li replied, and Su Anqian gave a thoughtful nod upon hearing this.

Lei Yuce was flying along up ahead, but he could detect the secret conversation taking place between Han Li and Su Anqian, and a hint of displeasure appeared in his eyes, only to vanish in a flash.

The group continued onward for a while longer when Jin Liu suddenly drew to a halt at hte forefront of the group.

Everyone else also stopped in their tracks upon seeing this, following which elated looks appeared on their faces at the sight that were greeted by.

Up ahead was a tall mountain that was rather strange in appearance in that it was segmented into two spherical halves that were stacked on top of one another, forming what appeared to be a massive gourd.

There was a cluster of connected dark green palaces at the foot of the mountain, forming what appeared to be an imperial city that was around twenty to thirty acres in area, and its layout was very similar to that of the clusters of palaces on the previous two levels.

With that in mind, it was very likely that the spatial door leading to the next level was situated in this cluster of palaces.

Even though this thought had occurred to everyone, no one descended toward the palaces.

If the spatial door really were here, then Lekima was most likely here as well, and no one wanted to confront it.

"Lekima only dared to take us on when we were separated into two groups, but as soon as we joined forces, it immediately fled in a panic, so I'm confident that there's nothing for us to fear even if we run into Lekima here! On top of that, I can see flashes of spiritual light in the palaces down below, indicating that there must be powerful treasures inside, so I say we go down there and do some exploring," Lei Yuce proposed.

Everyone was instilled with a sense of confidence upon hearing his analysis, and they were also tempted by the prospect of powerful treasures to be found in the palaces down below, so they quickly began to descend toward the foot of the mountain.

Before long, everyone had arrived in front of the outermost palace. Its gates were wide open, and there was a copper plaque hanging above its entrance with the words "Indelible Palace" inscribed upon it in large, golden characters.

As soon as they descended onto the ground below, everyone's expressions instantly changed slightly as they discovered that there was a burst of formidable restrictive power within this cluster of palaces.

The restriction had no impact on cultivation bases, but it severely restricted spiritual sense, and even with Han Li's tremendous spiritual sense, his spiritual sensory range had been reduced to no more than a thousand feet.

Lei Yuce was also slightly alarmed by this, but he had already rallied everyone to come here, so he couldn't turn back now. Hence, he mustered up his courage and strode into the palace as he declared, "It's just a spiritual sense restriction, there's nothing to be afraid of."

Despite what he was saying, he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a golden bowl immortal treasure that hovered above his head, releasing a layer of golden light to encompass his entire body.

Everyone else also summoned some protective immortal treasures before making their way into the palace behind Lei Yuce, only to discover that it was completely empty with the exception of a few pillars.

Thus, everyone quickly filed out of the palace through a side door, then continued their exploration.

There were many palaces in the area, and everyone was wary of the possibility of Lekima hiding in one of them, so they didn't dare to split up or travel too quickly.

Hence, even after half a day, they had only explored less than half of the area.

Thankfully, there were indeed some precious treasures in these palaces, so their efforts weren't unrewarded.

They hadn't encountered any danger this entire time, and even though they hadn't grown complacent, the tension in the ease had eased quite a bit.

The group passed through a long corridor before arriving in front of another palace, and this one was significantly larger than all of the previous ones.

On top of that, it was also extremely ornate and riddled with intricate engravings, indicating that it was no ordinary palace.

Having already reaped a great deal of spoils up to this point, everyone was feeling quite excited, and their eyes immediately lit up slightly at the sight of the palace before them.

The gates of this palace were also wide open, yet right as the group was about to enter, rays of blue light suddenly emerged around the palace, then converged to form a blue light barrier in their path.

Lei Yuce harrumphed coldly upon seeing this, and he flicked a finger through the air to release a streak of radiant, golden light.

Inside the streak of light was a golden flying sword that was curved like a snake, and it transformed into a ribbon of golden light that was several dozen feet in length before striking the blue light barrier with immense power.

The light barrier instantly rippled violently amid the sound of splashing water, but it was able to keep the ribbon of golden light at bay.

Lei Yuce was not very pleased to see his attack being withstood so easily, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release six golden scimitars that hurtled toward the blue light barrier in unison, while the golden flying sword from before also came swooping down once again.

"Let's break this restriction together, fellow daoists!" Wen Zhong yelled as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a streak of golden light that hurtled directly toward the blue light barrier, and everyone else immediately sprang into action as well.

In the blink of an eye, the blue light barrier was inundated by a ferocious barrage of attacks, and before long, it was shattered with a dull thump, following which everyone withdrew their immortal treasures before entering the palace.

All of a sudden, a hint of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart, but it only lingered for an instant before fading away, and he couldn't tell if it was just a false sense of foreboding resulting from excessive apprehension.

He shook his head to rid himself of those thoughts, then entered the palace at the very rear end of the group.

The space within the palace was quite large, around four hundred to five hundred feet in size, and it was completely empty with the exception of some stone pillars and a rectangular stone table at the very back of the palace.

The stone table appeared to be an offering table, and placed at its center was a golden tablet with some strange text inscribed upon it, text that was unfamiliar even to Han Li.

On top of that, there were many other items on the offering table, and they were very much a welcome sight for everyone.

Chapter 1071: Exchange

In addition to the tablet, there were a total of nine items on the offering table, all of which were spirit materials that were giving off astonishing aura fluctuations.

"That black lotus flower is the Tranquil Water Immortal Lotus, one of the ten immortal lotus flowers of the True Immortal Realm! Consuming it can significantly enhance one's cultivation base and grant one a Tranquil Water Immortal Physique, allowing them to master the laws of water far easier than the average cultivator!"

"That's Heavenly Vajra Diamond, a premium metal-attribute spirit material that can be used to refine immortal treasures with unmatched offensive prowess!"

"Is that a vial of True Profound Essence? It's so pure, and there's so much of it, enough for two people to progress to the Great Encompassment Stage!"

Everyone quickly erupted into a frenzy at the sight of the spirit materials on the table, and a flash of excitement also appeared in Han Li's eyes at the alluring sight, but his brows then furrowed slightly as he glanced at the walls and ground around the stone table.

Jin Liu was staring intently at the Tranquil Water Immortal Lotus and the Heavenly Vajra Diamond beside it with a fervent look in his eyes, yet right as he was about to approach the table, Han Li suddenly appeared in his path.

"What do you think you're doing?"

Jin Liu came under the false impression that Han Li was going to fight over the Tranquil Water Immortal Lotus with him, and a dark look instantly appeared on his face as he prepared to make a rush for the lotus flower.

"Take a look at what's around the stone table before you do anything rash," Han Li said in an indifferent manner, and Jin Liu reflexively did as he was told, upon which his expression instantly changed slightly.

There were seven dark red designs engraved onto the walls around the stone table, each of which was around a foot in size and appeared to have already been here for countless years.

The seven designs seemed to be depicting seven deities, but all of them were quite sinister in appearance, indicating that they were unorthodox, malicious deities.

Furthermore, the seven designs were arranged over the walls and the ground in a certain pattern, but due to their red coloration, they blended into the dark red material of the walls, thereby making them barely visible.

After hearing what Han Li had to say, everyone else also quickly noticed the seven designs on the walls.

"It looks like some type of restriction," Wen Zhong remarked as he examined the seven designs, while everyone else exchanged blank glances with one another, and it seemed that no one recognized these designs.

"There's only one way to find out!" Jin Liu said as he swept a sleeve through the air.

"Don't be rash, Jin Liu!" Su Anqian hurriedly called out, but it was already too late, and a streak of blue light flew out of Jin Liu's sleeve before sweeping toward the stone table.

As soon as the streak of blue light approached the stone table, the seven designs around it instantly began to glow with radiant, crimson light, conjuring a crimson light barrier.

At the same time, a large head belonging to one of the seven malicious deities appeared over the light barrier, and it opened its mouth to devour the streak of blue light.

After devouring the streak of blue light, the head let loose a menacing roar at Han Li and the others, looking as if it wanted to struggle free from the confines of the crimson light barrier to devour them.

A burst of violent intent erupted out of the head, and it was transmitted directly into the minds of everyone present.

Everyone instantly felt themselves seeing red as horrific scenes of mountainous piles of bodies and vast rivers of blood surfaced in their minds, while boundless killing intent converged toward their souls.

Thankfully, everyone present possessed lofty cultivation bases and sufficiently powerful spiritual sense to quickly dispel the killing intent.

The head of the malicious deity roared a few more times, but it was ultimately unable to struggle free from the crimson light barrier, and it quickly faded away, shortly following which the light barrier itself also disappeared.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this.

He didn't recognize this crimson array, but it appeared to him that this was a very similar array to the Weeping Blood Array in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, except it was more offensively oriented.

Having said that, he still had no idea how to unravel it.

"It looks like accessing the treasures inside is going to be quite difficult with this array in the way," Lei Yuce mused.

"There's nothing to be worried about! With so many of us here, I'm sure we can just break this array by force!" Jin Liu harrumphed coldly as he swept a greedy gaze over the precious treasures laid out on the stone table.

The method proposed by Jin Liu was a bit barbaric, but everyone nodded in agreement.

This was the simplest way to proceed, and they couldn't afford to waste too much time here.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

Even though he didn't know what this crimson array was, he had a feeling that trying to break it with brute force was not a good idea.

All of a sudden, Lan Yan interjected, "If you want to secure the treasures inside, then I suggest you don't do that."

Everyone turned to Lan Yan with surprised expressions upon hearing this, while Lei Yuce asked in an ecstatic manner, "Do you recognize this array, Fellow Daoist Lan?"

"I'm somewhat well-versed in the art of arrays, and I just so happened to see some records pertaining to this array in an ancient scripture. This array is called the Seven Blood Deity Array, and it contains the power of seven malicious deities.

“If you try to break the array with brute force, the power of those seven malicious deities will self-detonate within the array. I don't know how powerful the resulting explosion will be, but it'll definitely be enough to destroy all of the treasures inside," Lan Yan replied.

Everyone's expressions changed drastically upon seeing this, and a hint of lingering fear surfaced in Jin Liu's eyes as he realized that his rash decision had almost led to the destruction of all of the treasures on the stone table.

The Tranquil Water Immortal Lotus had perfect affinity with the cultivation art that he was using, and he was confident that it would allow him to break through his current bottleneck.

On top of that, he had been also searching for Heavenly Vajra Diamonds for countless years, and he had been hoping that a Heavenly Vajra Diamond or two would've been present on the first level, within that space that was filled with abundant metal-attribute spiritual qi.

The reason why he had tried to target Han Li on the second level was precisely because he suspected that Han Li could be in possession of this material, so he was ecstatic to see it here.

"If you recognize this array, then I'm sure you also know the way to bypass it as well, right, Fellow Daoist Lan?" Lei Yuce asked.

"You want me to unravel this array for no compensation?" Lan Yan asked as she raised an eyebrow.

Lei Yuce faltered slightly upon hearing this, then immediately proposed, "How about this? As compensation for breaking the array, you can choose one of the treasures on the stone table ahead of everyone else."

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon hearing this, but no one raised any objections.

"I can break this Seven Blood Deity Array, but I don't want any of the treasures inside. Instead, I want something else," Lan Yan said as she turned her gaze to Han Li.

"What would you like in return, Fellow Daoist Lan?" Lei Yuce asked.

"My senior martial brother is currently being held captive by Fellow Daoist Shi, and I want him returned to me," Lan Yan declared.

A surprised look appeared on Lei Yuce's face as he also turned his gaze to Han Li upon hearing this, and everyone else immediately turned their attention to Han Li as well.

Han Li immediately realized that Lan Yan was taking advantage of this opportunity to try and use everyone's collective power to force him into releasing Lan Yuanzi.

He remained silent as he stood with his hands clasped behind his back, and he couldn't help but wonder how Lan Yan knew that he had held Lan Yuanzi captive instead of killing him.

"Is that true, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Lei Yuce asked as he turned to Han Li.

"It is. Fellow Daoist Lan and her senior martial brother attacked me on a previous level in the pagoda, and I was able to defeat them before capturing her senior martial brother," Han Li replied.

Lei Yuce had guessed that some conflict had to have arisen between the three of them, but he hadn't anticipated it to be this severe, and his heart immediately sank slightly.

"I don't know what personal differences there are between the three of you, but right now, we're all in the same boat, so we need to work together. Would you be able to release Fellow Daoist Lan's senior martial brother, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Lei Yuce asked in an earnest manner.

"The two of them have a vendetta against me and are determined to hunt me down. What if they come after me again after I release her senior martial brother?" Han Li asked in a cold manner.

Lei Yuce felt this to be a reasonable concern, and he turned to Lan Yan with slightly furrowed brows.

"As long as you release my senior martial brother, I can swear a vow that we won't come after you again for as long as we're in this secret area. Besides, you're far more powerful than the two of us, so it would be foolish of us to try and oppose you," Lan Yan immediately declared.

"I have no trust in flimsy things like vows. Even an inner demon vow can be bypassed. I'm not going to place my safety in the hands of others, so don't bring up this matter again," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

Even though he had managed to defeat Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan, he had a feeling that there was still going to be more trouble to come from the Nine Origins Temple, and that was why he had captured Lan Yuanzi instead of killing him.

With the trump card of Lan Yuanzi up his sleeve, Lan Yan wouldn't dare to do anything to him,so there was no way he would hand Lan Yuanzi over to her so easily.

Jin Liu was desperate to break the array, and he had always harbored some distaste for Han Li, so he naturally sided with Lan Yan as he declared, "Fellow Daoist Shi, Fellow Daoist Lan has already put her sincerity on full display, so as a man, you shouldn't be too petty. On top of that, your refusal to hand over her senior martial brother is actively hindering everyone from accessing those treasures, so I strongly advise you to reconsider for the greater good."

A cold look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

He had saved Jin Liu prior to this, yet not only was he not grateful at all, he was now biting the hand that had previously fed him.

Chapter 1072: Refining Law Threads

"Are you trying to pressure me into complying, Fellow Daoist Jin?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"You can settle your personal differences once you leave this secret area. Right now, time is of the essence here in the Eon Pagoda. Besides, with so many of us here, you don't have to worry about anyone coming after you," Jin Liu countered in a cold voice.

"In that case, let's part ways here. All of you can go one way, while I'll go the other. If you want to make me comply by force, then I invite you to try," Han Li replied in an equally hostile manner.

"Let's not make any rash decisions, Fellow Daoist Shi," Lei Yuce hurriedly interjected. "I understand that this is a lot to ask of you, so how about this? Seeing as Fellow Daoist Lan has relinquished the right to have the first pick of the treasures on the stone table, you can have that right instead. Will that suffice as compensation?"

Wen Zhong and the others also chimed in to try and persuade him, and it was clear that in the wake of Han Li's display of power in the previous battle, they didn't dare to try and make him comply by force.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then said, "I can release Fellow Daoist Lan's senior martial brother, but I don't want any of the treasures on the stone table. Instead, I also want something else."

Lei Yuce was naturally very happy to hear that Han Li didn't want any of the treasures on the table, and he immediately asked, "What would you like instead, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

"If you want me to release your senior martial brother, then you'll have to give me a Fire Age Firefly hive in exchange," Han Li declared as he turned to Lan Yan, and Jin Liu's expression immediately stiffened slightly upon hearing this.

"What's that? I don't have one," Lan Yan asked with a perplexed expression.

"You may not have one, but someone else does," Han Li replied as he turned to Jin Liu with a hint of a smile on his face.

"What is the meaning of this, Shi Mu?" Jin Liu snapped in a furious voice.

Fire Age Firefly hives were extremely precious, and they were also very useful to him, so he was naturally very reluctant to comply.

"I'm just proposing a trade. Weren't you just saying that we shouldn't be so petty, and that we should make some personal sacrifices for the greater good? Surely you should practice what you preach, right, Fellow Daoist Jin?" Han Li shrugged.

Jin Liu wasn't anticipating having his own words used against him, and he could only glower at Han Li in silence.

Lan Yan was ecstatic to hear that Han Li was finally willing to release Lan Yuanzi, and she hurriedly turned to Jin Liu as she urged, "Please give me your Fire Age Firefly hive, Fellow Daoist Jin. I'm willing to purchase it from you with Immortal Origin Stones or offer up other precious materials in exchange."

"What do you say, Fellow Daoist Jin?" Lei Yuce asked with a hint of a threatening tone in his voice.

Jin Liu's powers were far inferior to Han Li's, so Lei Yuce felt no qualms exerting pressure upon him.

Jin Liu's expression darkened significantly upon hearing this, but a plan then seemed to have occurred to him, and he smiled as he said, "I can hand over the Fire Age Firefly nest, but there's no need for any compensation from Fellow Daoist Lan. Instead, I want to have the first pick of the treasures on the stone table."

The Fire Age Firefly hive was indeed extremely precious, but not as important to him as the treasures within the array.

Lei Yuce exchanged a few glances with everyone else, then decided that this was an acceptable trade.

With everything settled, Han Li didn't waste any more time as he swept a sleeve through the air to release Lan Yuanzi amid a flash of silver light, and he fell to the ground, still in an unconscious state.

Lan Yuanzi hurriedly rushed over to his side before picking him up from the ground.

The two of them were cultivating a law power fusion secret technique, and even though they hadn't fully mastered the secret technique yet, a special connection had formed between them, allowing them to detect whether the other was dead or alive.

Even though Lan Yan was aware that Lan Yuanzi was still alive, she had been feeling very uneasy this entire time, knowing that he had fallen into Han Li's hands, and now that he had been returned to her, she couldn't help but weep with joy.

At the same time, she swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of blue light to inspect Lan Yuanzi's internal condition.

Han Li paid no heed to the two of them as he strode over to Jin Liu, who harrumphed coldly before summoning his Fire Age Firefly hive, which was giving off tremendous law power fluctuations.

With the exceptions of Su Anqian, Jin Liu, and Han Li, this was everyone's first time seeing a Fire Age Firefly hive, and they couldn't help but be stunned by the tremendous time law powers that it harbored.

Furthermore, Jin Liu was intentionally making his movements very slow and methodical to ensure that everyone could get a close look.

Han Li could see what Jin Liu was doing, but he didn't care, and he promptly stowed the hive away.

Now that all three hives had fallen into his possession, all he had to do was find a safe place to refine them into time law threads, and his time law powers would be greatly enhanced, presumably allowing him to unleash that same ability that had driven Qi Mozi away.

With that in mind, a hint of excitement welled up in Han Li's heart, and he decided there and then that he had to refine the three hives right away.

As long as he could unleash that ability again, he was confident in his own ability to deal with any threat, whether it be Lekima, Qi Mozi, or anyone else.

With his mind made up, he quickly inspected his surroundings, then began to make his way toward a side door in the palace.

Right at this moment, Lan Yan turned to him with an accusatory look in her eyes as she asked, "Hey, why is my senior martial brother still unconscious? What have you done to him?"

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air in an expressionless manner, releasing a streak of golden light that vanished into Lan Yuanzi's body in a flash.

A layer of golden light instantly appeared over his body before fading away again, following which his eyelids slowly fluttered open.

"Are you alright, Senior Martial Brother?" Lan Yan asked with an ecstatic smile.

"Where are we right now?" Lan Yuanzi asked in a feeble voice upon catching sight of Lan Yan.

Meanwhile, Han Li continued to make his way toward the side door.

"Where are you going, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Su Anqian hurriedly asked.

"I have some matters to take care of, so I'll be leaving for a bit. You can all split the treasures on the stone table without me," Han Li replied, then promptly departed.

Beyond the side door was an empty hall, and after sweeping his spiritual sense briefly throughout the hall, Han Li gave a satisfied nod before sweeping both sleeves through the air, releasing numerous streaks of light throughout the entire hall.

Everyone was quite alarmed by Han Li's sudden departure, and they were relieved to see that he had only gone into a side hall instead of truly departing.

With the power that Han Li had displayed, he had become an indispensable member of the group, and no one was confident that they would be able to take on the likes of Lekima without Han Li with them.

Standing at the edge of the crowd were Xiong Shan and the black-robed duo, but all three of them were Golden Immortals, and they had kept a low profile the entire way here, so no one paid any attention to them.

"Is this the place?" the black-robed woman asked through voice transmission.

The black-robed young man closed his eyes momentarily as if he were sensing something, following which an excited look appeared on his face as he opened his eyes and replied, "It's this level! There's no mistaking it!"

"Don't get excited too soon! According to my knowledge, what you're trying to accomplish is not an easy task. Will you be able to get it done?" the black-robed woman asked.

The black-robed young man seemed to be a little displeased by the woman's skepticism, and he harrumphed, "I wouldn't have brought you here if I wasn't confident."

"Good. If you end up dying here, it'll be difficult for me to do what I need to do on my own," the black-robed woman said with a smile, and the black-robed young man gave another harrumph before closing his eyes again.

Instead of continuing to converse with her companion, the black-robed woman turned to the side hall with a peculiar look in her eyes.

Xiong Shan also currently had his gaze fixed on the side hall, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

Meanwhile, Lan Yan fed a pill to Lan Yuanzi, and the latter's complexion instantly improved slightly as he rose to his feet.

"Fellow Daoist Lan, now that your senior martial brother has been returned to you, let's begin breaking this restriction," Lei Yuce said, and Lan Yan raised no objections to this.

......

In the side hall, Han Li made a hand seal, and several layers of light barriers rose up all around him.

After that, he opened the Flower Branch domain before making his way inside.

At this moment, the bamboo pavilion in the domain was completely encompassed within an enormous ball of churning, black energy.

The black ball was giving off astonishing ghostly power, and all of the plants within several thousand feet of the pavilion were long dead. Thankfully, the medicine garden was far enough to remain unaffected.

Han Li knew that this was the result of Weeping Soul's inability to control the overflowing ghostly power in her body as she refined Ghost King Wu Chao.

He swept a sleeve through the air to release several dozen streaks of golden light, which formed a golden light barrier around the pavilion, and all of the churning ghostly power was instantly confined by the time law powers within the light barrier.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this. This was a set of time-attribute array flags that he had refined in the past, and it was working quite well here.

He then swept his sleeve through the air one more time to release the Essence Fire Raven before instructing, "Go and guard the entrance of the domain for me. If anyone attempts to come in, kill them."

The Essence Fire Raven let loose a clear cry in response, flew away toward the entrance of the Flower Branch domain.

Only then did Han Li sit down onto a vacant area in the domain, following which he summoned the three firefly hives.

After that, he took a deep breath, then began channeling his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

Chapter 1073: Drastic Increase

The five time-attribute law treasures appeared around him one after another, then began slowly circling around his body.

A series of time law threads emerged from the five law treasures, then wove themselves together to form a rapidly revolving golden vortex.

Han Li took a deep breath, then began chanting an incantation, and the vortex instantly began to contract at his behest.

A burst of incredibly formidable time law power fluctuations spread through the area as all of the golden light and time law threads within the golden vortex collapsed inward, forming a golden ring.

Han Li had manifested this golden ring on many past occasions, but this time, things seemed to be a little different.

While the golden ring was taking shape, the words in the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra were flowing through his mind with an unprecedented level of clarity, and in that instant, he was able to gain a deeper understanding of the secrets of the laws of time laid out in the cultivation art.

At the same time, the time law power within his body was beginning to stir, as if it were about to undergo some type of change, but all of a sudden, this feeling of enlightenment and clarity faded away, and the time law powers settled down again.

What was that?

Han Li attempted to make sense of what had just happened to him, but to no avail, and in the end, he cast this train of thought aside before returning his attention to the task at hand.

The golden ring flew forward through the air at his behest, then abruptly swelled to several times its original size before closing itself around one of the hives.

The ring was revolving rapidly while giving off resplendent golden light, and it was also releasing a burst of powerful suction force that enveloped the hive from all directions.

The hive began to crackle and pop as if it had been set alight, and balls of golden light flew out of it before vanishing into the golden ring.

The golden ring shuddered slightly before releasing a translucent, golden thread, which circled around Han Li a few times before wrapping itself around the Time Severing Torch.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, and he redoubled his efforts.

The golden light radiating from the ring became brighter and brighter, and it began to extract time law powers from the hive at a faster rate before converting it into time law threads.

One time law thread surged out of the golden ring after another before flying onto the Time Severing Torch, while the Fire Age Firefly hive shrank down rapidly, completely vanishing in a short span of time.

At this point, there were already fifty-two time law threads circling around the Time Severing Torch, giving off incredibly formidable time law power fluctuations.

Just as Han Li had anticipated, the hive contained no less time law power than himself, and after refining just a single hive, the number of time law threads in his possession had doubled!

All of a sudden, he could feel a vast abundance of time law powers in his body, and he was confident that he would be able to unleash that time-reversal ability again.

With this huge influx of time law threads, his five time-attribute law treasures had completely recovered, and they were glowing even brighter than before.

In particular, not only was his Time Severing Torch glowing radiantly, it seemed to have swelled slightly in size as well.

Han Li forcibly suppressed his excitement as he quickly moved onto the second hive, and the golden ring closed itself around the hive to absorb the time law powers inside.

Close to an hour flew by in the blink of an eye, and the other two hives had also been fully refined and converted into over a hundred time law threads.

At this point, there were over a hundred and sixty time law threads wrapped around the Time Severing Torch, and it had become around 30% larger than before and much more substantial in appearance.

The time law powers in Han Li's body had also swelled by severalfold, to the point that he was having a little trouble controlling it.

The vast abundance of time law power was churning throughout his body, but it didn't cause him any pain or discomfort.

After taking a moment to acclimate himself to his newfound powers, Han Li withdrew his time-attribute law treasures, then began channeling his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra to rein in the time law powers in his body.

Several hours later, he rose to his feet, and the time law power in his body was already completely under control.

Even though he hadn't tried to unleash the time-reversal ability again, he was confident that he was definitely capable of doing so at this moment.

"I wonder if they've already broken the restriction outside," Han Li murmured to himself, then turned to take a glance at the bamboo pavilion.

Weeping Soul was still refining Ghost King Wu Chao's ghostly power inside, so Han Li didn't disturb her as he rose up into the and flew out of the Flower Branch domain.

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air to recover all of the array tools laid out in the side hall, following which he made his way back into the main hall.

As soon as he did so, he was immediately greeted by the sight of a burst of radiant blue and crimson light.

After taking a moment to assess the situation before him, he discovered that there was a giant, square, blue array on the ground in the main hall, within which were seven smaller, circular arrays arranged in an arc within the main array.

At this moment, Lan Yan, Lei Yuce, Wen Zhong, the black-robed duo, Jin Liu, and Xiong Shan were seated in the array, with each of them occupying one of the circular arrays.

Meanwhile, Lan Yuanzi and Su Anqian were standing on lookout duty outside the blue array.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, you're back!" Su Anqian exclaimed with an elated expression at the sight of Han Li's return.

However, her expression then stiffened slightly as she began to carefully observe Han Li with a hint of bewilderment in her eyes.

He had only been gone for less than half a day, yet some type of massive change seemed to have taken place within him.

Meanwhile, Lan Yuanzi was looking at Han Li with a slightly awkward look on his face.

Han Li gave the two a nod of acknowledgment, then turned his gaze into the array, where Lan Yan and the others were making rapid strings of hand seals, while radiant blue light surged into the crimson light barrier from the array.

The blue light was filled with countless blue runes that contained water law powers, and they were flowing into the crimson light barrier with a dull rumble, much like the sound of crashing waves.

A string of ghastly howls rang out within the light barrier as the seven malicious deities emerged in unison, then swept their hands through the air to release bursts of viscous crimson light to oppose the blue light.

The crimson light was able to tear through the blue light before striking the blue array, but Lan Yan remained calm and composed despite this, seemingly having anticipated this outcome.

She chanted an incantation while making a rapid string of hand seals, then swiped her fingers over her wrists, and two jets of blood instantly spurted out of her wrists before fusing into the blue array.

Immediately thereafter, the array turned crimson in color, and the law power fluctuations that it was giving off also abruptly turned from the water attribute to the blood attribute.

A look of intrigue and surprise appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. This was the first time he had seen this type of law power transition.

The attacks from the seven malicious deities struck the crimson array, but not only did the attacks not do any damage, they fused into the array instead.

At the same time, numerous tendrils of crimson light shot out of the array before wrapping themselves around the seven malicious deities like lightning.

Immediately thereafter, everyone in the array switched to different hand seals in unison, and the crimson tendrils transformed into seven crimson rings around the malicious deities.

Waves of crimson light that were filled with countless crimson runes surged out of the rings, releasing incredibly formidable restrictive power that completely immobilized the seven malicious deities.

Lan Yan was ecstatic to see this, and she swept a sleeve through the air to summon a crimson badge, which released a plume of threads of crimson light at her behest.

These were blood law threads, and there were around fifty to sixty of them, all of which fused into the crimson array.

The array began to rumble violently as a series of giant, crimson runes that were each over ten feet in diameter surged out from within before striking the opposing light barrier, which quickly began to thin out.

In the face of the threat posed by Lan Yan's array, the seven malicious deities let loose a collective roar as a layer of liquid-like crimson light appeared over their bodies.

At the same time, a violent aura of malice erupted out of their bodies, one that was far more potent than what had been released by the head of that malicious deity from earlier, and it forced its way directly into the minds of everyone present, completely bypassing the protective spiritual light around them.

Han Li's body was also infiltrated by this malicious aura, and he was greeted by a horrific sight of a boundless sea of blood and vast mountains of mutilated bodies.

However, the time law powers in his body then sprang into action on their own, expeling this burst of malicious law powers to restore his lucidity, but the others were not so fortunate.

At this moment, Xiong Shan's eyes had turned bright red, and his entire body was trembling uncontrollably as if he had been possessed.

Jin Liu, Wen Zhong, and Lan Yuanzi's eyes had also taken on a red coloration, and they were letting loose animalistic snarls, but the hints of lucidity in their eyes indicated that they hadn't completely succumbed to the malicious influence in their bodies.

Lan Yan, Su Anqian, and Lei Yuce were more powerful than the rest, so they were less severely affected, and the law powers in their bodies had already begun eradicating the malicious aura acting upon them.

Right at this moment, Han Li directed his gaze toward the black-robed duo in the array.

Chapter 1074: Illusions

Even though the two of them had also been affected by this malicious aura, they were able to recover only slightly slower than Han Li.

However, in the instant that the two of them shrugged off the malicious influence, they exchanged a glance with one another, following which a layer of crimson light resurfaced in their eyes as they pretended to still be under the influence.

These minor details weren't able to escape Han Li's notice, but he didn't expose them.

With the seven people operating the array falling under the influence of the malicious aura, the light emanating from the array immediately dimmed, and the restrictive forces acting upon the seven malicious deities abated significantly.

The seven malicious deities roared to the heavens as they began to struggle with renewed vigor, and a string of loud cracks rang out as a series of cracks appeared on the seven crimson rings.

At this point, Lan Yan and Lei Yuce had already completely shrugged off the influence of the malicious aura, and alarmed looks immediately appeared on their faces upon seeing this.

However, everyone else was still currently under the influence, and the array couldn't be operated by just her and Lei Yuce alone, so there was nothing that they could do.

All of a sudden, a burst of radiant golden light descended from above, forming a ring of golden radiance around the seven malicious deities. Countless golden ripples surged out of the ring of light, and the struggles of the malicious deities instantly ceased.

Han Li then appeared within the ring of golden light before sweeping a sleeve through the air, releasing five streaks of golden light that vanished into the bodies of Xiong Shan and the others.

The bursts of golden light contained tremendous time law powers that instantly eradicated the remnants of the malicious auras in their bodies, and with that, the seven cultivators were able to regain control of the array, restoring the strength of the rings around the bodies of the seven malicious deities.

Lan Yan immediately opened her mouth to release a ball of blood essence into the crimson badge before her, and the law threads on the badge lit up before releasing another flurry of giant, crimson runes that struck the light barrier up ahead.

A string of resounding booms rang out as the crimson light barrier shuddered violently before being torn apart, following which it disintegrated into specks of crimson light.

Han Li withdrew the ring of golden light upon seeing this, and the seven malicious deities let loose a collective roar of indignation as their bodies also exploded into specks of crimson light.

"Thank you for your help, Fellow Daoist Shi!" Lan Yan said as she stood up and turned to Han Li with a grateful expression.

Han Li was just about to reply when there was an abrupt eruption of activity as Lei Yuce, Wen Zhong, Jin Liu, and Su Anqian launched themselves at the exposed stone table in unison.

The four of them each reached out before making a grabbing motion, conjuring up four giant hand projections that made a grab for the treasures on the stone table.

The table was instantly shattered into pieces amid a resounding boom, while the treasures were scattered in all directions before being claimed by the four hand projections.

Out of the nine treasures, Wen Zhong, Jin Liu, and Su Anqian had each claimed two, while Lei Yuce had managed to claim three.

The four of them had pounced like lightning, and only now did everyone else realize what had just happened.

"What are you doing? Didn't we agree to split these treasures evenly?" Xiong Shan asked with a dark expression.

The black-robed duo didn't say anything, but they were clearly not very happy, either.

"With your paltry cultivation bases, what right do you have to split these treasures evenly with us?" Jin Liu sneered, then turned an excited gaze to the two treasures that he had claimed, namely the Tranquil Water Immortal Lotus and the Heavenly Vajra Diamond.

Xiong Shan was furious to hear this, and his hands balled up into tight fists up his sleeves, but in the end, all he could do was lower his head in silence.

Lei Yuce exchanged a glance with Su Anqian, and the two of them each sent a treasure flying through the air, offering them to Han Li and Lan Yan as Lei Yuce said, "Fellow Daoist Lan, Fellow Daoist Shi, it was all thanks to the two of you that we were able to bypass this Seven Blood Deity Array, so even though you two have passed up the treasures here, I think you still deserve one each."

A glimmer of purple light flashed through Han Li's eyes, following which he swept a sleeve through the air to return the treasure being offered to him as he said, "There's no need for that, I'm already satisfied with the firefly hives I received earlier."

"I'm also content with having my senior martial brother returned to me," Lan Yan said as she returned her treasure as well.

"In that case, I won't force the issue. It looks like there are many treasures in this place, so I'm sure there will be more spoils to be reaped," Lei Yuce said with a smile, and he was just about to stow his claimed treasures away when all of a sudden, the three treasures in his hands suddenly disintegrated into three translucent, gray threads.

A flabbergasted look instantly appeared on his face upon seeing this, and before he had a chance to react, the three gray threads pounced at him like a trio of springing vipers.

Before Lei Yuce had a chance to react, the three gray threads pierced through the protective golden light around him before vanishing into his body, and the same thing had happened with the treasures claimed by Su Anqian and the others as well.

The four of them immediately fell to their knees as they threw their hands onto their heads, and they began to tremble uncontrollably while letting loose horrific cries of agony.

Everyone was very much taken aback to see this, and in the next instant, they immediately sprang back in retreat to open up some distance between themselves and the four affected individuals.

Han Li had been tempted to accept the treasure offered to him by Lei Yuce earlier, but his Infernal Devilish Eyes had tipped him off to the fact that there was something amiss about it, and that was why he had refused to accept it.

All of a sudden, the agonized cries of Lei Yuce and the others began to subside, and their pupils were rapidly turning gray as their bodies also ceased trembling.

"They've fallen under someone's control!" Lan Yan exclaimed as she swept a sleeve toward the four of them, releasing a burst of blue light that formed a blue dome over them.

The dome seemed to have been woven out of some type of special thread, and it was several hundred feet in size.

Every single thread was giving off a burst of rippling, blue light, and tens of thousands of waves of blue light immediately converged toward the Lei Yuce and the others from all directions.

At this point, the pupils of Lei Yuce and the others had already completely turned gray, and Su Anqian and Jin Liu raised their hands in unison to release four streaks of blue light, within which were two long, blue halberds and two large, blue flags.

The four immortal treasures intertwined with one another to form an enormous ball of blue light that opposed the descent of the blue dome, while Lei Yuce and Wen Zhong pounced at Han Li and the others.

Countless streaks of golden sword qi erupted out of their bodies before raining down upon Han Li and the others, and even before the streaks of sword qi had fully descended, countless gashes had already been sliced the walls and the ground, and the surrounding space was also trembling violently.

Xiong Shan, the black-robed duo, and Lan Yuanzi hurriedly sprang into action to defend themselves, and only with the four of them joining forces were they just barely able to ward off the attacks from Lei Yuce and Wen Zhong.

However, the shockwaves from their clashes were too much for the palace to endure, and it quickly collapsed into ruins.

With the confines of the palace removed, everyone flew up into the air, where they were able to fight more freely, and a fierce battle ensued.

Lan Yan was opposing Su Anqian and Jin Liu on her own, while Xiong Shan and the others were facing Lei Yuce and Wen Zhong.

In their current state, it seemed that Lei Yuce and the others weren't able to unleash their full power, so even though Lan Yan and the others were on the back foot, they were able to hold their own just fine.

"Who's sneaking around here? Come out!" Han Li yelled as he hovered in mid-air while scouring his surroundings with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

"Oh? Are those Infernal Devilish Eyes I see? I didn't think I would be seeing a devilish ocular ability here. Looks like I'm going to have another powerful illusion servant!"

A lazy voice had rung out in the nearby space, but it was echoing in all directions, as if there were countless people speaking at once, making it impossible to ascertain exactly where the voice was coming from.

Han Li wasn't able to identify the source of the voice, either, but he could tell that it didn't belong to Lekima, and his heart immediately sank a little.

Could it be that there really was more than just one fugitive being held captive on this level?

"Why are you sneaking around despite your powers? Are you afraid to show yourself?" Han Li yelled.

"You think you can goad me into coming out? What do you take me for, a three-year-old child? If you want me to show myself, then you'll have to make me!" the voice chortled.

"In that case, I'll do just that!" Han Li said as a faint smile appeared on his face, following which he reached out in a certain direction before making a grabbing motion, and a thick bolt of golden lightning sprang out of the palm of his hand before striking a spot several hundred feet away.

A deafening thunderclap rang out as the space there rippled violently, following which a middle-aged man appeared out of thin air with a surprised look on his face.

The man was dressed in a long, azure robe, and he had a set of gentle facial features, but his eyes were a pair of pupilless gray blurs, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

The golden lightning nearby still hadn't faded, and all of it converged toward the middle-aged man.

However, the man remained completely unfazed as he casually swept a sleeve through the air, and all of the surrounding golden lightning was eradicated by a burst of invisible force before it could reach him.

Chapter 1075: Breaking the Illusion

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing how easily the man was able to eradicate his Divine Devilbane Lightning.

At the same time, a peculiar look appeared on his face.

He was certain that this was the first time that he had ever seen this man, but for some reason, the man struck him with an inexplicable sense of familiarity, as if they had met somewhere before.

What Han Li failed to notice was that the black-robed young man, who was still locked in battle against Lei Yuce and Wen Zhong, was suddenly looking very excited at the sight of the middle-aged man.

"How were you able to find me?" the middle-aged man asked.

"Who are you, and why did you set this trap for us?" Han Li countered with a question of his own.

"Looks like neither of us wants to answer the other's questions. How about this? Let's take turns answering a question each?" the man proposed.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and seeing as Lan Yan and the others were holding their own just fine for now, he agreed to this proposal.

"I'll let you go first," the man said in a generous fashion.

"Who are you?" Han Li asked.

"I've already been trapped here for countless years, so even if I tell you my name, you won't have heard of it. I'm just a fugitive held captive in this pagoda," the man replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this ambiguous answer, but this did confirm to him that the man was indeed a fugitive being held on this level.

"My turn. Who are all of you, and how did you get here?" the man asked.

"We are all from the Golden Origin Immortal Region, and we stumbled upon Immortal Lord Tai Sui's cave abode by chance, so we came in to search for treasures," Han Li replied.

"You're saying Tai Sui's cave abode has emerged?" the man asked as a look of surprise and elation appeared on his face.

"It's my turn to be asking a question, is it not?" Han Li countered.

A hint of fury flashed through the man's eyes, but he suppressed it as he acquiesced, "Fine, go ahead."

"How many other fugitives outside of yourself are on this level of the Eon Pagoda?" Han Li asked.

The middle-aged man immediately burst into laughter upon hearing this.

"What's so funny?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

The man's laughter subsided, following which he scoffed, "Do you think I would answer such a question?"

"Does that mean you're no longer willing to continue this exchange of questions and answers?" Han Li asked.

"I've already stalled for enough time, so there's no need for me to continue this pointless game," the man replied with a sinister smile, and at the same time, countless rays of gray light erupted out of his eyes.

An alarmed look appeared on Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he immediately averted his eyes as a burst of bright, golden light appeared over his body, but his efforts proved to be futile, and in the next instant, he found himself in a murky, gray space.

The surrounding palace had suddenly vanished, as had everyone in it.

"Is this an illusion?" Han Li murmured to himself.

After taking a moment to compose himself, his hands balled up into tight fists, and arcs of golden lightning sprang out of his body to form a suit of lightning armor, giving him the appearance of a mighty lightning deity.

Immediately thereafter, he swept a sleeve through the air to summon thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, all of which were releasing arcs of radiant, golden lightning and incredibly formidable lightning law power fluctuations.

The thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords then shot forth at his behest, sweeping toward the surrounding gray space to slice a series of huge gashes into it.

However, those gashes then immediately faded away, restoring the gray space to its former condition.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to do anything else, the entire gray space abruptly brightened significantly, to the point that he was almost forced to close his eyes against the blinding radiance.

The thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly flew back to him at his behest, then began circling around him in a protective manner.

At the same time, the blinding gray light faded away, and Han Li discovered that he was still in the same gray space, but he had been bound to a copper pillar.

His hands and feet had been encircled in thick, copper rings, rendering him completely immobilized.

On top of that, his suit of golden lightning armor and the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had all disappeared.

Han Li was naturally quite alarmed by this turn of events, and over nine hundred profound acupoints instantly lit up over his body as he struggled against the copper rings with all his might, but he was unable to even make them budge in the slightest.

"Impossible!" he exclaimed.

Given his current physical prowess, no matter how high a caliber of immortal treasure this copper pillar was, there should've been no way for it to be completely unmoved in the face of his strength.

All of a sudden, a scorching flame appeared at the top of the pillar, and the entire pillar instantly turned bright red.

A large section of Han Li's body was instantly charred black, and it seemed that his physical defenses had suddenly disappeared.

He felt as if his soul had been set alight, and the pain was so excruciating that he couldn't help but give a muffled groan.

Before he had a chance to do anything, a series of gray blades appeared in the space before him, and there were too many of them to count.

In the next instant, all of the gray blades converged toward him in unison, and his expression changed drastically as he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which released a wave of golden ripples to encompass the entire surrounding area in a radius of close to ten thousand feet.

However, neither the copper pillar nor the surrounding gray blades were affected by his Mantra Treasured Axis at all, and the blades pierced into all parts of his body without any delay, causing Han Li to yell out involuntarily in pain.

At this point, it had become clear to him that he had fallen into an extremely powerful illusion, one that was exerting complete control over all of his senses.

This was an illusion that truly blurred the lines between illusion and reality, and he had never witnessed an illusion this powerful before.

Bursts of illusory law powers were also transmitted into Han Li's body alongside the excruciating pain as the gray blades pierced into him from all directions, but right at this moment, a burst of time law powers surged out of his body as an automatic defense mechanism.

The time law powers managed to ward off the illusory law powers infiltrating his body, but more and more gray blades continued to pierce into him, inflicting unbearable agony.

Hints of gray light began to appear in his eyes as his consciousness began to fade.

The attacks came in relentless waves that left him no time for respite, and even with his immense mental fortitude, he was struck by a sense of despair and the urge to relinquish his resistance.

Right at this moment, his Spirit Refinement Technique was channeled on its own, and a translucent sword projection emerged in his mind, giving off peerless sword intent.

The despair in his heart was instantly eradicated by the sword intent, and he abruptly snapped wide awake as a layer of cold sweat appeared on his forehead.

Gritting his teeth against the unbearable pain, a look of resolve appeared in his eyes as he prepared to channel his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra to completely destroy this gray space, but right at this moment, the surrounding gray space suddenly began to tremble violently without any warning.

Immediately thereafter, an enormous, crimson blade projection pierced into the gray space, giving off astonishing baleful qi.

Han Li felt as if he had been plunged from head to toe into a glacial pit, and it was as if his soul were being forcibly sucked out of his body toward the crimson blade projection.

He hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to settle the unrest in his soul, and at the same time, he was able to identify the crimson blade projection as the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber!

The gargantuan blade projection swept forcefully through the air, and the gray space was instantly torn apart before disintegrating into countless specks of gray light, upon which Han Li found himself back in the air above the collapsed palace.

His Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were still hovering in the air around him, and the golden lightning armor on his body was also still intact.

Over ten thousand feet away, the azure-robed middle-aged man was staring at the black-robed young man with a stunned expression.

At this moment, the black-robed young man was holding none other than the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, and on top of that, Lekima had appeared on the battlefield, and it was locked in battle against the black-robed woman.

There were several wind dragons that were over a thousand feet in length circling around Lekima, releasing flurries of blades of wind out of their mouths toward the black-robed woman.

The wind blades didn't appear to be remarkable in any way, but they were astonishingly powerful, able to slice rifts into the surrounding space with ease.

Hovering behind the black-robed woman was a dark red wheel projection with six black holes on its surface, and the projection was revolving incessantly, releasing formidable law power fluctuations that kept the wind blades at bay with ease.

As for Lan Yan and the others, their pupils had all turned gray, clearly indicating that they were being controlled just like Lei Yuce and the others, but at this moment, all of them were standing still on the spot, engaging in no further battle.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the black-robed, and he immediately developed a rough idea of what had just taken place.

Chapter 1076: Reunion of Old Acquaintances

"That's the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber! Who are you? Why is that saber in your possession?" the middle-aged interrogated in a cold voice.

A faint smile appeared on the black-robed young man's face, and all of a sudden, he transformed into a silver-haired young man amid a flash of crimson light.

To Han Li's surprise, the young man was none other than Fox 3.

Han Li didn't know if Fox 3 had also managed to identify him, given that he had adopted a disguise of his own.

"Ninth generation disciple of the Heavenly Fox Tribe, Liu San, pays his respects to his senior!" Fox 3 greeted with a respectful bow.

The middle-aged man's expression eased slightly at the sight of Fox 3's true appearance, but his voice remained rather cold as he remarked, "I didn't think that I would meet my brethren here. In that case, was that man the one who gave you the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber?"

"Yes, but also no," Fox 3 replied in a respectful manner.

"I have no interest in playing word games with you here! If you've already chosen to side with him, then why did you come here? Were you thinking that I wouldn't kill you just because we're both from the same tribe, or are you of the opinion that you can oppose me thanks to the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber?" the azure-robed man asked as a hint of killing intent flashed through his eyes.

"I wouldn't dare to think that, Senior. Your mastery of the laws of illusions is far beyond anything I can fathom. Even with a few more Heavenly Fox Bloodform Sabers at my disposal, I'd definitely be no match for you. I've come here because our tribe has been swept up in some unrest recently, and I'm hoping that you can return with me to help our tribe overcome this crisis," Fox 3 replied in an earnest fashion.

"Back when I departed, I already made it clear that I was cutting all ties with the Heavenly Fox Tribe. I can see that you're a bright, young talent, so I'm going to spare you. Leave this place right now!" the azure-robed man said in a cold voice, following which he snapped his fingers, and Lekima immediately disengaged itself from its battle against the black-robed woman before flying back to the man's side.

"The laws of reincarnation really are just as formidable as the rumors suggest. It's a pity that we can't fight to our hearts' content here. Let's continue our battle some other time!" Lekima said with fierce battle intent still burning in its eyes.

Instead of pursuing Lekima, the black-robed woman calmly made a hand seal, and the dark red wheel behind her disintegrated into over a hundred dark red law threads that vanished into her body, following which she flew over to Fox 3's side.

The azure-robed man took a glance at the black-robed woman, but didn't say anything as he drifted down onto Lekima's back and prepared to depart.

"Senior, our tribe is facing a great crisis right now! Are you just going to stand by and watch?" Fox 3 asked as an urgent look appeared on his face.

The azure-robed man's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this, but he then replied in a cold voice, "I've already told you that I've cut all ties with the Heavenly Fox Tribe, so don't come bothering me again."

A frantic look appeared on Fox 3's face upon hearing this, but he didn't know what else he could say.

"Hold on a second!"

Right at this moment, a projection of Shi Qinghou emerged from the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber amid a flash of crimson light.

A hint of contempt appeared in the azure-robed man's eyes at the sight of Shi Qinghou, and he harrumphed coldly, "You're still alive? No wonder the powers of the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber haven't declined at all. That means you must've also allied yourself with that man!"

"Our master may not be dead," Shi Qinghou declared, seemingly completely out of the blue.

The azure-robed man immediately swung around to glower intently at Shi Qinghou upon hearing this.

"Master is still alive? No, there's no way that's possible! I saw him perish with my own two eyes!"

"Our master wouldn't perish so easily. What you and I saw back then was most likely not a reflection of reality. I only recently discovered some leads that tipped me off to the possibility that our master could still be alive. Otherwise, there's no way I would've been willing to submit to that man," Shi Qinghou replied in a proud manner.

"I see, so this is why you've come to find me," the azure-robed man mused with a slow nod.

"That's right, I've come here to request your help," Shi Qinghou confirmed.

The azure-robed man's attitude had taken a drastic turn, and he immediately replied, "I'm more than happy to help you if it means helping our master, but right now, I'm imprisoned in this pagoda, and my bonded soul tablet is still on the seventh level, so I'm afraid I can't leave with you."

A hint of elation flashed through Shi Qinghou's eyes upon hearing this, and he immediately promised, "Rest assured, we've come prepared. I'll be sure to retrieve your bonded soul tablet for you."

"In that case, I'll be counting on you. The spatial door leading to the sixth level is just up ahead, but I don't know who's being held captive there. However, what I do know is that the higher you go, the more powerful the fugitives are, so make sure to be on your guard," the azure-robed man said.

"Rest assured, no one will be able to stand up to our combined powers. Wouldn't you agree, Fellow Daoist Han?" Shi Qinghou chuckled as he turned to look at Han Li, who raised an eyebrow in response.

"What? You're Fellow Daoist Han?" Fox 3 exclaimed with a stunned expression, while the black-robed woman's expression remained unchanged, seemingly indicating that she was already aware of Han Li's identity.

"Oh? So you're all acquainted with one another? Looks like the Heavenly Fox Tribe has at least made some strides in gaining some powerful allies since I left," the azure-robed man remarked.

"Both of them are friends of Fox 3, they have nothing to do with those stubborn old farts of the Heavenly Fox Tribe," Shi Qinghou corrected, and the azure-robed man turned a surprised gaze to Fox 3 upon hearing this.

Han Li flew over to the black-robed duo as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Long time no see, Senior Shi, Fellow Daoist Fox 3, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3."

"I knew our disguises wouldn't be able to fool you," the black-robed woman replied with a smile as she reverted back to her true appearance, and sure enough, it was none other than Wyrm 3.

"Are you really Fellow Daoist Han?" Fox 3 asked with a hint of suspicion in his eyes, and it was no wonder that he was suspicious.

After all, back when they parted ways in the Gray Realm, Han Li had only been at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage, yet in the short span of just one thousand years, he had reached the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage, displaying a downright astonishing rate of progress.

"Looks like all of you have already learned my true name. Please forgive me for giving a false name last time. I had to adopt an alias in order to avoid capture from the Heavenly Court," Han Li said with an apologetic smile as he also reverted back to his original appearance.

"You really are Fellow Daoist Han! I can't believe you've been able to progress so rapidly in your cultivation base! I was really worried when you and Shi Chuankong were taken away in the Gray Realm, thank heavens you're safe and well! How is Brother Shi right now?" Fox 3 exclaimed in an elated manner.

"A powerful cultivator from the Devil Realm had teleported the two of us out of the Gray Realm back then. Rest assured, Brother Shi is also doing well," Han Li replied with a smile.

"That's good to hear," Fox 3 said with a relieved expression.

"Let's catch up later once we've left the Eon Pagoda. Right now, we have more pressing matters to take care of," Shi Qinghou interjected.

"You're right, Senior Shi," Fox 3 immediately replied in a respectful manner.

"Fellow Daoist Han, it seems like fate has brought us together again. How about we join forces from here onward?" Shi Qinghou invited.

"Truth be told, I only stumbled into this immortal manor completely by chance, so I know next to nothing about this place. It sounds like you're far more familiar with this place than I am, so would you be able to enlighten me, Senior Shi?" Han Li asked, choosing to dodge Shi Qinghou's question for now.

"Of course. This Tai Sui Immortal Manor is a cave abode left behind by a Great Encompassment cultivator by the name of Immortal Lord Tai Sui. He cultivated the laws of time, just like you, and he was once the chief warden of the Heavenly Court's Immortal Prison, but for some reason, he went on to betray the Heavenly Court.

“As he fled the Heavenly Court, he took quite a few fugitives and powerful treasures with him, the most renowned of which is the Eon Divine Lamp, which is said to be an unfathomably powerful time-attribute treasure. Right now, the lamp is most likely on the seventh level of the pagoda.

“The Heavenly Court has been hunting him for countless years, but I bet no one could've anticipated that Immortal Lord Tai Sui had gone into hiding in the Golden Origin Immortal Region, which is very close to the Middle Earth Immortal Region," Shi Qinghou explained.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing mention of the Eon Divine Lamp.

Ever since he entered the Eon Pagoda, he had detected a burst of formidable time law powers within it, and that had served as his source of motivation for progressing up the Eon Pagoda. It seemed that this Eon Divine Lamp was most likely the source of the time law powers that he had detected.

"How did you know that this immortal manor was here? It was very well concealed, and I only managed to stumble upon it by a complete stroke of luck," Han Li said.

"You'll have to ask Fellow Daoist Wyrm 3 about that. Fox 3 and I followed her here," Shi Qinghou replied.

Han Li turned to Wyrm 3 with a surprised expression upon hearing this.

"This matter concerns the secrets of the Reincarnation Palace. You may be a Reincarnation Disciple, but I'm afraid that this is still not information that I can make available to you," Wyrm 3 said with a shake of her head.

Han Li didn't try to force the matter, and he fell silent with a contemplative look on his face.

Chapter 1077: The Sixth Level

"That's the extent of my knowledge about this Tai Sui Immortal Manor, and you're already aware of my objective for coming here, so what do you say about my earlier proposal?" Shi Qinghou asked.

"I can join forces with you, and I can even help you secure that bonded soul tablet, but if I encounter any difficulties from here onward, then I hope that the two of you can help me as well," Han Li replied.

"Deal!"

Both Fox 3 and Shi Qinghou were ecstatic to hear this, while Wyrm 3 remained silent with a contemplative look in her eyes.

"In that case, let's set off right away," Shi Qinghou said as he turned to the azure-robed man.

"Come with me. Don't look around along the way, and don't touch anything. Don't ask me any questions, either," the azure-robed man said, then began flying forward atop Lekima, while Lan Yan and the others trailed along behind him like a group of mindless zombies, and Han Li's trio followed along as well.

They traveled for a day and a night, departing from the gourd-like mountain before passing over the entire desert, following which they crossed a massive swamp, beyond which was an undulating mountain range...

Along the way, Han Li noticed some rather strange things, such as a massive ice sculpture in the middle of the desert, a huge, constantly revolving vortex in a swamp, bursts of dull, rhythmic rumbling coming from beneath a mountain range, and a series of of crimson chains that connected a large forest filled with close to a thousand trees.

The azure-robed man had made it clear that he didn't want to be asked any questions, and it was also very apparent that he didn't want to speak, so Han Li chose to hold his tongue, despite his curiosity.

After traveling for a while longer, the group finally arrived at another black palace situated on a grassland.

This palace was even larger than the previous one, and the interior was illuminated by a series of lit braziers.

At the very back of the palace stood a dark red door of light, and the azure-robed man said, "That's the entrance to the sixth level. This is where we part ways."

He then turned to depart, only to be stopped by Fox 3, who implored, "Would it be possible for you to release these companions of ours, Senior? We don't know what perils await us on the sixth and seventh levels, so the more people we have, the better equipped we'll be to deal with the potential dangers up ahead."

"These people could come in useful. Surely you could spare a few illusion servants," Shi Qinghou chimed in.

The azure-robed man's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but he quickly acquiesced, making a hand seal to release seven bursts of gray light that vanished into the bodies of Lan Yan and the others.

Immediately thereafter, a series of gray threads flew out of their bodies before vanishing into the azure-robed man's body.

Right at this moment, Lekima's voice rang out in Han Li's mind.

"If you see my bonded soul tablet on the seventh level, make sure to take it. I'll compensate you handsomely if you can bring it to me."

Han Li cast his gaze toward Lekima upon hearing this, only to discover that it was looking straight ahead, obediently carrying the azure-robed man on its back.

After recovering his law threads from Lan Yan and the others, the azure-robed man and Lekima promptly departed, vanishing without a trace in the blink of an eye, and it was as if they had never been here at all.

Meanwhile, Lan Yan and the others quickly began to return to their senses, and Han Li hurriedly reverted back to his disguised appearance upon seeing this.

Fox 3 and Wyrm 3 also did the same, and the former simultaneously stowed his Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber away as well.

Before long, all of the gray light in the eyes of Lan Yan and the others had faded away, and they were fully lucid again.

"Where are we right now? I don't remember anything after those gray threads entered my body!" Lei Yuce exclaimed in a panicked manner as he frantically scoured his surroundings.

It seemed that all those who fell under the control of those gray law threads had no recollection of anything that had happened after they were controlled.

"Please be at ease, everyone. The enemy is already gone, and we're safe now," Fox 3 reassured.

"Do you know what happened?" Lei Yuce asked.

"I do, a little..."

With that, Fox 3 fabricated a story of how Han Li had put on a stunning display of power to force the enemy into retreat.

Fox 3 was quite a good storyteller to begin with, and he invented a watertight story that was very sound and believable.

Han Li couldn't help but shake his head internally in exasperation, but he didn't say anything.

"So that means Fellow Daoist Shi saved us yet again. Words cannot express my gratitude, Fellow Daoist Shi. Once we leave the Tai Sui Immortal Manor, please come visit our Heavenly Water Sect so that we can show you some hospitality as a display of gratitude," Su Anqian said in an earnest manner.

Xiong Shan, Lan Yan, and Lan Yuanzi also expressed their gratitude toward Han Li, but the Lan siblings were looking at him with renewed wariness in their eyes.

As for Lei Yuce, Jin Liu, and Wen Zhong, the three of them were looking a little dejected.

They had gone to great lengths to break that restriction earlier, but ultimately didn't have anything to show for it. In particular, not only had Jin Liu had his Fire Age Firefly hive taken by Han Li, he had also just been saved by Han Li, so he was feeling very frustrated.

'"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Su. The enemy has temporarily gone into retreat, but they could return at any moment, so let's leave this place and get to the sixth level right away," Han Li said.

"Indeed, time is of the essence," Su Anqian replied with a nod, and everyone immediately began working on breaking the restriction on the spatial door.

The restrictions on all of the spatial doors were largely identical, so everyone had become quite proficient at breaking them, and it didn't take long before they were able to pass through the spatial door.

Han Li felt his vision blur momentarily, following which he was greeted by the sight of a boundless golden desert.

He cast his gaze into the distance, but there was only yellow sand as far as the eyes could see in all directions, and the air was rather dry and abrasive.

Right at this moment, Wyrm 3 and the others appeared beside him one after another, and all of them naturally split up into two groups.

Fox 3 and Wyrm 3 were naturally standing a little closer to Han Li, while the two Heavenly Water Sect cultivators had sided with the two Almighty Sword Sect cultivators, and the Lan siblings were also trailing along behind them.

Strangely enough, for some reason, Xiong Shan had also chosen to stand with Han Li's trio.

From there, everyone began to scour their surroundings, and after observing the area for a while, peculiar looks appeared on everyone's faces.

Wyrm 3 crouched down to pick up some of the sand from the ground, then gave it a close look as she mused, "This doesn't seem like normal sand."

"That's because it's not. Instead, all of this is powderized demon beast bones," Han Li said.

"How is that possible?" Wyrm 3 exclaimed in an incredulous manner.

"Fellow Daoist Shi is right," Lei Yuce said, then pointed in a certain direction, where there was an enormous object on the horizon several dozen kilometers away.

Everyone flew over to the object in question, upon which they discovered that it was a curved horn of some type of massive beast. The horn was golden in color, and it had clearly been severely ravaged by erosion.

Wyrm 3 flew over to the horn before laying a hand onto it, and as soon as she did so, the horn immediately crumbled away into a vast cloud of golden sand that dissipated in all directions.

"Which way do we go?" Fox 3 asked, then looked up at the sky, where a bright sun was hanging up above, but it wasn't giving off any heat, almost as if it were nothing more than an illusion.

Lei Yuce was just about to say something when Han Li suddenly pointed in a certain direction and said, "I think we should go that way."

Everyone turned to that direction, but there was nothing to be seen there aside from more sand.

The spiritual sense restrictions had become even more potent on the sixth level, so no one was able to detect anything beyond what they could see in their field of view.

"What's over there?" Su Anqian asked in a curious manner.

"My spiritual sense is too severely restricted for me to tell, but I can sense a special aura in that direction," Han Li replied.

Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 exchanged a hesitant glance with each other upon hearing this.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, it's not been an easy journey to get here, and I'm sure you're aware of how many people have already perished along the way, so I think we should proceed with more caution. Wouldn't it be better to have a thorough discussion before deciding on which way to go?" Lei Yuce proposed after a brief hesitation.

"Fellow Daoist Lei is right. The higher we go in this pagoda, the more perils await us, so we can't afford to be reckless," Jin Liu chimed in.

Su Anqian opened her mouth to say something, but ultimately remained silent.

"Honestly, now that we've reached the sixth level, it doesn't really matter where we go, so if no one wants to come with me, then I'll go by myself," Han Li said with a smile, then cupped his fist in a parting salute as he turned to depart.

"I'll come with you, Fellow Daoist Shi," Xiong Shan suddenly said.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but he didn't say anything as he flew away in silence, and Xiong Shan immediately followed along after him without any hesitation.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 decided to go after Han Li as well.

Chapter 1078: Coming Clean

Jin Liu was watching as Han Li vanished into the distance, and for some reason, he felt as if a heavy load had been lifted from his shoulders.

He had always been quite wary of Han Li, so it came as a relief to have finally parted ways with him.

The Lan siblings also both heaved an internal sigh of relief.

Even though they had been ordered to hunt down Han Li, it was clear that this was not a mission that they could complete, and if they had a choice in the matter, they would've preferred not to have encountered Han Li at all.

"Where do we go now?" Su Anqian asked.

"Please wait a moment, Celestial Maiden Su," Lei Yuce said, then flipped a hand over to produce a golden plate that was riddled with runes and engravings.

The plate rose up into the air above the palm of his hand, and a tiny flame rose up over its surface before moving away slightly, as if it were being drawn by some type of invisible force.

Su Anqian and the others didn't know what to make of this, but Wen Zhong's eyes had suddenly lit up at the sight of the plate.

Lei Yuce observed the direction of the flame's movement for a moment, then stowed the plate away as he pointed in that direction and said, "We should go that way?"

"What was that thing, Fellow Daoist Lei?" Su Anqian asked as her brows furrowed slightly.

Lei Yuce hesitated momentarily, then explained, "It's a little treasure that has some connection to the Eon Divine Lamp, so it should be able to point us in the right direction."

"In that case, can we be certain that Fellow Daoist Shi has gone the wrong way?" Su Anqian asked.

"Do you still recall the crossroads that we encountered when we first entered this pagoda?" Lei Yuce asked, raising a question for his own.

"You're saying that there are multiple paths that lead to the same destination?" Su Anqian asked.

"I don't know if Fellow Daoist Shi has taken the right path. Perhaps we'll ultimately all arrive at the same destination," Lei Yuce replied with a nod, and Su Anqian also gave a contemplative nod upon hearing this.

"Time is of the essence, so I suggest that we set off right away," Wen Zhong said.

......

Not only was spiritual sense severely restricted in the golden desert, everyone's flight speed was also significantly hampered.

"Fellow Daoist Xiong Shan, I don't care why you decided to follow me, but I'm warning you not to do anything out of line. I don't want to have to kill you again," Han Li said.

"There's no need for you to be wary of me, Fellow Daoist Han, it was purely by chance that the two of us encountered each other here. If Chief Warden Qi Mozi hadn't decided to bring me with him, I would either be at my post in the Immortal Prison right now, or cultivating in seclusion in my cave abode, and I wouldn't have come out before I reached the late-High Zenith Stage," Xiong Shan hurriedly explained.

"Why the late-High Zenith Stage?" Han Li asked.

"I was hoping that with the Immortal Palace's help, I would be able to get reach the late-High Zenith Stage ahead of you, at which point I'll be able to exact vengeance upon you, but I've now come to realize the futility of my endeavor," Xiong Shan replied with a wry smile.

"How did you manage to identify me?" Han Li asked as he glowered intently at Xiong Shan.

"You must've faced Chief Warden Qi Mozi in a battle not long ago, right, Fellow Daoist Han?" Xiong Shan asked.

"That's right. The fact that you're asking this question means that he must've left some type of mark on me during our battle, right?" Han Li asked.

"Your wisdom is truly unmatched, Fellow Daoist Han. Indeed, after Chief Warden Qi Mozi became aware of your penchant for adopting disguises with your Reincarnation Palace mask, he decided that he was going to plant a mark on your body the next time you faced each other in battle so that he could track you in the future," Xiong Shan confirmed with a nod.

"What kind of mark did he leave on me? Why haven't I been able to detect it at all?" Han Li asked.

"The mark doesn't give off any spiritual power fluctuations, and it can only be used to track someone at very close proximity through the use of a detection token," Xiong Shan explained as he summoned a small jade pendant before offering it to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the jade pendant from Xiong Shan to discover that it was hot to the touch.

"If you know who I am, then shouldn't you be avoiding me? Why are you following me instead?" Han Li asked as he stowed the jade pendant away.

"Well... Firstly, I feel like I'll be a bit safer with you, and perhaps I'll be able to reap some spoils that you don't care to claim. Secondly, if we run into Chief Warden Qi Mozi and he sees that I'm with you, he'll know that I've remained loyal to my post," Xiong Shan explained after a brief hesitation.

"Are you not afraid that I'll kill you again?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Xiong Shan instantly tensed up upon hearing this, but he maintained a calm and composed facade as he replied, "You've already killed me once, so all of our differences have already been settled. I haven't done anything to provoke you, and I'm sure you're not the type of person to take innocent lives. Even if you do kill me, at the very least, I will have chosen my fate, and that's better than perishing to some unknown cause in this godforsaken place."

"You're right in that I won't take innocent lives, but if I find you doing anything out of line, then don't blame me for turning on you," Han Li threatened in a cold voice.

Under normal circumstances, he definitely wouldn't have allowed Xiong Shan to follow him like this. However, at the moment, it was unclear where Qi Mozi was, so he decided to keep Xiong Shan around to see if there was some type of sinister plot afoot. If that were the case, then perhaps he would be able to use Xiong Shan as bait to lure out Qi Mozi and put an end to their conflict once and for all.

"Right now, you can kill me just by lifting a finger, so I definitely wouldn't dare to do anything out of line," Xiong Shan hurriedly replied.

As they were speaking with one another, Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 caught up to them, following which the former asked, "What exactly have you found in that direction, Brother Han?"

"I know that you're not one to make unsound decisions, but you should've at least tipped us off a little! Right now, we're following after you completely blind!" Fox 3 complained.

"I detected an aura in this direction that was both familiar and unfamiliar to me, so I wanted to go and take a look. There was no need for the two of you to follow me," Han Li replied.

"It's fine. At the very least, you have some direction, and perhaps this is the right way to go," Wyrm 3 said.

With that, the group flew onward with Han Li leading the way, and along the way, they spotted many enormous golden bones half-buried in the desert.

However, there was nothing else worthy of note about these bones aside from how massive they were, so no one paid them any heed.

After flying for around four hours, Han Li spotted a blurry outline in the distance. It seemed to be a majestic palace that was giving off radiant, golden light, and the aura that he had sensed earlier was becoming more and more pronounced.

Fox 3 and Wyrm 3 both perked up slightly at the sight of the silhouette on the horizon, and only after flying for several dozen more kilometers was the silhouette revealed to be a grand palace comprised entirely of golden sand.

Numerous giant golden horns could be seen on the walls of the palace, serving as decoration, and laying on its ceiling was a golden-robed young man.

It was a rather handsome young man with a lazy look on his face, and he was tossing a round golden skull up and down in a bored manner.

The skull was far larger than the average human skull, indicating that it belonged to some other type of foreign being, and it had been tossed around so much that its surface had become polished smooth.

The young man tossed the skull up one more time, then caught it again before rising to his feet and casting his gaze toward Han Li's group, who were approaching from several dozen kilometers away.

Right at this moment, a palm-sized golden lizard suddenly scurried its way out of his collar to stand on his shoulder, where it also began observing Han Li's group.

"I knew it..." Han Li mused to himself as a grim look appeared on his face.

"Do you recognize this man, Brother Han?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"I don't, but I know what he is. He's a Gold Devouring Immortal," Han Li replied.

"What?! A Gold Devouring Immortal? His aura indicates that he's already at the Great Encompassment Stage! A Great Encompassment Stage Gold Devouring Immortal is going to be a massive pain to deal with!" Fox 3 exclaimed.

"I'm beginning to regret coming with you now, Fellow Daoist Han," Xiong Shan groaned with a forlorn expression.

Before Han Li had a chance to say anything, the young man appeared no more than several thousand feet away from them in a flash, where he began to observe their group with an intrigued expression, while Han Li and the others looked back at him with wary expressions.

"There's no need to be so anxious, I won't kill you right away," the young man said with a smile.

He then picked up the golden lizard that was perched on his shoulder as he continued, "It's incredibly boring being trapped in this pagoda, and I've only had this Golden Mongoose Lizard to keep me company over the past million years. Now that you're here, I can have a bit of fun!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he hurled the golden lizard through the air, sending it flying directly at Wyrm 3's face like a golden spear.

A dark red light barrier instantly appeared before Wyrm 3 without any warning, and the Golden Mongoose Lizard plunged headfirst into the light barrier like a speeding arrow, causing the light barrier to cave in to such a degree that the lizard only drew to a halt no more than an inch away from Wyrm 3's glabella.

Immediately thereafter, the light barrier began to ripple like water before rebounding forcefully to send the lizard flying back through the air.

All of a sudden, Han Li yelled, "Look out!"

Chapter 1079: Deal

Wyrm 3 reflexively took a step back upon hearing this, only to feel someone grab onto her shoulder before throwing her back through the air.

At the same time, the body of the Golden Mongoose Lizard suddenly began to swell up like a balloon, following which it exploded violently into a ball of rapidly expanding golden light.

The ball of golden light then transformed into an enormous, golden vortex with countless blades of golden light sweeping through it.

These blades of golden light were imbued with incredibly formidable metal law powers that instantly sliced the nearby space into ribbons.

After sending Wyrm 3 flying to safety, Han Li stepped forward while channeling his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra and his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts in unison, then threw a punch forward to release a semi-transparent golden fist projection that struck the golden vortex with tremendous power.

A resounding boom rang out as the vortex exploded, sending the blades of golden light inside sweeping through the air in all directions.

At the same time, the golden-robed young man had already pounced at Han Li, much to the latter's dismay.

As expected of a fellow Gold Devouring Immortal, this golden-robed young man was just as keen for battle as Jin Tong was.

Han Li didn't dare to take any chances against such a formidable Gold Devouring Immortal, and he immediately channeled his Reversal True Axis ability to dart back in retreat.

"So you've mastered the laws of time as well," the young man remarked with a displeased look on his face, clearly having been reminded of the man who had trapped him in this place.

Immediately thereafter, a layer of golden ripples surged out of his body, giving him an illusory appearance.

All Han Li saw was a golden blur before the young man abruptly appeared before him, then reached out to make a grab for his throat.

The man had displayed such incredible speed that even Han Li was unable to keep up.

Right at this moment, a streak of swordlight shot out of Wyrm 3's sleeve before hurtling directly toward the man's head.

However, this didn't deter the man at all as he continued to make a grab for Han Li with a disdainful sneer on his face.

The streak of swordlight was imbued with immense power, but it instantly shattered upon impact against the man's body, and it wasn't even able to leave a mark on his golden robe.

Right as the tips of the man's fingers were about to make contact with Han Li's throat, a burst of golden light suddenly appeared behind him, and his Mantra Treasured Axis emerged before releasing countless rays of radiant, golden light in all directions.

The young man was instantly rooted to the spot, while Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, all of which converged toward the man from different directions.

Bursts of golden lightning erupted out of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, all of which were aimed at the vital regions of the man's body, and he was instantly inundated by a hostile sea of golden lightning.

The sea of golden lightning raged and rumbled incessantly, scorching the very space around it.

However, after the lightning dissipated, the young man remained completely unscathed, and aside from some char marks on his robe, he was entirely unaffected.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew high up into the sky at his behest before combining into a single flying sword.

A vast torrent of golden lightning erupted out of the combined Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and a pillar of golden lightning descended from the heavens before crashing down upon the golden-robed man with devastating power.

An earth-shattering thunderclap rang out as the man was struck by the pillar of lightning, and he was immediately sent plummeting out of the sky.

All of a sudden, it was as if a pool of golden lightning had appeared in the desert, eradicating everything within it.

Wyrm 3 and the others had already retreated far away, and their expressions changed drastically upon seeing this.

Among them, Xiong Shan was displaying the strongest reaction, one of shock and dismay, and he couldn't help but heave a forlorn sigh as it dawned on him just how far Han Li had left him behind.

Moments later, the lightning subsided, and it was revealed that the tip of the combined Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword was pinned firmly against the golden-robed man's head, but it hadn't managed to even pierce through his skin.

The physical constitution of a Great Encompassment Stage Gold Devouring Immortal was truly astounding.

"Do you have any other tricks up your sleeve? If not, then I'm about to retaliate," the young man said in a bored manner.

At the same time, layers of golden ripples were emanating from his body, forcing back the rays of golden light released by Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

By refining the Fire Age Firefly hives, Han Li had attained a large number of time law threads, granting him far superior time law powers that he had thought would've at least been sufficient to immobilize the average Great Encompassment cultivator, but it appeared that this was not enough to keep a Great Encompassment Stage Gold Devouring Immortal in check.

All of a sudden, the young man's smile faded, and a pair of near-transparent wings appeared on his back.

The wings began flapping rapidly amid a barely audible buzzing sound, releasing waves of semi-transparent golden light that clashed against the golden ripples released by the Mantra Treasured Axis.

As more and more wave of golden light were released, the power of the Mantra Treasured Axis was nullified further and further, allowing the man to move freely within a certain area.

He dusted off the charred parts of his golden robe, then rubbed the spot on the top of his head where he had been struck by Han Li's sword, following which he looked up at Han Li and loosely clenched his hand into a fist.

It was only a small gesture, but a terrifying aura erupted out of his body as a result.

A burst of radiant, golden light appeared behind him, within which was a giant Gold Devouring Beetle projection, and it was giving off formidable law power fluctuations that instantly forced back the surrounding golden ripples even further.

"Look out!" Wyrm 3 yelled in an alarmed manner as she stepped forward to help, only for Han Li to raise a hand to stop her.

She turned to Han Li with a perplexed expression, and she was left feeling even more puzzled when Han Li suddenly withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis.

"What are you doing, Brother Han?" Fox 3 asked with a befuddled expression, and the golden-robed young man was also rather taken aback by this turn of events.

"May I ask your name, Fellow Daoist?" Han Li suddenly asked.

"Isn't it a little late for Brother Han to be trying to make friends now?" Fox 3 exclaimed in a flabbergasted manner, while Wyrm 3 continued to look on with a perplexed expression.

The man's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he offered no response.

Han Li remained unbothered by this, and he continued, "I can see that you were also imprisoned here by Immortal Lord Tai Sui, just like everyone on the previous levels of this pagoda, so there's no need for us to be enemies."

The man immediately erupted into laughter upon hearing this, as if he had just been told a hilarious joke.

"If you let us go, I promise that we'll do everything in our power to lift the restriction in this place and free you from here. What do you say?" Han Li asked, looking completely unfazed.

"How can you possibly free me from this pagoda when you can't even defeat me? Do you know what kind of monster is being held captive on the seventh level? You think all it'll take is for me to let you through, and you'll be able to achieve your objective without any resistance? I've finally had some playthings show up on my doorstep, I'm not handing you over to that old madman so easily!" the young man scoffed.

"I'm confident in our ability to deal with whatever's on the seventh level, it's just a matter of whether you're willing to let us through now," Han Li declared in an indifferent manner, and a hesitant look appeared in the man's eyes at the sight of Han Li's unwavering confidence.

If it were possible, of course he wanted to be freed from this godforsaken pagoda.

Over the past several million years, he had been so bored that he had massacred all of the other living beings on this level before grinding their bones down into golden powder, and that was how this desert had come into existence.

Unfortunately, he had gone too far on his killing spree, to the point that the only thing that remained to keep him company was that Golden Mongoose Lizard.

Despite his desire to leave, he couldn't help but wonder if Han Li really did possess the power to free him from this place.

"I'm open to the idea, but how are you going to show me that you won't perish to that old madman, and how are you going to prove to me that you have what it takes to free me from this pagoda? How about you take a punch head-on from me?" the man proposed.

Wyrm 3's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but before she had a chance to stop him, Han Li replied, "Deal."

Chapter 1080: One Punch

"Brother Han, an all-out blow from a Great Encompassment Stage Gold Devouring Immortal is not to be taken lightly! I know that you're confident in your abilities, but this is an extremely perilous undertaking!" Wyrm 3 said to Han Li through voice transmission.

"Brother Han, all he said is that you had to take a punch from him head-on, but he didn't stipulate that you can't use any treasures. I can temporarily lend you my Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber so you have a better chance of withstanding a punch from him," Fox 3 also communicated through voice transmission.

"Thanks for looking out for me, but I can look after myself," Han Li replied with a smile.

Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 exchanged a perplexed glance with each other upon hearing this, but didn't try to dissuade Han Li any further.

"If you have any pieces of protective clothing, then I suggest you put on as many layers as possible. As long as you don't evade my punch, you can do anything you want to defend yourself. Let me warn you that I'm not going to be holding back," the man said with a wide grin.

Han Li nodded in response, then turned to Wyrm 3's trio and gestured for them to distance themselves from him.

The three of them immediately retreated to close to ten kilometers away.

"What on earth is Brother Han planning? Will he really be able to withstand an all-out blow from this Gold Devouring Immortal?" Fox 3 asked.

"I'm not sure, but knowing the type of person that he is, I'm sure he won't take any undue risks, so we'll just have to wait and see," Wyrm 3 replied.

Xiong Shan didn't say anything. In fact, he had the most confidence in Han Li out of the trio, and he had a feeling that this Gold Devouring Immortal was about to be screwed over by Han Li.

After Wyrm 3's trio had retreated to a safe distance away, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a spherical light barrier around him, one that was over ten thousand feet in radius.

"You think your time spirit domain will be enough to oppose my attack?" the golden-robed man asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"I'm ready," Han Li declared in a calm manner, then took a step back before adopting a horse stance while simultaneously channeling both his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra.

An intrigued look appeared in the young man's eyes upon seeing this, and all of a sudden, a burst of radiant, golden light erupted out of his body as his robes began to flap and billow audibly.

At the same time, rings of golden light began to proliferate through the surrounding area from beneath his feet like ripples over the surface of a lake, spreading all the way to hundreds of kilometers away.

All of the grains of golden sand in the desert began to bounce up and down as if they were jumping for joy, and concerned looks appeared in the eyes of Wyrm 3's trio as they sensed the golden-robed man's unfathomable power.

Han Li was situated closest to the young man, so he was able to sense his power even more clearly than Wyrm 3 and the others, and even though he was stunned internally, he was able to maintain a calm facade.

"Here I come!" the young man declared as he also took a step back, pulling his fist back to his own waist as he prepared to launch himself forward.

Han Li remained silent as he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which fused as one with his time spirit domain and rose up into the air like a bright moon that was giving off rays of gentle light.

Immediately thereafter, Illusory Dawn Sand spilled over the ground, almost indistinguishable from the golden sand of the desert, and a series of mountains quickly emerged over the landscape.

The Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree then emerged before transforming into a lush forest, while water of time flowed down from the heavens, forming a winding river that trickled through the forest.

Finally, a golden torch that was releasing countless specks of golden fire rose up into the air, and the specks of golden fire resembled stars that lit up the entire sky.

The golden-robed young man was quite taken aback to see this, but unlike Qi Mozi, he wasn't aware of the secrets of the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra, so all he felt was intrigue.

He could sense that the surrounding flow of time was slowing down, and that his movements were becoming more and more restricted, but he still scoffed, "How are these illusory objects going to help you?"

At the same time, the golden light radiating from his body had reached an unprecedented level of brightness, and he launched himself forward while throwing a punch directly at Han Li.

A giant, golden fist projection shot forth through the air, and it seemed to be completely unaffected by Han Li's time law powers as it hurtled toward him with devastating power.

However, in the instant that the fist projection was unleashed, the man noticed that the punch was far less powerful than he had anticipated.

Immediately thereafter, he finally realized what had happened to him.

Much to Han Li's dismay, most of the time law threads that he had recently attained had been drained of their power in order to unleash the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra's time-reversal ability, and he hurriedly withdrew his five time-attribute law treasures in order to conserve his time law powers.

As soon as the law treasures faded away, the fist projection instantly accelerated significantly, reaching Han Li in the blink of an eye.

Fortunately, he was already fully prepared, and his physical constitution had been bolstered to the maximum by his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts as he threw a punch of his own in retaliation.

At the same time, he drew upon all of the starpower in his entire body before condensing it into his fist, and an earth-shattering boom rang out as his fist collided with the oncoming golden fist projection.

A vast explosion of golden and white light took place, stirring up an incredibly chaotic vortex that spread through the air in all directions, annihilating everything within a radius of dozens of kilometers.

Hundreds of sand whirls erupted up into the heavens like a nest of monstrous, golden serpents, producing a deafening rumbling.

Han Li was sent flying back through the air before plunging several thousand feet deep into the sand below, and all of his joints were creaking and groaning incessantly, while his entire body was throbbing with pain.

He thrust his palms forcefully into the ground beneath himself, launching himself out of the sand and barreling his way straight through dozens of sand whirls before drawing to a halt in front of the golden-robed young man.

Shortly thereafter, the sand whirls faded away, but there was still a vast volume of sand drifting through the air, severely affecting visibility.

"I believe I've just fulfilled my end of the deal," Han Li said, then threw up a mouthful of blood.

"How is this possible? What did your spirit domain do to me just now?" the man asked as he looked down at his own fist with a perplexed expression.

"Your cultivation base had temporarily been reversed several million years, but it'll gradually recover," Han Li said, and despite his nonchalant tone, the golden-robed man was astonished to hear this.

Sure enough, he could sense that his own cultivation base had been significantly regressed, and that was why his punch had been lacking in power.

"Seeing as you've managed to withstand a punch from me, I will also fulfill my end of the deal. Not only will I no longer oppose you, I can even take you to the seventh level, but in exchange, you have to free me from this pagoda," the man said.

"If you had agreed to my proposal without making me withstand that punch, then our agreement would've been able to stand on those terms, but now that I've been forced to withstand a punch from you, some of the conditions have to be changed," Han Li said.

"What do you mean by that? Are you going back on our agreement?" the man asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"No, I'm still going to fulfill my promise of freeing you from this pagoda, but in return, I need you to do something for me," Han Li replied.

"What is it?" the man snapped, struggling to rein in his own temper.

At this point, Wyrm 3's trio was about to arrive on the scene, so Han Li switched to voice transmission as he said, "Among the people who entered the Eon Pagoda, one of them is a Great Encompassment cultivator who's a sworn enemy of mine, and I want you to help me deal with him. Of course, this is not something that necessarily has to be done.

“As long as he doesn't come after me, you don't have to target him, and once we leave the Eon Pagoda, you'll be free, so you won't have to do it."

"That's it?" the man asked in a skeptical manner.

"That's it," Han Li confirmed with a nod.

At the same time, they were joined by Wyrm 3's trio, and the three of them were all looking at Han Li with rather peculiar looks on their faces.

They had detected extremely formidable law power fluctuations while Han Li was unleashing his Five Elemental Illusory World, but they weren't aware of exactly what had happened. However, it was now abundantly clear to them what had unfolded after detecting the golden-robed man's regressed cultivation base.

"Also, there's something else that I can tell you. During my travels, I encountered two High Zenith Stage Gold Devouring Immortals, and I presume you'd be interested in them," Han Li continued.

"Where did you encounter these two Gold Devouring Immortals?" the young man immediately asked.

"One in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region and the other in the Golden Origin Immortal Region. One of them was a small child, while the other was a vicious woman," Han Li lied, making up a story on the spot.

"If you can take me to them, I can protect you even after we leave the Eon Pagoda, and if that Great Encompassment cultivator that you spoke of comes after you, I will do everything in my power to kill him," the golden-robed man promised through voice transmission.

"That sounds like a good deal," Han Li replied with a smile.

With this agreement made, the tension between the two of them eased significantly, and Han Li smiled as he asked, "Can you tell me your name now"

"My name is Qu Lin," the man replied, and Han Li revealed his own name as well.

"Time is of the essence, Fellow Daoist Han. I'll take you to the seventh level right away," Qu Lin said in an urgent manner.

"There's no hurry, please allow me some time to rest and recover," Han Li said.

Even though Qu Lin's cultivation base had been regressed by Han Li's Five Elemental Illusory World, an all-out blow from him was still nothing to scoff at, and Han Li had sustained some internal injuries from withstanding that punch.

With that, he sat down with his legs crossed, then took a pill before closing his eyes to meditate.

Chapter 1081: Self-Sacrificial Rescue

On the other side of the golden desert, Lei Yuce and the others were currently gathered before a reddish-brown stone archway.

A series of runes were engraved onto the archway, seven or eight of which were currently flashing with faint, golden light. Inside the archway was a dark red light barrier, bound to which were nine dark golden chains.

Upon close inspection, one would discover that these chains were also riddled with tiny scale-like runes, and they were giving off extremely formidable restrictive power.

"What's the verdict, Fellow Daoist Lei? Can you unravel this Nine Dragon Deity Locking Array or not?" Jin Liu asked with slightly furrowed brows.

Instead of immediately giving a response, Lei Yuce spoke briefly with Wen Zhong in hushed tones, then said, "This Nine Dragon Deity Locking Array has been tampered with by someone, making it more difficult to unravel than otherwise, so I'm going to need some time."

"How long will it take?" Su Anqian asked.

"This array is very complex to begin with, and even with just a single Dragon Scale Chain altered, the difficulty of unraveling the array will increase significantly. At the very least, four of these chains have been tampered with, so by my estimates, it's going to take around two to three days," Lei Yuce replied.

"Two to three days? That's way too long!" Jin Liu exclaimed.

"If you have some other faster way to break the array, then feel free to do so yourself, Fellow Daoist Jin," Wen Zhong said with a displeased expression.

An angry look flashed through Jin Liu's eyes upon hearing this, but he offered no response.

When it came to arrays, his aptitude was very mediocre. Otherwise, he wouldn't have misidentified the Star Palace Standoff Array as the Yin Yang Latch Array earlier. Hence, he was naturally unable to unravel this Nine Dragon Deity Locking Array.

The Lan siblings exchanged a glance with each other, then shook their heads in unison, clearly also powerless in the face of this array.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Lei Yuce said, "There's something else I can try, but I don't have much confidence that it's going to succeed."

"If there's something else we can try, then we naturally have to try it! We can't afford to be delayed here like this!" Jin Liu immediately said.

"You make it sound so simple! Senior Martial Brother Lei is referring to a way to break the array by force, and even the slightest mishap could result in grievous bodily harm!" Wen Zhong snapped in a disgruntled manner.

A hint of concern appeared in Su Anqian's eyes upon hearing this, while Jin Liu stroked his own chin with tightly furrowed brows as he mused, "In that case, it looks like we'll just have to wait."

"Fellow Daoist Lei, if the alternative method is too risky, then it would be better to be safe than sorry, even if it means a delay of two or three days," Su Anqian said.

"It's fine, Celestial Maiden Su, I can give it a try," Lei Yuce replied.

A hint of exasperation flashed through Wen Zhong's eyes upon hearing this, and he wanted to try and dissuade Lei Yuce, but he knew that it would only be in futility, so he remained silent.

"In order to break this array quickly, I'll have to use the Six Integrations Wilderness Array to force open the Nine Dragon Deity Locking Array, thereby temporarily creating an opening for us to pass through. In order to accomplish this, I'm going to need everyone's help," Lei Yuce said.

"I'm aware of the Six Integrations Wilderness Array. It's an array that's far inferior to the Nine Dragon Deity Locking Array, so how can this possibly work?" Jin Liu asked with a skeptical expression.

"The Six Integrations Wilderness Array naturally won't be enough to get the job done on its own. I'm going to be using a Nine Dragon Jewel to serve as the core of the array in order to enhance its power," Lei Yuce explained.

"A Nine Dragon Jewel? If you really do have such a treasure up your sleeve, then this plan becomes a lot more plausible," Jin Liu replied with a nod.

"Lan Yan and I will do everything in our power to assist you," Lan Yuanzi assured, while Su Anqian nodded in agreement.

With that, Lei Yuce flipped a hand over to produce a collection of array tools, which he began laying out around the stone archway with Wen Zhong's assistance.

Before long, the foundation of a hexagonal array had emerged.

Shortly thereafter, the Six Integrations Wilderness Array was complete, and after thoroughly examining the array to ensure that nothing was amiss, Lei Yuce declared, "The array is complete. Please step inside with me, fellow daoists."

Everyone did as they were told, with each person standing on one of the six corners of the hexagonal array, waiting for Lei Yuce to activate the array.

Lei Yuce exchanged a glance with Su Anqian, then flipped a hand over to produce a fist-sized purple jewel, which flew through the air before descending upon the center of the Six Integrations Wilderness Array.

There were arcs of lightning flashing over the jewel, and nine dragons could be seen roaming incessantly over its surface amid bursts of dull rumbling.

With the Nine Dragon Jewel in place, Lei Yuce began chanting an incantation, and everyone immediately followed suit while making a series of hand seals before each of them pointed a finger at the jewel.

Six beams of spiritual light of different colors shot out of their fingertips before converging within the purple jewel, and countless arcs of purple lightning instantly surged out from within, forming a purple light barrier that encompassed the entirety of the Six Integrations Wilderness Array.

A draconic roar rang out as the nine dragon projections flew out of the Nine Dragon Jewel, following which all of them swelled to around ten feet in length before pouncing at the stone archway.

A resounding boom rang out as the archway shuddered violently, and it immediately began to tremble after the nine purple dragons surged into the dark red light barrier.

Everyone immediately began injecting their immortal spiritual power into the array upon seeing this, and a hole began to slowly appear at the center of the dark red light barrier, revealing another space beyond it.

"It's working!" Jin Liu exclaimed with an ecstatic expression.

"We're still nowhere near done yet, so don't get complacent," Lei Yuce cautioned.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the nine Dragon Scale Chains bound to the stone archway suddenly began to glow with radiant, golden light, and a series of golden ripples erupted out of the chains to fill the entire dark red light barrier.

Furthermore, a burst of incredibly chaotic suction had emerged at the point where the golden light and the purple lightning met, sucking in all of the surrounding world's origin qi in a frenzy.

At this point, all that could be seen through the hole was a vast expanse of darkness, and the violent aura of spatial turbulence could be detected from the other side.

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon detecting this, and Lei Yuce yelled, "It looks like we've underestimated the power of the Nine Dragon Deity Locking Array. We have to make a concerted effort to open up a spatial passageway before the power of the array is fully activated!" Lei Yuce yelled.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the black vortex at the center of the stone archway suddenly shuddered violently, following which a burst of violent power erupted out from within.

At the same time, nine golden dragon projections shot out of the Dragon Scale Chains bound to the archway, then pounced at Lei Yuce and the others.

Everyone felt a burst of terrifying power surging directly toward them, and Jin Liu abandoned the array to make his escape, followed closely by the Lan siblings.

In the wake of their abrupt departure, the entire array instantly fell apart, and the Nine Dragon Jewel at the center of the array also exploded in an uncontrolled state, sending purple lightning erupting in all directions.

Wen Zhong also backed out of the array, and thus, Lei Yuce and Su Anqian were the only ones remaining inside, left to face the golden dragon projections and purple lightning on their own.

Both of them reacted very quickly, but they were standing on the two corners of the hexagonal array that were closest to the stone archway, leaving them with no time to escape.

Lei Yuce immediately sprang forward without any hesitation to place himself in front of Su Anqian, and a suit of purple lightning armor was beginning to take shape over his body, but it clearly wasn't going to fully materialize in time.

A resounding boom rang out as the golden dragon projections and purple lightning exploded violently.

At this point, Jin Liu and the others had already retreated to a safe distance away, and they were all observing the explosion with tense expressions.

Rays of golden light and arcs of purple lightning erupted in all directions in a chaotic fashion, violently stirring up all of the world's origin qi within a radius of dozens of kilometers.

The chaotic phenomenon raged on for close to a minute before finally subsiding, and as the dust settled, it was revealed that an enormous, charred crater had appeared in the ground.

All of the surrounding golden sand had been melted by the intense heat from the explosion, then cooled and solidified into huge golden plates of irregular shapes.

Outside the crater, the stone archway remained completely unharmed, and it had already reverted back to its original state.

Jin Liu and the others hurriedly flew over to the edge of the crater before looking down to discover a charred figure with a more petite figure held tightly in their arms.

The suit of silver lightning armor that had previously encased Lei Yuce's body had already completely disintegrated, and his robes were also in tatters.

His back was heaving violently, and his aura was fluctuating in an extremely unstable fashion, indicating that he had sustained very severe internal injuries.

In contrast, Su Anqian was completely unscathed.

Chapter 1082: Wanted Fugitive

Wen Zhong was the first one to rush into the crater, and Jin Liu hurriedly followed suit.

Jin Liu gently pried Lei Yuce away from Su Anqian, while Wen Zhong hurriedly caught the former to support him.

"Are you alright?" Jin Liu asked as he placed his hands onto Su Anqian's shoulders.

Su Anqian shrugged off his hands, then turned to look at Lei Yuce, who had just been fed a pill by Wen Zhong, but was still clearly in terrible condition.

Upon sensing Su Anqian's gaze, he turned to look back at her before putting up a strong front by flashing her a feeble smile.

Su Anqian averted her gaze upon seeing this, but internally, she was rather moved by Lei Yuce's selfless gesture. She knew that if it wasn't to protect her, he definitely wouldn't have sustained such severe injuries.

Meanwhile, Lei Yuce got up into a seated position with Wen Zhong's help, then closed his eyes and began to meditate.

As soon as he began channeling his cultivation arts, the residual golden light and purple lightning in his wounds were instantly forced out, and it was such a painful process that his face immediately became twisted with agony, but he remained silent the entire time.

A sympathetic look appeared in Su Anqian's eyes upon seeing this, and she strode over to Lei Yuce's side, then flipped a hand over to produce a small, blue vial, which she offered to him as she said, "These are some Prime Water Pills from our Heavenly Water Sect. They won't have much of an effect on your injuries, but they're quite potent for replenishing energy, so they should be quite helpful for your recovery."

"Thank you, Celestial Maiden Su," Lei Yuce said as he accepted the vial with an ecstatic expression, then tipped out a pill from inside and swallowed it before continuing to meditate.

A hint of displeasure flashed through Jin Liu's eyes upon seeing this, and he asked, "What do we do now?"

Wen Zhong gave a cold harrumph and offered no response, clearly very unhappy with Jin Liu for abandoning the array.

Lan Yan also turned to him with a disdainful expression, but before she had a chance to say anything, she was stopped by Lan Yuanzi.

In the wake of their battle against Han Li, Lan Yuanzi had become very averse to confrontation, and he shook his head to dissuade Lan Yan from speaking out against Jin Liu.

Lan Yan's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but she held her tongue in the end.

Right at this moment, all of them suddenly looked up into the sky to discover Han Li's group flying toward them from afar.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the severely ravaged ground below, and upon their landing, Lei Yuce also opened his eyes to see what was happening.

"Didn't you go another way? Why have you also come here?" Jin Liu asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"Is this Eon Pagoda your private property, Fellow Daoist Jin? Do we have to secure your permission before we come here?" Fox 3 countered as he raised an eyebrow, and Jin Liu had no response to this.

"Who's this, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Lei Yuce asked with his gaze on Qu Lin.

"This is Fellow Daoist Qu Lin. He's been held captive on the sixth level of this Eon Pagoda for many years, and we've arrived at an agreement, one in which he'll be helping us make our way to the seventh level," Han Li replied.

Lei Yuce was silent for a moment, then cautioned through voice transmission, "Fellow Daoist Shi, please remember that all of the beings trapped in this pagoda were once extremely renowned fugitives of the Heavenly Court, so making agreements with them could easily backfire if you're not careful."

Han Li was rather perplexed about why Lei Yuce was offering him these words of caution, but he offered no further explanation as he replied through voice transmission, "Thank you for looking out for me, Fellow Daoist Lei."

Right at this moment, Wyrm 3 suddenly remarked, "This is a Nine Dragon Deity Locking Array!"

"Indeed it is, Fellow Daoist. Are you able to bypass it?" Lei Yuce asked with a hopeful expression.

"The Dragon Scale Chains have been tampered with, so it's going to be a bit difficult," Wyrm 3 mused.

"Indeed. It would've taken me at least two days to unravel the array, so I attempted to break through it by force, only to suffer backlash from the array and sustain some rather severe injuries," Lei Yuce sighed with a forlorn shake of his head.

Han Li also turned his attention to the array, and after some observation, he was able to determine that it would only require less than a day for him to break it.

However, before he had a chance to say anything, Qu Lin had already strode over to the array before casually pressing a hand over the runes on the stone archway.

"What are you doing? Stop!" Lei Yuce hurriedly yelled, but given his current condition, he was powerless to intervene.

"Be quiet! I'm breaking the array, can't you see?" Qu Lin snapped as he continued what he was doing.

"The array has already been tampered with, so it must be treated with caution! If you try to address it haphazardly, you're only going to further compound our woes!" Lei Yuce said in an enraged manner, and Wen Zhong was preparing to intervene by force, while Jin Liu was observing from the side, ready to take Su Anqian and escape at the first sign of backlash from the array.

Right at this moment, Qu Lin pressed down onto one of the runes on the stone archway, and the dark red light barrier at its center instantly brightened significantly, while the nine Dragon Scale Chains slid away.

All of a sudden, the Nine Dragon Deity Locking Array was unraveled, just like that, much to everyone's astonishment.

"You were the one who tampered with this Nine Dragon Deity Locking Array in the first place, right?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"That's right. At the time, I thought that I would perhaps be able to find a way to leave this place if I could go to the seventh level. However, after reaching the seventh level, I was almost beaten to death by the old madman imprisoned up there. I only just barely managed to escape by the skin of my teeth, and after getting back, I reset the array before altering it for further fortification," Qu Lin revealed.

"How did you manage to return from the seventh level?" Han Li asked.

"Thankfully, I had the foresight to open up the Chaotic Origin Nine Palace Array on the other side after reaching the seventh level, so I had an escape route that I could take," Qu Lin explained.

Han Li nodded in response, then turned to everyone else as he said, "Now that the restriction's broken, let's not waste any more time."

Lei Yuce had some questions that he wanted to ask Han Li, but it was clear that the latter wasn't in the mood to do any explaining, so he didn't raise any questions.

However, no one was keen on stepping through the spatial door right away, and it seemed that everyone was quite apprehensive about what could be on the other side.

"If none of you are willing to go in, then I'll be going on ahead," Qu Lin sneered, then passed through the dark red light barrier and vanished out of sight.

Han Li conjured up a layer of protective spiritual light around himself, then also began to make his way toward the light barrier, but as soon as he took a step forward, a yellow vortex suddenly appeared beneath his feet, releasing tremendous suction force.

The vortex had appeared so abruptly that Han Li was caught completely off guard, and in the blink of an eye, close to the entirety of his lower body had sunken into it.

Despite the abrupt nature of this turn of events, Han Li was able to react very quickly, channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts right away, and two dull thumps rang out beneath his feet as he launched himself up into the air.

However, as soon as he flew out of the vortex, a burst of sludge also erupted out from within, then wrapped itself around his ankle before tugging him back down toward the vortex below.

In the instant that his ankle was caught within the burst of sludge, Han Li immediately felt his entire foot go numb, and he looked down to discover that both his foot and his boot had turned a gray, petrified state.

He immediately swept his other foot toward the burst of sludge, and countless arcs of golden lightning erupted out of the tip of foot to sever the sludge like a golden blade.

Immediately thereafter, he flew back over a thousand feet before landing on the edge of the giant, charred crater, where he cast a wary gaze toward the yellow vortex.

After all of the sludge had fallen back into the vortex, a yellow figure slowly emerged from within, and it was a hideous woman dressed in a large, yellow robe.

"Elder She Chan! What are you doing here?" Lan Yuanzi exclaimed.

"What am I doing here? To clean up your mess, of course! Even after all this time, you two still haven't managed to capture him!" She Chan snapped with a displeased expression.

Lan Yuanzi's brows furrowed slightly as he opened his mouth to explain himself, but didn't seem to know what to say.

Judging from everyone's reactions upon hearing mention of the name "She Chan", it was clear that they were well aware of who she was.

Han Li's gaze remained fixed on She Chan as he tried to move his petrified left foot, upon which he discovered that he had already regained feeling in it, but the blood flow to the foot still seemed to be slightly inhibited.

"Everyone, listen up! The man standing before you right now is Han Li, a member of the Reincarnation Palace and a wanted fugitive that the Heavenly Court has been hunting for many years! He is responsible for a long laundry list of crimes across various immortal regions, including the death of Golden Origin Immortal Palace Master Dongfang Bai!

“If you're willing to help me capture him, then you'll be putting both yourselves and your sects in the good graces of the Heavenly Court. What do you all say?" She Chan asked as she swept her gaze over everyone present.

Lei Yuce and the others were all completely rooted to the spot, clearly flabbergasted by this abrupt bombshell.

Chapter 1083: Reversal

After taking a moment to compose themselves, Lei Yuce exchanged a glance with Wen Zhong, and the former shook his head ever so slightly.

Wen Zhong gave a slight nod in response, and the two of them remained silent, seemingly content to serve as bystanders.

After some contemplation, Su Anqian also decided to remain an impartial observer, while Fox 3 and Wyrm 3 naturally remained silent as well.

She Chan swept her gaze over everyone one after another before settling her gaze on the Lan siblings.

Lan Yuanzi cupped his fist in an apologetic salute as he said, "Please forgive us, Elder She. Lan Yan and I have already sworn a vow against going after Fellow Daoist Han for as long as we're in the Eon Pagoda. If you need our help in apprehending him, then I'm afraid we'll only be able to lend you our assistance once we've left this place."

"Are you an idiot? What does a trivial vow matter for in the face of the greater good? Have you forgotten our objective for hunting down this man?" She Chan snapped.

Lan Yuanzi's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, but after a brief hesitation, he maintained his cupped fist salute with his head lowered, and Lan Yan also did the same.

"Fine, do as you please then! Once we return to the sect, I'm going to report this matter to our patriarch and have your master provide an explanation for this farce!" She Chan said in a furious voice.

Lan Yan's expression changed drastically upon hearing this, but before she could do anything, Lan Yuanzi tugged on her sleeve as he said through voice transmission, "We can bear the consequences of disobeying orders, but if we go back on a vow, then our master will be extremely disappointed in us."

Lan Yan bowed her head again upon hearing this.

She Chan was feeling very embarrassed by the fact that even the fellow members of her own sect were unwilling to help her, and she threatened in a cold voice, "I hope you two won't come to regret this."

All the while, Jin Liu was looking on with a hint of schadenfreude in his eyes.

He knew that the more enraged She Chan became, the more ruthless she was going to be against Han Li, and that was naturally a very welcome sight for him.

Meanwhile, Han Li remained standing on the spot with a calm and relaxed expression, pondering how he was going to deal with She Chan.

He probably doesn't even realize just how screwed he is! Jin Liu scoffed internally at the sight of Han Li's composed display.

"If you're all going to just stand by and watch, then make sure you stay back and don't do anything out of line!" She Chan warned, then abruptly vanished from the spot without any warning, leaving only a ball of yellow light where she had been standing just a moment ago.

Everyone immediately backed away far into the distance upon seeing this, and in the next instant, a violent sandstorm rose up from behind Han Li before converging toward him from all directions.

Han Li was already prepared for this, and he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability to instantly vanish from the spot, escaping from the sandstorm in the process.

As soon as the sandstorm closed in around the spot where Han Li had been standing just a moment ago, countless grains of sand instantly erupted in all directions, and a yellow light barrier emerged from within before spreading outward, encompassing the entire surrounding area with a radius of dozens of kilometers in the blink of an eye.

Caught within the light barrier, Han Li instantly felt a burst of tremendous gravitational force crash down upon him, as if he were being crushed under several invisible mountains, thereby severely hampering his movement.

The scenery within She Chan's spirit domain was constantly shifting, and a series of short and barren mountains had appeared on the edge of the spirit domain.

As for the area near Han Li, numerous yellow swamps of different shapes and sizes had appeared on the ground, and there was earthy yellow sludge flowing inside, with large bubbles occasionally emerging from within them.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon catching a whiff of the nauseating odor of rot and decay in the air, and right at this moment, a burst of low croaking suddenly rang out from nearby.

Han Li hurriedly turned in that direction to discover the head of a toad that was the size of a house exposed above the surface of a swamp no more than several thousand feet away from him.

Its two golden eyes were staring at him in a cold and emotionless manner, and the dense clusters of warts on its skin presented a disgusting and unsettling sight to behold.

With a flick of his wrist, thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords appeared around Han Li in unison, and they circled around in the air momentarily before hurtling directly toward the giant, yellow toad.

The swords left a trail of golden lightning in their wake, but due to the effects of the earth law powers within the spirit domain, they were traveling far slower than usual. However, the power imbued within them hadn't been diminished in the slightest.

Right as the flying swords were about to reach it, the yellow toad suddenly vanished into the swamp.

Han Li hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique upon seeing this, trying to use his spiritual sense to track it down, but all he could detect was a boundless sea of earth law powers.

She's able to use her spirit domain as cover and perfectly conceal her own aura within it! This could be troublesome...

Right at this moment, the ground beneath Han Li's feet reared up violently as the giant toad abruptly emerged from below, flinging him up into the air.

Han Li remained calm and composed as he swiftly swept a sleeve through the air, and his thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords immediately began flying back to his side.

However, before the flying swords could reach him, a huge shadow suddenly appeared up above. As it turned out, a huge mountain had suddenly flown over from afar, and it was in the process of crashing down directly upon him.

An ordinary mountain of this size wouldn't have posed any threat to Han Li, but given that it had been manifested within She Chan's Spiritform Stage spirit domain, it was sure to contain boundless earth law powers that would grant it unfathomable weight.

With that in mind, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he flicked his wrist upward, and his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly began flying upward at his behest.

Right as the mountain was about to crash down upon Han Li, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords pierced into its underside, then began releasing a flurry of golden lightning and azure sword projections.

A vast sea of golden lightning erupted out of the flying swords, holding the mountain aloft to arrest its fall, while Han Li channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, then began plummeting out of the sky in an upside-down orientation with his fist held close to his waist, as if he were preparing to throw an almighty punch.

A massive crater had already opened up on the ground below, and the giant, yellow toad was springing upward with its cavernous mouth wide open to swallow Han Li whole.

Within mere moments, Han Li had already plunged headfirst into the yellow toad's mouth, and the toad instantly closed its mouth to devour him.

However, at the same time, Han Li threw a punch downward with resplendent starlight glowing from his fist.

A vast expanse of blinding, white light erupted within the toad's mouth, which was quickly forced open by a burst of tremendous power that exploded outward from within.

Immediately thereafter, the giant toad's entire body exploded with a resounding boom.

In the wake of the yellow toad's demise, the surrounding spirit domain rapidly shrank down to only around a tenth of its original size, and the light radiating from it also began to gradually dim, as if the spirit domain were about to vanish altogether.

At the same time, the mountain up above disintegrated into yellow sludge that rained down from the heavens like a mudslide.

Han Li had no time to evade the falling sludge, and it cascaded down onto his entire body.

With a flick of his wrist, he withdrew his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords back up his sleeve, while everyone was looking on with bewildered expressions, clearly incredulous that a Great Encompassment cultivator had been defeated and slain so easily.

Among them, Jin Liu was displaying the strongest reaction, one of both disappointment and indignation.

However, right at this moment, Han Li abruptly stiffened like a clay statue, then plummeted out of the sky in a completely uncontrolled fashion before crashing down onto the ground with a resounding thump.

An alarmed look immediately appeared on Wyrm 3's face as she began rushing to Han Li's aid, only to be stopped in her tracks by Fox 3, who yelled in an urgent voice, "What are you doing? Have you forgotten our mission? We need to remain focused on the big picture!"

Wyrm 3 stopped in her tracks upon hearing this, but her gaze remained fixed on Han Li.

The yellow sludge that had fallen onto him earlier had solidified into a cloak of clay that encased his entire body, and it was as if he had truly been transformed into a clay statue.

Furthermore, this cloak of clay was riddled with strange patterns that were giving off extremely formidable earth law power fluctuations, forming a powerful seal that trapped him inside.

Initially, Han Li was still able to struggle slightly against the cloak of clay, but as the coloration of the clay rapidly darkened, he was quickly rendered completely immobilized.

Only after the layer of clay had completely dried did a palm-sized toad jump out of a nearby swamp before transforming into She Chan's human form, who turned to the clay statue beside her with a derisive sneer in her eyes.

Chapter 1084: Secret Arrangement

Lei Yuce and the others hesitated momentarily upon seeing this, then began to fly toward She Chan, clearly under the impression that the battle was over.

There was a look of schadenfreude in Jin Liu's eyes as he flew toward She Chan with everyone else, while Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 remained where they were, seemingly rather hesitant about how to proceed.

"You were trying to help him earlier, right? Are you also a member of the Reincarnation Palace? If so, then don't hold back. What if you can still save him?" She Chan chuckled as she turned to Wyrm 3 with a provocative expression.

A furious look appeared in Wyrm 3's eyes as her hands balled up into tight fists.

"So you really are an accomplice of his! You..."

All of a sudden, She Chan's voice trailed off mid-sentence as a burst of golden light surged over the clay statue that Han Li was encased in, and a strange-looking golden tree projection suddenly appeared, then began to rapidly grow, sprouting branches and vines that wrapped themselves around the clay statue.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of formidable time law powers erupted forth amid a flash of blinding golden light, and the layer of clay around Han Li reverted back into a pool of yellow sludge that flowed onto the ground, following which Han Li sprang forward with the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in his hand aimed directly at She Chan.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and She Chan immediately attempted to dart back in retreat, only to discover that a layer of strange golden sand had appeared on the ground below, reaching up to her ankles to root her to the ground.

She could feel a burst of peculiar time law power fluctuations emanating from the golden sand below, completely immobilizing her legs.

Before she had a chance to do anything, the vines from the golden tree projection also snaked their way over to her before wrapping themselves around her upper body.

At the same time, the Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind Han Li, further immobilizing She Chan.

Han Li plunged his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword down without any hesitation directly upon She Chan's chest, where her heart was situated, and due to how abruptly this sequence of events had unfolded, everyone else was also caught within Han Li's time law powers, rendering them completely immobile.

A loud, metallic clang rang out as the tip of Han Li's sword struck She Chan's chest, raising a trail of golden sparks, but the sword wasn't able to pierce through her skin!

Han Li was clearly rather taken aback to see this, and right at this moment, a series of yellow runes appeared over She Chan's body, releasing bursts of earth law power fluctuations that began to contend against the time law power fluctuations released by the manifestations of Han Li's three time-attribute law treasures.

As one of the three paramount laws, the laws of time held a natural advantage over She Chan's law powers, and it was only due to She Chan's superior cultivation base and mastery over her law powers that she was able to contend against Han Li at all.

The surrounding time law power fluctuations were slowly forced back, and a layer of earthy yellow light appeared around She Chan, creating a small safe zone around her as her mobility was gradually restored.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly injected more immortal spiritual power into his three time-attribute law treasures to tighten their hold on She Chan.

She Chan had only fallen for his trap in a moment of complacency, so if he were to allow her to escape now, then it was going to be very difficult for him to trap her again.

Thanks to the influx of immortal spiritual power, the three time-attribute law treasures were able to slowly eradicate the safezone that had appeared around She Chan, rendering her completely immobile again.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief upon seeing this, then swept a sleeve through the air to release thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, all of which released countless arcs of golden lightning to form a dense sea of golden lightning.

The sea of golden lightning was churning incessantly as a golden dragon reared its head from within, then let loose a thunderous, draconic roar before twisting around and swooping down upon She Chan with unstoppable might.

Countless tiny spatial rifts were left in the wake of the golden lightning sword dragon, and the entire desert began to tremble violently as if an earthquake were taking place.

Right as the golden dragon was about to devour She Chan, a burst of blue light suddenly appeared behind Han Li without any warning.

It was a fist-sized blue bead with several golden runes glowing on its surface, and a burst of blue light abruptly erupted forth from within, forming an enormous blue vortex in the blink of an eye.

The entirety of Han Li's attention was focused on controlling his time-attribute law treasures and containing She Chan, so by the time he detected what was happening behind him, it was already too late.

He felt a burst of tremendous power sweep toward him from behind, and a resounding thump rang out as he was sent flying forward, resulting in a loss of control over his time-attribute law treasures and his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The sword dragon formed by the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords disintegrated into thin air right before it descended upon She Chan, while all of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords themselves automatically flew back into Han Li's body.

After flying several thousand feet through the air, Han Li was finally able to steady himself before turning to Lei Yuce and the others with a furious look on his face.

At this moment, everyone was staring at Jin Liu with surprised expressions.

He was the one who had just attacked Han Li with that Chaotic Origin Infernal Water Bead, and in the wake of this inexplicable attack, Su Anqian exclaimed with an incredulous expression, "Why did you do that?"

"Why? He's a wanted fugitive of the Heavenly Court, should we not all be playing our part to capture him! You are the ones at fault for not helping Senior She, while I'm the one doing the right thing!" Jin Liu declared in a righteous and justified manner.

"Are you not afraid that your actions will bring disaster to our Heavenly Water Sect? How is making an enemy out of the Reincarnation Palace any more appealing than opposing the Heavenly Court?" Su Anqian countered in an enraged manner.

"Are you saying that I should serve as an accomplice to a wanted fugitive? In that case..."

Before Jin Liu had a chance to finish, She Chan interjected, "Why not just tell the truth, Fellow Daoist Jin? In accordance with the agreement that we just struck up through voice transmission, I'll help you claim Celestial Maiden Su over here as long as you help me capture Han Li."

An awkward look appeared on Jin Liu's face upon hearing this, but he quickly composed himself as he said, "In any case, let's capture Han Li first."

By revealing their secret agreement, She Chan had backed Jin Liu into a corner, giving him no choice but to help her, and he was naturally very displeased by this betrayal, but he didn't dare to express any dissatisfaction.

At this moment, everyone was glowering at him with intense disdain in their eyes, and there was even a hint of a killing intent in Lei Yuce's eyes.

The Chaotic Origin Infernal Water Bead had interrupted Han Li and allowed She Chan to free herself, but thankfully, it hadn't managed to inflict any injuries upon him.

Han Li suppressed the fury in his heart as he tightened his grip around his combined Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, then swooped down upon She Chan from above.

This time, She Chan was regarding him in a much more serious manner, clearly having learned her lesson from their earlier exchange.

With a flick of her wrist, her spirit domain was conjured up once again, transforming the surrounding landscape into one of mountains and swamps.

Sludge began to rise up from the ground before transforming into a series of giant hands that made a grab for Han Li, and he had only managed to fly several thousand feet through the air before another mountain came crashing down upon him.

The gravitational force in the surrounding space became heavier and heavier, and as a result, he was slowed down further and further.

"Let me help you, Fellow Daoist Han," Wyrm 3 said, following which she released her dark red spirit domain.

Situated within her spirit domain, Han Li instantly felt a significant reduction in the potency of the gravitational force acting upon him.

Before he had a chance to thank her, Fox 3 also summoned his spirit domain as he sighed, "Looks like I'll have to get involved as well."

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and true spirit bloodlines in unison, instantly taking on the form of a giant devilish deity with three heads and six arms.

"That confirms it! Those two are also members of the Reincarnation Palace! Help me take them down, fellow daoists!" She Chan yelled.

Lei Yuce and the others remained completely unmoved, and even the Lan siblings had turned away to stoically ignore her.

"Are all of you planning to rebel against the Heavenly Court?!" She Chan yelled in a furious voice, but there was nothing that she could do as she sprang up into the air to meet Han Li.

With a flick of her wrist, a huge club appeared in her grasp. The club was giving off bursts of formidable earth law power fluctuations, clearly indicating that it was a very powerful immortal treasure.

At this point, Han Li had already drawn upon all of the starpower in his body, as well as his True Dragon, Kun Peng, and Giant Mountain Ape bloodlines, and Divine Devilbane Lightning was pouring out of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in a frenzy, forming an enormous lightning sword that he swung down with almighty power.

Meanwhile, layers upon layers of black rock were appearing over the surface of She Chan's club, granting it an astronomical amount of weight, and it had also conjured up a giant club projection to oppose Han Li's lightning sword.

Chapter 1085: Defeating the Enemy

The lightning sword clashed against the club projection with a deafening boom, sending incredibly powerful shockwaves sweeping through the air in all directions.

Amid the shockwaves, a projection of a golden dragon and a Kun Peng could be seen crashing into the club projection one after the other to tear it apart, immediately following which a giant ape projection descended upon She Chan while swinging its fists down with tremendous power.

The club projection was the first to break, allowing the giant lightning sword to crash down from above unopposed.

"Impossible!" She Chan exclaimed as a large crack appeared over her club, following which a long gash was sliced into her body from her shoulder to her chest, and she was sent flying back through the air.

Arcs of golden lightning clung tenaciously to her wound, and instead of dissipating, they infiltrated her body to attack her internal organs.

She Chan's skin was extremely resilient, even among early-Great Encompassment cultivators, but her internal organs were rather special and were far more vulnerable.

Hence, if she were to allow the golden lightning to wreak havoc in her body as it pleased, then even her cultivation foundation could be permanently damaged.

With that in mind, She Chan plunged straight down into a swamp below, clearly having decided that her best option was to flee.

Jin Liu immediately also fled the scene upon seeing this, but he was confronted by Wyrm 3 and Fox 3 before he could get away.

Instead of pursuing Jin Liu, Han Li remained hovering up in the sky in his three-headed devilish deity form, scouring his gaze over the landscape in search of She Chan.

Right at this moment, an agonized howl suddenly rang out from down below, following which a figure with silver flames burning all over their body flew up into the air.

Their clothes were in tatters, their hair was completely disheveled, their body was riddled with wounds, and it was none other than She Chan.

Chasing after her in hot pursuit was the Essence Fire Raven, and Han Li immediately pounced at her as well while swinging his sword through the air again.

Another giant, golden lightning sword came crashing down from the heavens, and conflicted looks appeared on the faces of the Lan siblings upon seeing this.

The two of them were very close with She Chan, and if her life were under threat, then they would be forced to intervene.

However, before they had a chance to do anything, She Chan suddenly roared in a resentful voice, "You'll pay for this!"

As soon as her voice trailed off, a gash suddenly appeared over her glabella, following which a longan-sized white bead flew out from within before rising up toward Han Li's giant lightning sword.

"Look out! She's going to detonate her own beast core!" Lei Yuce exclaimed as he reflexively positioned himself in front of Su Anqian.

"No, that's her Toad Moon Jewel!" Lan Yuanzi yelled, and Wyrm 3's expression changed slightly upon hearing this.

It was said that there was a special type of toad demon beasts that possessed a Toad Moon Jewel in their bodies in addition to their beast cores, and the jewel allowed them to enhance their rate of cultivation progression by absorbing the power of moonlight.

The importance of this Toad Moon Jewel was third only to their nascent soul and demon core.

As a Great Encompassment cultivator, the Toad Moon Jewel in She Chan's body had to have already been accumulating power for countless years, and its detonation was surely going to have catastrophic effects.

With that in mind, everyone hurriedly fled into the distance.

Xiong Shan knew that he was the weakest of everyone present, and he had already fled far into the distance ahead of everyone else.

A hint of foreboding had also welled up in Han Li's heart, but it was already too late for him to withdraw his sword.

The Toad Moon Jewel trembled violently for a moment, then exploded to produce an eruption of blinding light, which then suddenly faded away before the entire sky turned dark, as if day had suddenly transitioned into night.

A ray of cold moonlight shone down from above, basking the entire landscape in a silver glow.

It was as if the entire space had been frozen solid by the cold moonlight, following which everything shattered like a silver mirror, and countless dark spatial rifts appeared in the air.

Bursts of spatial turbulence could be seen raging within the spatial rifts, releasing terrifying spatial fluctuations that instantly had everyone fleeing for their lives.

However, there were simply far too many spatial rifts in the area, making it very difficult to avoid all of them.

In a lapse of concentration, Su Anqian was almost swallowed up by a spatial rift that had abruptly opened up behind her, and it was Lei Yuce who swooped in once again to save her.

Having been saved by him twice, Su Anqian had finally begun to develop a hint of affection for him, and her eyes were no longer as cold as before when she gazed upon him.

However, Jin Liu wasn't so fortunate. He had been surrounded by everyone earlier, so he was the last to flee the scene, and he had only managed to travel a few thousand feet before he crashed headfirst into an enormous spatial rift.

He forcibly twisted his body to the side to try and glide through the air in a parallel direction to the spatial rift, but the tremendous suction force released by the rift was too much for him to resist, and he was sucked in inch by inch, with not even his nascent soul managing to escape.

The area directly surrounding the Toad Moon Jewel had the highest concentration of spatial rifts, and at this point, She Chan was already nowhere to be seen. All that remained was Han Li with his Mantra Treasured Axis hovering behind him, releasing waves of golden light to slow the expansion of the spatial rifts.

At this moment, he was holding a green gourd with its mouth pointed directly up ahead.

A green vortex was swirling incessantly at the gourd's mouth, and it was gathering some translucent silver particles in the surrounding area before condensing them to reform the Toad Moon Jewel.

The jewel had been absorbing moonlight for countless years, and Han Li instinctively felt like it would be very useful to him, so he had chosen to recover it.

After that, he summoned his Essence Fire Raven back to his side, then traversed through the multitude of spatial rifts as he descended back down to the ground.

There seemed to be some type of tacit understanding between everyone as they all remained silent, with no one mentioning the battle that had just taken place, and all of them took a few pills before sitting down to meditate.

After taking some to rest and recuperate, Han Li rose to his feet as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute toward everyone.

"Thank you, fellow daoists."

Even though all of them had chosen to refrain from helping She Chan mostly out of consideration for their own self interest, it was still undeniable that their decision had helped Han Li.

"There's no need to thank us, Fellow Daoist Han. You dealt with her purely through your own powers," Lei Yuce said.

"My eyes have truly been opened, Brother Han..." Xiong Shan mused with mixed emotions in his eyes.

"Time is of the essence, so let's continue onward," Han Li said, and everyone nodded in response before making their way into the spatial door one after another.

Han Li's vision blurred momentarily, following which he found himself standing in a gray cave.

The cave was quite large, and it extended into shadowy darkness up ahead, making it impossible to tell how long it was.

Gusts of yin wind were blowing toward everyone from up ahead, and the air temperature in the cave was quite low, as evidenced by the layer of black frost on the stone walls on either side.

Lei Yuce and the others appeared nearby one after another, then also began inspecting their surroundings.

All of a sudden, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he noticed that Qu Lin was nowhere to be seen, even though he had come through first.

Everyone else's expressions also darkened slightly upon noticing Qu Lin's absence, but Han Li chose not to bring up the matter as he said, "Let's go. Make sure to be on your guard, everyone."

In the wake of his most recent display of power, no one felt it inappropriate for him to adopt a leadership role, and everyone was content to follow him.

Spiritual sense was suppressed even further on the seventh level, so as a safety precaution, everyone chose to proceed on foot rather than by flight. Thankfully, given everyone's lofty cultivation bases, they were still able to make very fast progress, nonetheless.

However, this underground cave was unexpectedly long, and even after traveling for over ten minutes, there was still no end in sight. On top of that, the further they went, the more fierce the surrounding yin winds became.

All of a sudden, Han Li stopped in his tracks as he warned, "Be careful, everyone!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, seven or eight monstrous creatures with human faces and wolf bodies appeared up ahead.

Each of these creatures was several dozen feet in length, and their bodies were covered in long, reddish-brown fur that resembled bamboo fiber cloaks, and as they pounced at Han Li's group, they displayed exceptional speed and offensive prowess.

Gust of black wind erupted out of the claws, easily leaving deep marks on the ground and walls of the cave, the edges of which were charred black as if by some form of corrosion.

Lei Yuce and the others were alarmed by this sudden turn of events, but they remained composed as they lashed out in retaliation against these creatures.

The wolf-like creatures seemed to have realized that they had bitten off more than they could chew, and they opened their mouths to release a sea of reddish-black flames in an attempt to ward off everyone's attacks.

However, this proved to be futile as the barrage of attacks tore through the sea of fire with ease before destroying the wolf-like creatures on the other side.

After they were slain, the bodies of the wolf-like creatures quickly disintegrated into black smoke, but each of them left a fist-sized reddish-black bead behind.

"What are these things?" Wen Zhong asked with an intrigued expression as he raised a hand to release a burst of golden light toward the beads.

"Don't touch them!" Han Li hurriedly yelled, but it was already too late, and as soon as the golden light released by Wen Zhong came into contact with the beads, they immediately exploded into balls of radiant reddish-black light that swept through the air in all directions.

Chapter 1086: Ancient Sword

A deafening boom rang out as a wave of reddish-black light swept over the entire cave, causing it to collapse, and Han Li's group was buried under a vast volume of rubble.

Thankfully, everyone was well-versed in earth movement techniques, and they were able to burrow their way into the ground right as the cave collapsed.

However, as soon as they made their way underground, a burst of sinister cackling instantly rang out, immediately following which a giant black claw the size of a house emerged from deeper underground to make a grab for everyone.

The giant claw was attached to a massive, lizard-like creature, but its body was far more bloated than that of a lizard.

The creature was lurking underground, and its aura was completely indistinguishable from that of the earth around it, so its sneak attack had caught everyone completely off guard.

By the time everyone realized that there was something lurking underground, it was already too late to take evasive measures.

Right as everyone was about to fall into the grasp of the giant creature, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a bolt of radiant golden lightning that struck the oncoming claw with a loud thump.

The bolt of lightning was tiny compared with the black claw, but it was able to tear through the latter with ease, following which it struck the giant beast's chest, blasting a hole the size of a water vat into its body.

The lizard-like creature let loose a blood-curdling howl, and it immediately attempted to flee deeper underground, but by then, Lei Yuce and the others had also begun lashing out against.

The creature was instantly overwhelmed by a devastating barrage of attacks, tearing its body to shreds.

As was the case with the wolf-like beasts from earlier, its body also disintegrated into black smoke, and even though it was underground, it still spread rapidly in all directions, staining all of the soil and rocks that it came into contact with black.

The black smoke instantly swept over everyone, and they hurriedly conjured up layers of protective spiritual light to try and keep it at bay.

Xiong Shan was at the very back of the group, and he did the same thing, managing to ward off the black smoke with a layer of golden spiritual light, but right at this moment, an extremely faint glimmer of black light shot out of the black smoke before piercing through Xiong Shan's protective spiritual light and vanishing into his body.

However, this went completely undetected by everyone, including even Xiong Shan himself.

After slaying the lizard beast, everyone continued onward for quite some time, and only after advancing beyond the collapsed section of the underground cave did they return to the surface.

"My sincerest apologies, everyone. My rash actions placed all of you in a perilous situation," Wen Zhong said in an apologetic manner.

"There's no need to be so self-critical, Fellow Daoist Wen. None of us could've anticipated that those beads would explode upon contact," Su Anqian consoled. "By the way, Fellow Daoist Han, you seemed to be aware of what those things were, would you be able to enlighten us?"

Everyone else also turned their attention to Han Li upon hearing this, and he explained, "Those wolf-like creatures were Devilish Corpse Wolves, a type of devil beast found in the Devil Realm, so it's no surprise that none of you recognized them. These creatures manifest Corpse Fire Beads in their bodies that instantly explode upon contact with any other type of energy."

Everyone was enlightened upon hearing this, but at the same time, they couldn't help but wonder how Han Li was familiar with these creatures. Could it be that he had been to the Devil Realm before?

Despite everyone's curiosity, no one dared to pry, and the group continued onward in silence.

After advancing for roughly another fifteen minutes, a huge, open area that was over a hundred times larger than the cave from before appeared up ahead.

There were piles of golden ore strewn all over the area, with the largest ones piling up to several hundred feet tall to resemble small mountains, while the smallest ones were only slightly taller than the average adult human, and it seemed that they had been arranged in a set formation.

Everyone exchanged a few wary glances with one another upon seeing this, and they carefully proceeded into the area.

Thankfully, after stepping into the array of ores, nothing happened, and after a brief pause, everyone continued onward.

Before long, they had already traveled for close to ten kilometers.

All of a sudden, there were no more piles of ore to be seen, and a small plaza appeared up ahead.

The plaza was paved with radiant, golden tiles, and at its center stood a golden altar that was over a thousand feet tall. The altar was split up into the three tiers and was entirely constructed from a type of golden material. Furthermore, the structure appeared to consist of only a single piece, with no signs of connective segments to be seen.

At the top of the altar was a golden platform that was around ten feet in size, engraved onto which was a golden yin yang symbol. Pierced into one side of the yin yang symbol was a strange, golden sword with a three-sided blade. On one side was engraved the sun, the moon, and stars, on another side was engraved a piece of scenery complete with mountains, rivers, and forests, and on the final side were engravings of a dragon and a phoenix.

Bright, golden light was emanating from the ancient sword, releasing bursts of metal law power fluctuations that struck everyone with a slightly painful sensation, as if their skin were about to be sliced open.

Hovering above the other side of the yin yang symbol was a golden flame the size of a human head, giving off bursts of formidable time law power fluctuations.

Bursts of golden runes were flowing out of the yin yang symbol, spreading over the entire altar to form a cage-shaped array.

The metal and time law powers intertwined with one another, and not only were they not in conflict at all, they coexisted extremely harmoniously, encompassing the entire altar.

However, what was far less harmonious was the giant black rift above the altar, out of which gusts of howling black wind were blowing incessantly, looking as if they were coming straight from the depths of hell.

The array of ore around the plaza seemed to have an aura concealment effect, so no one had detected the existence of the altar prior to this, and everyone was immediately rooted to the spot by the enormous aura that the altar was releasing.

"What is this? A seal?" Su Anqian exclaimed with a stunned expression.

Han Li was also observing the altar with a surprised expression, and his gaze quickly fell upon the ancient sword and the golden flame at the top of the altar.

That sword is forged from none other than Heavenly Vajra Diamond! No wonder it has such a powerful aura! As for that golden flame, the time law powers imbued within it are very peculiar. It's completely different from any of the five types of law powers in the Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra...

In contrast with everyone's stunned reactions, Lei Yuce and Wen Zhong were much more composed, and they exchanged an elated glance with one another.

At the very back of the group, Xiong Shan was completely rooted to the spot at the sight of the ancient, golden sword at the top of the altar, and his breathing began to accelerate as a look of intense desire appeared in his eyes.

He swept his gaze briefly over Han Li and the others, then abruptly shot forth through the air while conjuring up a giant, golden hand that made a grab for the ancient sword.

"Don't be reckless, Fellow Daoist Xiong!"

Everyone was very alarmed to see this, and in particular, Lei Yuce and Wen Zhong flew forward in unison to try and stop Xiong Shan, but it was already too late.

A resounding boom rang out as the golden hand closed itself around the ancient sword, only for countless streaks of golden swordlight to erupt out of the sword, tearing the giant hand into ribbons with ease.

On top of that, the sword began to tremble and buzz as if it had been enraged by Xiong Shan's gestures, and it released a flurry of translucent sword qi that erupted through the air in all directions.

Everyone hurriedly sprang into action to defend themselves from the streaks of formidable sword qi.

The Lan siblings were facing each other as Lan Yuanzi opened his mouth to release a blue bead, which had eight blue, dragon-shaped runes engraved upon it.

The blue bead transformed into a spherical light barrier that was several dozen feet in size at his behest, encompassing both himself and Lan Yan.

At the same time, Wyrm 3 swept a sleeve through the air to release a small shield amid a flash of white light, and the shield swelled rapidly in size before transforming into a white light barrier around herself and Fox 3.

Lei Yuce and Wen Zhong were also working together, releasing numerous small, golden flags out of their sleeves, which descended onto the ground to form a circle around them.

The flags released bursts of dazzling, golden light, forming a golden array that encompassed both of them within it, following which Lei Yuce turned to Su Anqian as he urged, "Come in here, Celestial Maiden Su!"

The golden array then extended toward her at his behest to encompass her within it, elongating the circular array into an oval.

A series of mixed emotions flashed through Su Anqian's eyes, but she didn't take any evasive measures, allowing the golden light barrier to enshroud her.

However, for her part, she summoned a large, blue flag, which released a burst of blue ripples to form a separate blue light barrier that also encompassed all three of them.

Meanwhile, Han Li let loose a low roar as all of his profound acupoints lit up, following which his True Extreme Film surfaced over his body.

On top of that, he swept a sleeve through the air to release thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, which circled around him to form a golden sword barrier with arcs of lightning flashing over its surface.

Immediately thereafter, the streaks of translucent sword qi descended upon him, striking the golden sword barrier from all directions.

The sword barrier began trembling violently as a string of loud explosions rang out, and even though the thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords remained unharmed, the sword array that they had formed was on the verge of falling apart.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he flew back in retreat along with his sword array while releasing two thick bolts of golden lightning out of his hands into the surrounding sword array.

The array had been on the verge of collapse, but it was instantly stabilized.

However, several streaks of translucent sword qi still managed to sneak through and strike him before the array was completely stabilized.

Thankfully, his True Extreme Film was able to withstand them with ease.

One's True Extreme Film became more powerful as one opened more profound acupoints. Having already opened close to a thousand profound acupoints, Han Li's True Extreme Film was more powerful than any defensive immortal treasure in his possession.

At this point, he had flown out of the range of the sword qi, and he descended onto a pile of ore outside the plaza.

Chapter 1087: Abnormal Actions

Han Li had managed to ward off the translucent sword qi without much trouble, but the same didn't apply to everyone.

A series of gashes were quickly torn into the spherical light barrier around the Lan siblings, and it began to flash erratically, on the verge of collapse.

Their expressions changed drastically upon seeing this, and they hurriedly released a series of blue law threads that fused into the barrier to fortify it.

Eight blue dragon projections instantly appeared over its surface, letting loose draconic roars as they roamed over the light barrier.

As a result, the spherical light barrier was instantly stabilized, and the Lan siblings were also able to fly out of the plaza to reach safety.

Inside the protective barrier, one of Lan Yuanzi's arms had been severed at the elbow, and there was also a deep gash on Lan Yan's shoulder.

These streaks of translucent sword qi had been far more powerful than they anticipated. Thankfully, they had summoned their most powerful defensive immortal treasure, the Eight Dragon Water Bead. Otherwise, they would've surely lost their lives.

Similarly, a series of gashes had also been sliced into the white light barrier around Wyrm 3 and Fox 3, putting it on the verge of collapse.

In this dire situation, Wyrm 3 pressed both of her hands against the light barrier, and two bursts of dark red light erupted out of the palms of her hands, forming a dark red light barrier that was imbued with a burst of reincarnation law powers.

The dark red light barrier wasn't particularly thick, but it was extremely resilient and managed to keep the oncoming sword qi firmly at bay.

However, instead of retreating out of the plaza, the two of them were staring intently at the golden altar up ahead.

As for Lei Yuce and Wen Zhong, both of them were casting a rapid stream of incantation seals into the golden array around them, and a golden sword projection that was over a thousand feet tall instantly appeared within the array.

All of the translucent sword qi that pierced into the array were instantly tamed, circling around the golden sword projection momentarily before fusing into it.

Where's Xiong Shan? He's not already dead, is he?

Han Li scanned his gaze over the surrounding area in search of Xiong Shan, only to discover that the latter was currently flying toward the golden altar with a cloud of golden mist around him.

The golden mist was giving off insubstantial sword intent that resembled clouds and mist, and the streaks of oncoming translucent sword qi merely passed straight through his body without harming him at all.

What kind of secret technique is this?

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he took a closer look, upon which he discovered that even though the cloud of golden mist was keeping Xiong Shan safe from the oncoming sword qi, with each streak of sword qi that passed through him, the cloud of mist would be whittled down slightly.

However, to everyone's surprise, not only did Xiong Shan not fall back in retreat, he continued to pounce on the ancient sword, and in the blink of an eye, he was no more than a hundred feet away from it.

The golden flame beside the golden sword seemed to have detected something, and it immediately swelled drastically in size before releasing bursts of golden fire that fused with the sword qi released by the ancient sword.

As a result, the streaks of translucent sword qi were instantly granted a faint, golden glow, transforming them into streaks of fiery sword qi.

Enhanced by the flames, the storm of sword qi swelled to several times its original size, encompassing the entire area around the altar in a radius of close to ten thousand feet.

The cloud of golden mist around Xiong Shan was instantly completely inundated by fiery sword qi, and it began to rapidly shrink as a string of agonized howls rang out from within it.

Fox 3, Wyrm 3, and Lei Yuce's trio were also instantly inundated by the fiery sword qi, as were Han Li and the Lan siblings.

Streaks of fiery sword qi fell upon the sword barrier around Han Li, instantly tearing it apart, and the thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were knocked flying like falling leaves in a gust of fierce wind.

After breaching the golden sword array, the fiery sword qi fell upon Han Li, and this time, a series of deep gashes were sliced into his True Extreme Film, almost tearing through the film entirely.

In response, Han Li hurriedly summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, which released waves of golden ripples that encompassed the entire area within a radius of over a thousand feet around him.

Enshrouded within the golden ripples, the streaks of fiery sword qi was slowed down significantly, but they were still hurtling toward him, just at a far more lethargic pace.

Han Li was rather surprised to see that the fiery sword qi hadn't been stopped entirely by his time law powers, but it then quickly dawned on him that this had to have been a result of the golden flames that had been injected into the sword qi.

The Time Severing Torch appeared beside the Mantra Treasured Axis at Han Li's behest, and it released a burst of fiery, golden light that manifested the Time Severing Fire Domain.

Thanks to the drastic increase in the number of time law threads in the Time Severing Torch, its powers had been significantly enhanced, to the point that the time-stopping power of Han Li's Time Severing Fire Domain was almost on par with that of Qi Mozi's spirit domain.

The streaks of fiery sword qi were finally stopped in their tracks after entering the Time Severing Fire Domain, but right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out from the direction of the Lan siblings.

A radiant, blue sun that was several thousand feet in size abruptly appeared before radiating dazzling, blue light in all directions.

Eight blue dragons shot out of the blue sun before pouncing at the mighty storm of fiery sword qi, keeping it at bay for just an instant.

Taking advantage of this tiny window of respite, Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan were able to rush their way to safety.

At this point, both of them were looking very disheveled. Their complexions were deathly pale, while their bodies were riddled with wounds, and they hurriedly took some pills to aid in their recovery.

Han Li took a glance at the two of them, then immediately turned his gaze back to the ancient sword and golden flame at the top of the altar with an intrigued look in his eyes.

The sword was a metal-attribute immortal treasure, while the golden flame contained time law powers, yet these two types of law powers were able to combine to produce power far greater than the sum of their individual parts.

Prior to developing lightning law powers, Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were also able to be used in conjunction with his time law powers, but following their attainment of lightning law powers, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had evolved into immortal treasures that rejected his time law powers.

If his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords could also be used in conjunction with time law powers, then that would undoubtedly make for a very formidable combination.

Excited by this prospect, Han Li made a beckoning motion to recover his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords back up his sleeve, then began flying toward the altar, relying on his Mantra Treasured Axis and Time Severing Fire Domain to keep him safe.

However, right at this moment, the black wind blowing out of the rift above the altar abruptly intensified significantly, sending gusts of yin wind sweeping through the entire cave, scattering even the fiery sword qi around the altar.

A chorus of ghastly howls rang out as Han Li instantly stopped cold in his tracks.

Right at this moment, the ancient sword and the golden flame on the altar lit up once again, as did the golden array around them, and the streaks of fiery sword qi that were hurtling toward Han Li and the others stopped in their tracks before converging toward the rift.

"It's too late to be focusing on us now!"

A burst of sinister cackling rang out from within the black rift, following which a thick bolt of black lightning erupted out from within, blasting a huge hole into the barrage of fiery sword qi up ahead before striking the golden flame.

While all of the fiery sword qi was directed toward the black rift, a cloud of barely visible golden mist pounced on the opportunity to drift toward the altar at an incredible speed, timing its approaching to perfection.

Everyone's attention was focused on the black rift and the two items on the altar, so no one noticed the faint cloud of golden mist.

The bolt of black lightning struck the golden flame at the top of the altar with a resounding boom, producing a massive explosion of black and golden light that caused the nearby space to warp and buzz incessantly.

The golden flame flickered a few times, following which its connection with the yin yang symbol beneath it was severed, and it was sent flying through the air, coincidentally directly toward Han Li.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up as he hurriedly made a hand seal, and several time law threads flew out of his Time Severing Torch before wrapping themselves around the golden flame and pulling it toward him.

To his surprise, the golden flame was easily pulled to his side without any resistance.

At this point, the cloud of thin golden mist had also reached the top of the altar, and it abruptly transformed into Xiong Shan.

At this moment, Xiong Shan was in an absolutely horrific physical condition. His body was riddled with countless wounds, and his legs and left arm were nowhere to be seen, leaving only a severely ravaged right arm behind.

Strangely enough, none of these wounds shed even a single drop of blood.

The ancient sword was currently still releasing streaks of sword qi, and what remained of Xiong Shan's body was instantly punched full of holes, almost tearing him apart entirely.

Despite this, Xiong Shan seemed to be completely unaware of his own grievous condition a he continued to stare at the ancient sword with a look of obsessive infatuation in his eyes, and he reached out with his only remaining hand to grab onto the hilt of the sword before tugging it upward.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

That bolt of black lightning from earlier had been extremely formidable, yet it was only just barely able to knock the golden flame down from the altar. Given Xiong Shan's current condition, it was extremely unlikely that he would be able to pull the ancient sword out of the altar.

However, things did not unfold as Han Li anticipated.

Chapter 1088: Claiming the Sword

Contrary to everyone's expectations, the ancient sword was easily pulled out of the altar by Xiong Shan, who swayed unsteadily for a moment before steadying him, following which he looked down at the golden sword in his hand with a slightly demented smile on his face.

With both the ancient sword and the golden flame gone from the altar, the golden array instantly dimmed, and all of the fiery sword qi in the surrounding area faded away as well.

Right at this moment, Fox 3, Wyrm 3, and Lei Yuce's trio were all revealed.

The white light barrier around Fox 3 and Wyrm 3 was nowhere to be seen, clearly having already been destroyed, and the two of them were currently enshrouded under a dark red wheel.

Their clothes were in tatters and stained with blood, giving them a very sorry and disheveled appearance.

In contrast, Lei Yuce's trio appeared to be faring much better. The golden array around them was still intact, but less than half of the golden sword projection inside still remained.

Lei Yuce and Wen Zhong were both looking deathly pale, clearly having severely overexerted themselves.

Their faces paled even further at the sight of the golden flame in Han Li's hand and the ancient sword that had been pulled out by Xiong Shan, but before they had a chance to say anything, a faint crack suddenly rang out from within the golden altar, as if something had just shattered.

A sense of foreboding immediately welled up in Han Li's heart upon hearing this sound.

All of a sudden, a chorus of elated cheers rang out from within the altar, followed by an eruption of blinding, black light, and the entire cave began to quiver and rumble violently.

The golden altar also began to tremble violently, and several more black rifts appeared around it in rapid succession.

"Fellow Daoist Han, Fellow Daoist Xiong, place those things back on the altar! Hurry!" Lei Yuce yelled with a horrified expression, and a hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

Meanwhile, Xiong Shan was holding the ancient sword tightly to himself, and he completely ignored Lei Yuce as he flipped a hand over to produce a crimson pill, which he promptly devoured.

After a brief moment of internal conflict, Han Li made up his mind, gritting his teeth as he prepared to return the golden flame to its original spot, but right at this moment, an earth-shattering boom rang out as the golden altar exploded into countless pieces.

Standing at the top of the altar, Xiong Shan was instantly sent flying by the explosion, and he just so happened to be flung directly toward Han Li.

He was in such terrible condition that he didn't even seem to be capable of flight, so he was unable to control his own body as the shockwaves sent him flying through the air, but his right hand remained firmly clutched onto the golden sword as if it were even more important than his own life.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light upon seeing this, catching Xiong Shan to prevent him from crashing into the cave wall behind him.

"Thank you, Brother Han," Xiong Shan said, but there wasn't any gratitude in his expression.

Instead, he was looking at Han Li with a very wary expression, as if he were afraid that Han Li would try to take his sword from him.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he couldn't help but feel as if Xiong Shan's sanity were currently a little compromised. However, he didn't say anything as he turned his gaze to where the altar once stood.

A door of black light had appeared from the wreckage of the altar, and large bursts of black light were surging out from within.

The door of light flashed erratically for a brief moment before abruptly shattering, and in the blink of an eye, over a hundred figures appeared in the cave, all of whom were yelling in excitement and exultation.

"Finally! I'm free!"

"How long has it been? I can barely recall a time when I wasn't trapped in this godforsaken place!"

"Where is Tai Sui? I'm going to skin him alive!"

Most of these figures were humanoid in form, while some were half-human, half-beast, and some of them were entirely beastly in appearance. All of them had devilish qi swirling around them, indicating that they were all devilish beings.

Han Li withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis and Time Severing Fire Domain as he drifted back in retreat until his back was against the cave wall behind him so that there was no way for him to be surrounded.

Most of these devilish beings were at the High Zenith Stage, and in particular, several of them possessed tremendous auras that weren't inferior to his own.

Xiong Shan had also recovered somewhat at this point, and he hurriedly flew back in retreat as well, situating himself near Han Li.

At this moment, there was a layer of crimson light glowing over his body, and countless fibers of flesh were sprouting from his wounds before intertwining with one another to rapidly heal his injuries and regenerate his lost limbs.

Before long, his body was back to normal, but his complexion was still deathly pale.

At this point, Lei Yuce and the others had also drifted back in retreat. Lei Yuce's trio was standing together, while Fox 3 and Wyrm 3 had been joined by the Lan siblings, all of whom were glowering at Han Li and Xiong Shan for putting them in this situation.

After taking a moment to revel in their excitement, all of the devilish beings turned to Han Li and the others with sinister grins on their faces.

A particularly muscular and imposing man emerged from the ranks of the devilish beings, then asked, "Were you the ones who opened the seal?"

The man had bronze skin over his incredibly well developed muscles, as well as a majestic lion's mane around his head, giving him the appearance of an almighty feline deity.

"That's right. We are from the Golden Origin Immortal Region, and we stumbled upon this place by chance. Who are all of you, and why are you here?" Han Li asked.

"I really must thank you for freeing all of us. As compensation, I'm going to allow all of you to become our food! Hand over your blood and souls!" the maned devilish man cackled as a cruel smile appeared on his face.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he launched himself at Han Li with incredible speed and power before swinging his giant fists down upon Han Li.

The man seemed to be very familiar with fighting human cultivators, and he knew that the right strategy to adopt was to use his superior physical properties to crush the enemy. Here in this confined space, his physical attacks were going to be faster and more effective than any immortal treasure or secret technique.

Unfortunately, he was gravely mistaken on this occasion. In the face of his sudden attack, Han Li abruptly vanished from the spot, then reappeared several hundred feet away.

The man immediately stopped in his tracks with a surprised expression upon seeing this, and right at this moment, a streak of golden sword light that was five hundred to six hundred feet in length came crashing down from the heavens amid a rumbling thunderclap.

The streak of golden swordlight left a uniform spatial rift in its wake, and its fearsome sword intent instantly filled the entire cave.

The devilish man's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he made a grabbing motion with his right hand to summon a huge, black hammer.

With a swing of his arm, the hammer was sent flying toward the streak of golden swordlight as a ball of black light.

This hammer was far more powerful than the average devilish treasure. During his travels in the devilish realm, he had stumbled upon a mountain formed by Profound Infernal Iron by chance, and he had gone to great lengths to transport the mountain into an underground fire vein.

Using the power of the underground fire vein, he refined the mountain over the course of a hundred thousand years, at which point he had finally eradicated all of the impurities in the mountain to convert it into a chunk of pure Profound Infernal Divine Iron.

After that, he gathered hundreds of types of premium metal-attribute ore, which he infused into the Profound Infernal Divine Iron, then forged it using a devilish secret technique for tens of thousands of years to produce this Profound Infernal Divine Hammer.

The hammer didn't look very remarkable, but it was so incredibly heavy that even the average High Zenith cultivator wouldn't be able to lift it.

The devilish man possessed incredible strength, allowing him to hurl the hammer through the air like a flying juggernaut.

The streak of swordlight collided with the black hammer, and the latter was instantly sliced into two with an extremely smooth cross-section.

After slicing through the hammer, the golden swordlight continued to descend upon the devilish man's whose expression changed drastically as he opened his mouth to release a black bead.

The black bead immediately exploded upon flying out of his mouth, forming a ball of black light that was over a hundred feet in size around him.

The streak of golden swordlight crashed down onto the ball of black light like a bolt of lightning, and once again, the ball of black light was torn apart with ease.

The two halves of the ball of black light were instantly eradicated by the sword intent erupting out of the golden swordlight, but the devilish man was nowhere to be seen.

The streak of golden swordlight then faded away to reveal Xiong Shan, and he was still holding firmly onto the ancient sword in his hand.

His complexion hadn't improved much, but there was a look of excitement and elation on his face as he stared at the ancient sword in his hand with a fervent expression.

It was as if the sword had become the center of his universe, something that he would gladly lady down his own life for.

The devilish man reappeared over ten thousand feet away amid a flash of black light, and his complexion was a little pale as he looked down at the destroyed black hammer in his hand with a lamenting look in his eyes.

The Profound Infernal Divine Hammer was no longer usable, but thankfully, its materials hadn't been destroyed, so he could forge it again, but he had no idea how long that was going to take.

"That's the Primordial Ancient Sword!" the devilish man exclaimed in a wary voice upon catching sight of the ancient sword in Xiong Shan's hand.

After destroying the Profound Infernal Divine Hammer so easily, Xiong Shan's appraisal of the ancient sword had been elevated even further, and his eyes were glowing with excitement as he roared, "We are the ones who freed you, yet you've immediately turned to bite the hand that fed you! You're going to pay for your ingratitude!"

The Primordial Ancient Sword released a burst of bright swordlight that encompassed his entire body once again as he spoke.

Immediately thereafter, both Xiong Shan and the Primordial Ancient Sword vanished in unison amid a flash of golden light, transforming into a streak of golden swordlight that was over a thousand feet in length that hurtled directly toward the devilish man with unstoppable might.

Chapter 1089: Unexpected

The devilish man seemed to have been enraged by Xiong Shan's arrogant attitude, and he summoned a long, black saber as he scoffed, "What insolence! You're nothing more than a mere Golden Immortal! You're a million years too early to claim yourself as my equal!"

A sinister-looking skull was engraved onto the hilt of the saber, and its blade was long and slender, with lightning-shaped patterns running along its entire length. Arcs of black lightning were dancing over its surface, and it was giving off an even more formidable aura than the Profound Infernal Divine Hammer.

With a vicious swing of the saber, a vast expanse of black qi was released, forming a black cloud that surged toward the streak of golden swordlight.

At the same time, close to a hundred lightning-shaped, translucent black threads shot out from within before converging toward a single spot to conjure up a black lightning lion the size of a house, and it pounced at the streak of golden sword light with incredibly violent lightning law power fluctuations surging out of its body.

In the face of this fearsome assailant, the swordlight formed by Xiong Shan didn't display any timidity. Instead, it sped up even further, and it seemed that he had supreme confidence in the Primordial Ancient Sword.

In the next instant, the streak of swordlight collided with the lightning lion, resulting in a violent explosion of black and golden light that caused the entire cave to tremble violently.

However, all of the walls of the cave were bolstered by restrictions, so even though many cracks had appeared over them, the cave didn't collapse.

A loud tearing sound rang out as the black lightning lion was sliced into two, reverting back into black lightning threads that erupted in all directions.

The devilish man shuddered violently as he stumbled back several steps before finally steadying himself with an incredulous look on his face.

The streak of golden swordlight had also been eradicated, and Xiong Shan stumbled out into the open, looking even paler than before, but his eyes were still filled with fervent excitement.

The devilish man was at the late-High Zenith Stage, while Xiong Shan was only a late-Golden Immortal cultivator, yet thanks to the Primordial Ancient Sword, he was able to gain a consistent upper hand over his opponent in their clashes.

Judging from the law power fluctuations emanating from the Primordial Ancient Sword, Han Li had determined that it was a fourth tier immortal treasure, but in light of this incredible display of power, it appeared that it was most likely actually a third tier immortal treasure.

With that in mind, Han Li couldn't help but feel a little envious of Xiong Shan, and he wondered when he was going to be able to secure such a powerful immortal treasure that perfectly complemented his law powers.

Meanwhile, all of the other devilish beings had also sprung into action.

Devilish cultivators had always harbored intense animosity toward cultivators of the Immortal Realm, particularly human cultivators, and after being trapped here by Immortal Lord Tai Sui for so many years, their hearts were filled with boundless resentment and vindictive fury.

However, not all of the devilish beings decided to attack Han Li and the others. Instead, only around half of them did so, while the other half was more interested in leaving the Eon Pagoda right away, and they flew straight out of the cave as streaks of black light.

Han Li paid no heed to the fleeing devilish beings as there were currently around seven or eight devilish cultivators rushing at him at once.

A cold gleam flashed through his eyes as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

The thirty-six flying swords transformed into hundreds of streaks of golden swordlight, all of which were flashing with golden lightning as they rained down upon Han Li's devilish assailants.

All of the devilish cultivators were using yin-attribute cultivators, so the lightning law powers of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords served as a natural bane to them, and they hurriedly began to adopt defensive measures against the oncoming barrage of golden swordlight.

While their attention was focused on the storm of golden swordlight, Han Li made a hand seal to summon his Mantra Treasured Axis, which released waves of golden ripples that instantly swept over a distance of several thousand feet.

His devilish assailants were completely caught off guard by this, and as soon as the golden ripples washed over them, they were instantly rooted to the spot.

In the next instant, the storm of golden swordlight passed through them, following which Han Li withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis, and the bodies of the devilish cultivators instantly exploded into pieces, while their nascent souls had also been eradicated.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and before the devilish beings even had a chance to react, they were confronted by the reality that seven or eight of their High Zenith Stage brethren had just been slain in the blink of an eye.

This naturally caused quite a stir among the other devilish beings, all of whom turned to look at Han Li with wary expressions, while Lei Yuce and the others were once again stunned by Han Li's power.

Han Li paid no heed to everyone's scrutiny as he vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden lightning, then reappeared over ten thousand feet away.

From there, he summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis once again, and it released waves of golden ripples that instantly encompassed a group of close to ten devilish beings nearby.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the hundreds of streaks of swordlight flew through the air once again, shredding the immobilized devilish beings into pieces.

At this point, the wariness in the eyes of the devilish beings had turned to fear, and all of them began to fly as far away from Han Li as possible.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he prepared to set off in pursuit of the fleeing devilish beings, but right at this moment, a string of thunderclaps rang out, following which a black lightning spirit domain appeared out of thin air before descending upon him.

The devilish man with the lion's mane was standing in the black spirit domain, observing Han Li with a cold expression.

Meanwhile, Xiong Shan was locked in battle against several other High Zenith Stage devilish beings.

In his excitement, he had unleashed too many powerful attacks in quick succession with his newly obtained Primordial Ancient Sword. As a result, his immortal spiritual power reserves quickly ran dry, so he was forced to resort to a more conservative style of battle and was no longer able to oppose the maned devilish cultivator.

Enshrouded within the black lightning spirit domain, the golden lightning around Han Li's body instantly melted away, and a surprised look appeared on his face upon seeing this.

Not only that, but the golden lightning surging over his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had also been suppressed.

"I don't care who you are, you're not leaving this place alive!" the devilish man roared with a furious expression as he swung his black saber down upon Han Li, releasing a hundred and fifty lightning law threads that intertwined to form an almighty, black lightning dragon.

The dragon was giving off a terrifying aura that was far more formidable than that of the black lightning lion from before, and it flew through the air as a bolt of black lightning, instantly reaching Han Li before grabbing down viciously at him with a giant claw.

A vast shadow instantly appeared over Han Li, and it was as if the entire sky were about to collapse under the weight of the lightning dragon's almighty claw.

The devilish man seemed to have used some type of acceleratory ability similar to the Reversal True Axis to complete that sequence of movements at an incredible speed, and Han Li had only just noticed the black lightning spirit domain around him when the dragon claw was already upon him.

All he had time to do was throw a punch in retaliation, unleashing a golden fist projection that hurtled directly toward the oncoming draconic claw.

The fist projection was imbued with tremendous power that crushed the space in its wake, resulting in the emergence of countless spatial rifts.

All of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords around him also shot forth through the air behind the fist projection, forming an azure sword lotus flower that was around an acre in size, with countless sword projections swirling around within it.

The lightning dragon let loose a thunderous, draconic roar, and its claw clashed violently against the golden fist projection, tearing through it with ease.

The draconic claw continued downward without pause, grabbing onto the azure sword lotus flower.

Even though the lightning law powers of Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were being suppressed by the devilish man's spirit domain, the swords themselves were still extremely formidable, and the sword lotus flower formed by thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords was far more powerful than the golden fist projection.

The black, draconic claw struck the sword lotus flower with an earth-shattering boom, and the latter was able to hold its own briefly before exploding into thirty-six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords that scattered in all directions.

As a result, the black dragon was momentarily stopped in its tracks before continuing to descend upon Han Li, and that split-second delay was all Han Li needed to summon his time spirit domain, which expanded rapidly in all directions, encompassing the lightning dragon within it in the blink of an eye.

At the same time, his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him, then released waves of golden ripples that encompassed the lightning dragon as well.

Immediately thereafter, the Time Severing Torch emerged beside the Mantra Treasured Axis before releasing its Time Severing Fire Domain, which also enshrouded the lightning dragon.

With Han Li's time spirit domain, Mantra Treasured Axis, and Time Severing Fire Domain acting upon it at once, the lightning dragon was instantly immobilized, despite its almighty power.

Chapter 1090: Retreat

The devilish man was astonished to see this.

He had gauged Han Li to be a very formidable opponent, and his time-attribute law abilities were particularly troublesome to deal with. Hence, he had gone all-out from the get-go, using his spirit domain to suppress Han Li's power before using a secret technique that forcibly elevated his speed at the expense of law threads, and finally, he had unleashed an all-out attack with all of the remaining law threads in his body.

He had thought that even if he couldn't kill Han Li, he would at least be able to severely wound him, but things had not gone according to plan at all.

The devilish man had a very violent and ruthless personality to begin with, and these personality traits had been even further exacerbated during all this time that he had been trapped here. Hence, after being freed, he was eager to exact vengeance on any Immortal Realm cultivators that he encountered.

However, even his most powerful attack had failed to defeat Han Li, and his rational thinking began to win out over the vengeful fury in his heart, telling him that the best course of action was perhaps to flee.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief after containing the black lightning dragon, but at the same time, he was reprimanding himself for being too complacent. If he had unleashed his time spirit domain from the get-go, then he definitely wouldn't have fallen into such a perilous situation.

At the same time, he flipped a hand over to produce the Profound Heavenly Gourd, but before he had a chance to do anything, the golden flame from the altar suddenly began to glow radiantly beside him.

In the wake of the recent sequence of events, he had forgotten all about the golden flame.

At this moment, the golden flame seemed to be resonating with the time spirit domain around it, and it swelled to several times its original size. On top of that, it seemed to be completely unaffected by the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Time Severing Fire Domain.

A burst of formidable time law power fluctuations erupted out of the golden flame, causing the surrounding time spirit domain to shudder violently.

Han Li turned to the golden flame with a surprised expression, then swept a sleeve through the air to release two streams of incantation seals, which surged into the golden flame and his Profound Heavenly Gourd.

Some of Han Li's time law threads were still inside the golden flame, and they instantly lit up before directing the flame toward the lightning dragon, sending it flying through the air as a golden shadow.

At the same time, a burst of green light erupted out of the Profound Heavenly Gourd before also sweeping toward the lightning dragon.

The green light released by the Profound Heavenly Gourd was faster than the golden flame, and it wrapped itself around the lightning dragon before tugging forcefully downward.

The lightning dragon shuddered violently before slowly slumping down in a limp fashion.

However, the lightning dragon was formed by over a hundred of the devilish man's law threads, so the volume of law power that it contained was too tremendous for even the Profound Heavenly Gourd to be able to capture it in a short time.

Right at this moment, the golden flame also struck the black lightning dragon, and the latter instantly began to rapidly wither away upon contact.

Its body was split into two in the blink of an eye, much to Han Li's elation and the devilish man's shock and horror.

However, in the next instant, the golden flame suddenly began to flash erratically. The time law power within it was churning violently, destabilizing the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Time Severing Fire Domain to loosen their hold on the lightning dragon.

The devilish man's eyes lit up upon seeing this, and he fell to his haunches, then transformed into a giant lion devil beast that was several hundred feet in size.

The lion's entire body had a bronze coloration, as if it had been forged from copper, and its skin was riddled with black lightning patterns. Furthermore, it had a pair of curved, black horns on the top of its head with arcs of black lightning flashing over them.

All of a sudden, the lightning surging over the lion's horns brightened significantly until they resembled a pair of miniature, black suns.

The two halves of the lightning dragon's body instantly shrank down rapidly into a pair of black lightning rings, one larger than the other.

The two lightning rings were giving off incredibly fearsome lightning law powers that weren't necessarily more formidable than those of the lightning dragon, but were far more condensed and focused. On top of that, these law powers were also sharper, allowing the two lightning rings to struggle free from the green light while also somewhat forcing back the surrounding Mantra Treasured Axis and Time Severing Fire Domain.

In the blink of an eye, the two lightning rings had flown out of the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Time Severing Fire Domain, but Han Li certainly wasn't going to allow them to get away so easily, and he immediately opened his mouth to release two streaks of light, one azure and one golden.

The streaks of azure light vanished into the Profound Heavenly Gourd, causing it to light up while releasing numerous translucent, green threads.

These glowing, green threads shot forth through the air at an incredible speed, instantly catching up to the pair of black lightning rings to ensnare them once again.

There were as many as three or four dozen of these green threads, and as soon as they wrapped themselves around the lightning rings, the latter were instantly stopped in their tracks.

Meanwhile, the streak of golden light flew over to the golden flame, and it contained close to thirty time law threads, all of which intertwined to form a large, golden net that encompassed the golden flame within it.

The unstable time law power fluctuations surging out of the golden flame were instantly contained, restoring stability to the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Time Severing Fire Domain.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li made a rapid string of hand seals, and the golden ripples released by the Mantra Treasured Axis instantly began to expand outward, rapidly spreading toward the pair of black lightning rings.

An alarmed look appeared in the eyes of the lion devil beast upon seeing this, and it let loose a thunderous roar as all of the black lightning patterns on its body lit up, following which all of the light converged toward the pair of horns on its head.

The horns instantly took on a translucent appearance, and the lightning flashing over them brightened even further, to the point that they were virtually impossible to directly behold.

The larger one of the two black lightning rings lit up and struggled free from the threads of green light before vanishing into the lion devil beast's mouth in a flash.

The smaller lightning ring was also struggling with all its might, but it didn't seem to possess enough power to free itself from the green threads, and as soon as the golden ripples emanating from the Mantra Treasured Axis washed over it, it was instantly rooted to the spot.

Immediately thereafter, the threads of green light dragged the lightning into the Profound Heavenly Gourd.

The lion devil beast was so furious to see this that a deranged look had appeared in its eyes, and it let loose an almighty roar that shook the entire cave.

A cold sneer appeared on Han Li's face as he rushed toward the lion devil beast as a golden shadow, and his time spirit domain also expanded toward his opponent.

At this point, the devilish lion was already aware that it had bitten off far more than it could chew, and it immediately fled the scene as an arc of black lightning, leaving behind only a furious roar of: "You'll pay for this!"

The morale of all of the other devilish beings in the cave completely collapsed upon seeing this, and all of them immediately fled for their lives as well.

Han Li chose not to give chase as he withdrew his time spirit domain and time-attribute law treasures.

With the time spirit domain gone, the golden flame also reverted back to its original state.

However, it had shrunk down to only just over half its original size, and the time law powers within it had also diminished significantly, indicating that it had expended much of its power while attacking the black lightning dragon.

The golden flame had a similar effect to the innate ability of Fire Age Fireflies, but at a far higher level of potency.

However, it seemed that he would only be able to use it one more time at most, and that was quite a pity.

With that in mind, he heaved a forlorn, internal sigh, and the time law threads surrounding the golden flame formed a lotus-flower-shaped seal around it at his behest, following which he stowed the golden flower away up his sleeve.

Lei Yuce and the others didn't give chase, either. All of them were already carrying injuries, so they had constantly been on the back foot against their devilish assailants, and it would've been very foolish to go after them.

After all of the devilish beings fled the scene, everyone hurriedly descended onto the ground to rest and recuperate.

Han Li hadn't sustained any injuries, but he had expended a great deal of energy during the battle, so he also took some time to rest.

Close to two hours later, everyone rose to their feet one after another, and Lei Yuce turned to Han Li with mixed emotions on his face as he said, "It appears we must thank you once again, Fellow Daoist Han. If it wasn't for you, all of us would've most likely perished here."

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Lei. What was the deal with those devilish beings? It seemed like you knew something about them in advance," Han Li said in a meaningful voice, and everyone else also turned their attention to Lei Yuce upon hearing this.

However, instead of immediately answering Han Li's question, Lei Yuce flew over to the wreckage of the golden altar, where the door of black light was already nowhere to be seen.

After sweeping a sleeve through the air to scatter some of the rubble on the ground, a circular, golden stone slab was revealed with a complex array engraved upon it, and eight golden stone pillars were standing on the corners of the array.

Not only were there several cracks on the array, many sections of it had been damaged, and the entire array had become dull and completely devoid of luster.

A grim look instantly appeared on Lei Yuce's face upon seeing this, and he turned to Xiong Shan as he reprimanded, "Fellow Daoist Xiong, this is all because of your reckless actions!"

"My apologies, I didn't know that pulling out the sword would free so many devilish beings. I'll make sure to be more careful from now on," Xiong Shan replied.

Despite his apology, he wasn't looking apologetic at all. Instead, his eyes were filled with unbridled joy as he stole occasional glances at the Primordial Ancient Sword in his hand.

At this moment, there were twenty to thirty golden law threads circling around the sword, and it seemed that he was in the process of refining the sword.

Lan Yuanzi and the others couldn't help but gaze upon the Primordial Ancient Sword with envious looks in their eyes, and Lei Yuce's brows furrowed slightly at Xiong Shan's insincere apology, but he didn't say anything further.

Xiong Shan was previously the weakest member of the group, but with this Primordial Ancient Sword in his possession, no one else in the group aside from Han Li could say with any degree of certainty that they would be able to defeat him.

Chapter 1091: Sealed Devilish Beings

"At this point, it's only right that all of you know the truth. I do indeed know a little about this seventh level of the Eon Pagoda. As all of you are already aware, this pagoda is a prison in which many fugitives are being held captive, and the fugitive on this seventh level is an almighty devil, one that's far more powerful than all of the other fugitives we've encountered so far," Lei Yuce explained.

"There were even Great Encompassment Stage beings among the fugitives that we've already encountered, could it be that this one is a Dao Ancestor?" Lan Yan scoffed, clearly skeptical of Lei Yuce's words.

"The founding father of our Almighty Sword Sect participated in the sealing of this devil, and according to the records left behind by him, even if that devil isn't a Dao Ancestor, he's not far away," Lei Yuce replied with a grim expression, and Lan Yan's flippant smile slowly faded upon hearing this.

"The founding father of the Almighty Sword Sect once came to this place as well? Could it be that he was familiar with Immortal Lord Tai Sui?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid I don't know the answer to that question," Lei Yuce replied with a shake of his head.

Han Li didn't say anything, but internally, he was feeling a little skeptical, and he couldn't tell if Lei Yuce actually didn't know, or if he was simply withholding this information.

"Could it be that the devilish being that you're referring to is the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity, the one who was said to have used the entire Golden Origin Immortal Region as a blood sacrifice?" Su Anqian suddenly asked.

"That's right. I'm sure you must be well aware of his existence, Celestial Maiden Su," Lei Yuce confirmed.

"Our Heavenly Water Sect has records of that catastrophic calamity," Su Anqian replied as her complexion paled slightly.

"Would you care to elaborate?" Han Li asked.

"Many of you aren't from the Golden Origin Immortal Region, so you won't be aware of this event. Countless years ago, going all the way back to the era where our Immortal Realm was in direct conflict with the Devil Realm, our Golden Origin Immortal Region once endured a major catastrophe.

“An almighty devilish being by the name of the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity descended upon the Golden Origin Immortal Region and created a vast devilish array to slaughter the entire immortal region. Over half of all of the living beings in the Golden Origin Immortal Region at the time perished to that array, and it was only broken by a Dao Ancestor from the Heavenly Court.

“To this very day, the Golden Origin Immortal Region is still yet to recover from that ordeal, and even the mere mention of the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's name is considered to be taboo," Su Anqian sighed.

"I see," Han Li mused as a contemplative look appeared in his eyes, and he couldn't help but wonder if this Dark Heavens Devilish Deity had anything to do with the Night Sun Empire.

"Truth be told, the emergence of the Tai Sui Immortal Manor wasn't a coincidence. According to the records of our sect, the immortal manor most likely emerged as a result of the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity's attempts to break the seal that he's confined within, and Wen Zhong and I have come here with the objective of fortifying the seal.

“The seal has a total of five cores, each corresponding to one of the five elements, and that golden altar was the metal-attribute core," Lei Yuce added.

"Does that mean that one of the cores of the seal has already been destroyed?" Lan Yan asked in an uneasy manner, and grim looks immediately appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this.

"That's right. As long as the five cores are intact, there's no way for the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity to escape, but now that one of them has been destroyed, if the other cores are destroyed as well, then there's a very good chance that the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity will be able to break free from his seal.

“If that happens, not only will all of us lose our lives here, the entire Golden Origin Immortal Region will be subjected to another disastrous calamity, so make sure to proceed with caution from here onward and do not destroy any more cores," Lei Yuce said with a solemn expression, and everyone nodded in response.

"What do we do now? Do we keep going?" Lan Yan asked.

"Yes, but before we leave, I'm going to attempt to repair this array. This array is the foundation of the metal-attribute core, and even though it's been destroyed, the energy within it still hasn't completely dissipated, so if I can repair it, perhaps it can still function partially as intended," Lei Yuce replied, then crouched down to examine the array on the ground.

Wen Zhong also stepped up to help him, and after a brief discussion, the two of them quickly began working on the array.

Han Li and the others weren't familiar with the array, so they couldn't offer any help.

Close to a day passed by in a flash, and Han Li and the others were all in a state of seated meditation when they felt a burst of formidable array fluctuations sweep through the air, prompting them to rise to their feet.

The golden array on the ground had already been repaired, and a thick pillar of golden light rose up from it before vanishing into the ceiling of the cave above.

The array then slowly ceased operating at Lei Yuce's behest, and the pillar of golden light quickly faded away.

"Thankfully, the damage wasn't too severe, and we were able to repair the array," Lei Yuce declared with a faint smile.

"Will it still be able to serve its original purpose?" Lan Yan asked, seemingly quite fearful of the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity.

"I'm not sure, we can only hope so," Lei Yuce replied. "Let's get out of here, we've already been delayed here for far too long."

Lei Yuce swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, releasing a burst of golden light that swept up some nearby rocks before piling them onto the golden array.

At this point, everyone had already mostly recovered from their injuries, and they were eager to continue onward.

......

After walking through the cave for a long time, they finally arrived at its entrance.

Outside the cave was a platform that was several thousand feet in size, and there were jagged rocks all over the ground, as if this place were situated halfway up a mountain.

Upon arriving at the edge of the platform, everyone peered into the distance, but they were unable to see anything but dense, gray mist.

Xiong Shan peered into the distance for a while, then suddenly slashed his golden longsword through the air to release a massive streak of golden swordlight.

The streak of swordlight possessed tremendous power and should've been able to glide through the air for hundreds of kilometers, but to everyone's surprise, it was only able to travel several thousand feet before exploding violently, as if it had struck a wall.

"There's a restriction here," Xiong Shan murmured to himself.

"Save your energy, everyone. The restriction outside this mountain is connected to the foundation of the entire Eon Pagoda, so unless you possess the power to destroy the entire pagoda, you won't be able to break this restriction by force," Lei Yuce said.

Han Li released his spiritual sense to scour the surrounding area upon hearing this, only to discover that his spiritual sense was so severely restricted here that he wasn't able to release it very far at all.

Hence, everyone had no choice but to fly their way up the mountain.

After flying for close to ten thousand feet, Wyrm 3 suddenly stopped in her tracks, and everyone else immediately did the same.

They followed the direction of her gaze to discover what appeared to be a man-made stone staircase, leading up the mountain in a winding fashion, at the base of which was a flat cliff.

"Let's go take a look," Lei Yuce said, then flew over to the stone staircase, followed immediately by everyone else.

Upon descending onto the cliff, Han Li looked around to discover that there was nothing of note in the surrounding area aside from the stone staircase.

Thus, everyone began to scale the staircase, making their way up toward the mountain summit.

After advancing for several thousand feet, they arrived on an even larger cliff, standing upon which was an antiquated blue palace that had been constructed along the face of the mountain.

Ahead of the palace was a plaza that was several thousand feet in size, and its mirror-like surface resembled that of a lake, with what appeared to be a cloud of blue mist hanging over it, giving it a rather illusory appearance.

Lan Yuanzi's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the cloud of mist.

"What's wrong?" Lan Yan asked.

"I can sense some water law power fluctuations in the air... I think this is most likely a water-attribute illusory array," Lan Yuanzi mused.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he began to carefully examine the surrounding area with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Thanks to his Infernal Devilish Eyes, he was able to see a series of vortexes within the cloud of mist, exerting both forces of attraction and repulsion upon one another to form a very special energy field.

After peering into the mist for only a short while, Han Li felt his eyes begin to grow moist, as if water vapor were creeping into them, and he looked around in a perplexed manner, only to discover that Lei Yuce and the others were nowhere to be seen.

A wry smile appeared on his face upon seeing this. Only now did he realize that they had already stepped into the illusory array from the moment that they reached the top of the staircase.

After taking a moment to compose himself, he began channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique, attempting to use his tremendous spiritual sense to forcibly break the illusion.

However, as soon as he did this, the surrounding environment was instantly transformed.

The vortexes that he had spotted earlier suddenly began to revolve far faster and more violently than before, and they were crashing into one another like a cluster of tornadoes.

At the same time, the sound of loud, crashing waves rang out, and Han Li discovered that he had appeared above a vast, black sea.

Chapter 1092: The Second Altar

Standing in the air above the black sea, Han Li looked around to discover that the entire sky above was filled with dark clouds.

Gusts of ferocious wind were sweeping toward him from all directions, raising enormous waterspouts that also began to close in on him.

Han Li knew that this was nothing more than an illusion, but the sense of asphyxiation that he was feeling and the freezing sensation of the waves crashing into his body were so realistic that he couldn't help but be stunned.

Bursts of deafening rumbling rang out as several of the surrounding waterspouts collided, forming a giant waterspout that swallowed up Han Li.

As he tumbled up and down with the chaotic currents, bursts of tremendous force were crashing incessantly into his body, striking him with excruciating pain while also threatening to scatter his consciousness.

All of a sudden, a burst of golden lightning erupted out of Han Li's body in all directions amid a resounding thunderclap, instantly tearing the giant waterspout apart, following which he plummeted straight down into the seawater below.

To his surprise, the surrounding seawater didn't seem to have any buoyancy, and despite his attempts to resist, he was sucked down into its depths against his will.

There seemed to be bottom to this vast sea, nor were there living beings inside. Han Li was all on his own as he embarked on what felt like an endless descent...

Meanwhile, everyone else was in much the same situation as Han Li, except they were all experiencing different illusions.

For example, Wyrm 3 was currently trapped in a crimson river that was also devoid of all living beings, but there were countless shadows drifting through the water around her like clumps of errant water weeds.

As these shadows converged toward her, they clung to her body one after another, causing her to become heavier and heavier, thereby making her sink deeper and deeper into the river.

Lei Yuce and the others were also all rooted to the spot with twisted looks on their faces, clearly grappling with illusions of their own.

Right at this moment, a blue symbol lit up on both Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan's arms, and each symbol released a burst of blue light that joined together above their heads.

As soon as the two bursts of blue light came together, they instantly conjured up a blue light barrier that was giving off formidable water law power fluctuations, encompassing the two of them within it.

Immediately thereafter, the two of them each gave a muffled groan as they opened their eyes.

"That was a close call," Lan Yan said as she patted her own chest with a hint of lingering fear in her eyes.

"Thank heavens the Water Elemental Spirit Talismans that Master planted in us took effect here," Lan Yuanzi mused.

"It's also very fortunate that both of us entered that illusory array together, so the talismans were able to fuse with each other. Otherwise, the power of just a single talisman may not have been enough to awaken either one of us from that illusion," Lan Yan said.

"Alright, let's not waste any more time," Lan Yuanzi said as he cast his gaze toward the palace.

"What about them?" Lan Yan asked as she turned her gaze back to everyone else.

"We'll have to leave them to break the illusion on their own," Lan Yuanzi said.

With that, the two of them quickly traversed through the plaza under the protection of the light barrier to arrive at the palace.

Upon reaching the entrance of the palace, Lan Yuanzi inspected the gates momentarily to discover that there were no restrictions on it, and he gently pushed them open.

As soon as the gates were opened, a burst of potent water law power fluctuations immediately swept toward the two of them, making them feel as if they were basking in a warm spring breeze.

As they made their way into the palace, they spotted a blue altar that was identical in size and design to the golden altar that they had previously encountered.

There were two damaged areas on the altar, one on the left, and the other on the right, and hovering above it was a palm-sized, blue cloth pouch that looked as if it had been woven out of silk. Embroidered at the center of the pouch was a design of a wave that was giving off a faint sheen, and it was releasing extremely formidable water law power fluctuations.

Just like on the golden altar, there was also a golden flame hovering beside the blue pouch.

Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan exchanged a glance with each other, then began to make their way toward the altar, and as soon as they did so, a burst of loud rumbling instantly rang out.

Lan Yuanzi immediately grabbed onto Lan Yan's arm, and both of them stopped in their tracks to listen carefully for the source of the sound, upon which they discovered that it was coming from the blue pouch on the altar.

The sound resembled that of a turbulent river forcing its way through narrow floodgates, and the Lan siblings immediately exchanged an elated glance with each other upon hearing this.

"Wait here for a moment while I retrieve that pouch," Lan Yuanzi said with an excited smile.

"Wait! What if you end up releasing that devilish deity?" Lan Yan asked with a hesitant expression.

"Don't worry about that. Setting aside whether Lei Yuce was even telling the truth about that devilish deity, even if we do release it, there will be other people to deal with it. If worse comes to worst, we'll just have to immediately leave this place and return to the Nine Origins Temple after retrieving the pouch, and nothing that happens from there onward will have anything to do with us," Lan Yuanzi reassured.

Lan Yan was still clearly feeling rather concerned, but before she had a chance to say anything, Lan Yuanzi continued, "Think about it: we've already failed in our mission to capture Han Li, and we've soured our relationship with She Chan as well. If we don't return to the Nine Origins Temple with anything to show for our efforts, what do you think is going to await us?"

Lan Yan's expression changed slightly upon hearing this.

"Not only will we be punished, our master will most likely be held culpable as well. However, if we can return with this treasure, perhaps we'll be spared some punishment. At the very least, we should be able to keep our master from being swept up in our mess," Lan Yuanzi continued.

Lan Yan finally relented upon hearing this.

"In that case, we'll do as you say, but do be careful."

Lan Yuanzi smiled as he nodded in response, then began to make his way toward the altar.

However, he had only taken a couple of steps when he turned around to face Lan Yan, then said, "Once the pouch is freed from the restriction on the altar, it'll be sure to release extremely formidable law power fluctuations, so make sure to keep your distance from me and be on your guard."

"In that case, let's try and use our fusion secret technique. That way, even if something goes wrong and we're unable to secure the pouch, at the very least, we'll be able to ensure self-preservation," Lan Yan hurriedly said.

Lan Yuanzi's brows furrowed slightly in indecision upon hearing this.

After some contemplation, Lan Yuanzi decided, "That's a good idea. Truth be told, I'm not very confident in my ability to retrieve the pouch on my own."

Lan Yan was very happy to hear this, and she strode over to the altar by Lan Yuanzi's side.

After taking a moment to examine the altar, Lan Yuanzi swept a sleeve through the air to release numerous array flags and array plates before getting to work around the altar.

......

Inside the illusory array, Han Li and the others were still rooted to the spot with agonized looks on their faces, and not even a single one of them was able to break out of their illusions.

At this moment, Han Li was still sinking ever deeper into the black sea, unable to awaken despite his best efforts to channel his Spirit Refinement Technique.

Could it be that this illusion is built upon a foundation of water law powers rather than spiritual sense?

Even as this thought sprang into Han Li's mind, he still couldn't think of a way to free himself from the illusion.

It was if the black sea really was a bottomless abyss, one that he could sink eternally into without reaching the bottom.

Han Li felt as if he had fallen into a plane where space and time didn't exist, and that he would continue to sink with no end in sight unless he could break the illusion.

......

Around fifteen minutes later.

A circular array had taken shape around the blue altar in the palace.

Lan Yuanzi examined the array momentarily, then gave Lan Yan a nod, and the latter immediately summoned a blue oil paper umbrella.

There was a scenic image of a pond filled with colorful koi fish drawn onto the surface of the umbrella, and it was an extremely vivid and life-like image.

With a gentle twirl of the umbrella, it began to revolve in mid-air, and the pond on the umbrella seemed to have also been stirred up, with ripples running over its surface, but the koi fish within remained stationary and unaffected.

The umbrella drifted higher up into the air at Lan Yan's behest, hovering above the altar like a floating dome.

"Let's begin," Lan Yuanzi declared, and both of them began making hand seals in unison.

A blue light barrier emerged from each of their bodies, forming a two-layered spirit domain that encompassed both themselves and the altar.

After that, they began chanting an incantation, and the array flags around the altar began to unfurl while releasing bursts of formidable water law power fluctuations.

At the same time, the array plates on the ground also lit up, releasing pillars of blue light that rose up to surround the entire altar.

Chapter 1093: Too Late

With the array activated, the blue oil paper umbrella above the altar began to accelerate in its revolution, and the pond on its surface began to sway violently as if it were enduring a fierce storm.

It was as if water were threatening to splash out of the edges of the umbrella, and the dozen or so koi fish in the pond also began to move over the surface of the umbrella, leaving golden trails in their wake.

At the same time, the entire altar began to tremble violently. The golden flame above it didn't display much of a reaction, but the blue pouch was bulging erratically while the rumbling within it grew louder and louder, to the point it resembled a thunderstorm raging directly beside one's ears.

Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan exchanged a tense look upon seeing this, but before they had a chance to do anything else, a resounding boom rang out as eighteen water dragons erupted out of the blue pouch before pouncing at the two of them.

Each water dragon was over a hundred feet in length, and their bodies looked as if they had been carved out of crystal, giving off incredibly formidable water law power fluctuations.

"Brace yourself!" Lan Yuanzi warned as the eighteen water dragons crashed into the array that they had set up.

A string of resounding booms rang out in rapid succession as countless arcs of blue water lightning erupted out of the eighteen water dragons' bodies, encompassing the entire altar with blue lightning.

Lan Yan's complexion paled slightly as she sensed the awe-inspiring power imbued within the water lightning, and she hurriedly composed herself before continuing to make a string of hand seals, assisting Lan Yuanzi by injecting her immortal spiritual power into the oil paper umbrella up above.

All of a sudden, the oil paper umbrella swelled to several times its original size, and the pond on its surface began to churn violently, while the koi fish leaped out of the water over and over again, leaving golden trails on the umbrella in their wake.

At the same time, a series of runes lit up over the umbrella's shaft, following which numerous black vortexes emerged, releasing bursts of suction force that began sucking in the blue lightning raging down below in a frenzy.

The eighteen water dragons were still violently wreaking havoc, while the water lightning that they released was being rapidly absorbed by the oil paper umbrella.

At this point, the entire pond on the umbrella was churning so violently that it looked as if it had been brought to a boil, and the koi fish inside were frantically flopping up and down, while arcs of lightning flashed over their scales.

As the oil paper umbrella continued to absorb the water lightning, it seemed that an impasse had been reached. The amount of water lightning around the altar wasn't increasing any further, but it remained as powerful as ever.

"Looks like this is the best that we can do. If we keep this up, the umbrella is most likely going to give out soon, so we have to take a risk now!" Lan Yuanzi said with a grim expression, and Lan Yan nodded in response.

The two of them sat down with their legs crossed, then closed their eyes as each of them made a strange hand seal, and bursts of formidable water law power fluctuations began to surge out of their bodies.

At the same time, numerous thin threads began to emerge over the two surrounding spirit domain light barriers, and the threads intertwined before tugging on one another to fuse the two light barriers together.

Immediately thereafter, a nascent soul emerged from the glabellas of both Lan Yuanzi and lan Yan, and they drifted toward each other before also fusing together.

The fused nascent soul swelled rapidly in size until it was comparable in size to the average adult human, and it had a set of rather gender-ambiguous facial features.

Immediately thereafter, bursts of formidable water law power fluctuations surged out of the combined spirit domain, encasing the fused nascent soul in a suit of strange-looking blue water armor.

The fused nascent soul's aura instantly swelled drastically, enhanced by the suit of water armor, and it took a glance at the physical bodies of the Lan siblings, who were still seated at their original spots, before flying over to the edge of the altar.

The fused nascent soul reached its hands into the barrier of lightning up ahead before bringing them apart, and the layer of water lightning directly up ahead was parted to create an opening, which the nascent soul was able to burrow its way into.

As soon as the fused nascent soul entered the altar, it was immediately attacked by the eighteen water dragons, and in response, the nascent soul made a strange hand seal, then thrust both hands toward the oncoming water dragons, conjuring up a circular water shield to ward off their attacks.

A burst of thunderous rumbling rang out as the eighteen water dragons crashed into the shield, sending bursts of blue water lighting erupting in all directions.

Countless arcs of violent water lightning struck the nascent soul, and even though they were kept out by the suit of water armor, the nascent soul's features still became twisted with agony.

Despite this, the fused nascent soul continued to inch its way toward the altar, displaying no intention of backing down.

As the rumbling grew louder and louder, the water lightning became more powerful, and the fused nascent soul's suit of water armor was beginning to evaporate.

At the same time, large plumes of water vapor began to surge out of the oil paper umbrella above, and the pond on its surface was becoming noticeably shallower, while seven or eight of the koi fish in the pond had already dissipated.

Right on the verge of collapse, the fused nascent soul was able to step onto the altar before grabbing onto the blue pouch, then tore the pouch out of the altar.

As soon as the pouch was displaced, all of the eighteen water dragons instantly converged to form an orb of water that returned to the pouch, and the thunderous commotion immediately died down.

At this point, the pond on the oil paper umbrella above the altar had run completely dry, and not only had all of the koi fish vanished, the surface of the umbrella had also become withered and wrinkled, as if it had been scorched by flames.

As the final hint of spiritual light faded from the umbrella, it abruptly erupted into flames before being reduced to ashes in mere seconds.

After retreating from the altar, the fused nascent soul split back up into two nascent souls that flew back into the bodies of Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan.

Immediately thereafter, their eyes sprang open, and Lan Yan was currently holding the blue pouch as she cast an ecstatic gaze toward Lan Yuanzi.

The latter opened his mouth to say something, but before he had a chance to do so, the altar suddenly began to tremble violently as a series of massive cracks appeared over its surface, and the cracks were rapidly expanding.

Lan Yuanzi hurriedly rose to his feet before grabbing onto Lan Yan's hand, following which he flew out of the palace toward the plaza outside.

As he did so, he noticed that the layer of mist over the plaza was beginning to thin out bit by bit before completely fading away altogether, freeing everyone from their illusions.

Having been abruptly snapped out of the bottomless sea, Han Li gasped for air as he hurriedly swept his gaze over his surroundings, immediately spotting the violently quaking blue palace and the Lan siblings in the air above.

A perplexed look appeared on his face upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to ask any questions, a resounding boom rang out from within the palace.

Immediately thereafter, an enormous black rift emerged all the way from the palace to the plaza beneath his feet, tearing the entire cliff apart.

An alarmed look appeared on Lei Yuce's face as he attempted to fly into the palace to salvage the structure, but he had only just risen up into the air when the palace was completely split into two, with its two halves collapsing to either side.

Through the destroyed palace, Han Li could see a golden flame hovering above the altar inside, and it was flickering erratically, looking as if it could be snuffed out at any moment.

He immediately channeled his Great Five Elemental Illusion Mantra upon seeing this, using his time law powers as a guiding force as he made a beckoning motion toward the golden flame from afar.

The restriction on the altar had already been destroyed by the Lan siblings, so the golden flame was drawn to Han Li without posing any resistance.

In the wake of the golden flame's departure, the altar completely collapsed, and an enormous black hole appeared in its wake.

The shattered altar plummeted into the hole, but no sound of its landing could be heard.

"It's too late..." Lei Yuce murmured to himself with a grim expression.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a chorus of ghastly shrieks rang out from within the hole beneath the altar.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he detected the horde of formidable auras rising up from within the hole.

"Tai Sui, you old scoundrel! I have returned!"

A sharp voice that was filled with boundless resentment rang out from deep within the hole.

Chapter 1094: Warding Off the Enemy

Immediately thereafter, a giant devilish being that was around a hundred feet tall with white bone plates all over its body erupted out of the hole before hovering in the air above the palace.

The devilish being's entire body was as translucent as white jade, and it had no skin, flesh, or internal organs. As opposed to a human head, it had the skull of a goat, and there was a pair of white bone wings on its back, flapping incessantly to keep the creature aloft.

Han Li could sense that this creature's aura was no less formidable than that of the copper lion devilish beast, and his brows furrowed slightly at this observation.

"Were you the ones who freed me?" the devilish being asked as he swept his gaze over Han Li's group.

Han Li and the others didn't know what its intentions were, so they remained silent as they looked up at the creature with wary expressions.

All of a sudden, the devilish being's gaze settled upon the blue pouch in Lan Yan's hand, and it remarked, "If that pouch is in your possession, then you must've been the ones who broke the seal. I may be a devil, but even I know the importance of repaying kindnesses, so you can have these as a gesture of gratitude from me."

The devilish being swept a hand through the air as it spoke, releasing several fist-sized blue crystals that were giving off potent water law power fluctuations.

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon seeing this, clearly taken aback by this turn of events.

"So you won't answer my questions, nor will you accept my gifts. Honestly, you're beginning to hurt my feelings," the devilish being said in a cold voice, then swept a hand through the air once again, sending the blue crystals flying toward everyone at an alarming speed.

As the crystals hurtled through the air, a ball of black light appeared within each of them, and they swelled rapidly before exploding, sending powerful shockwaves and plumes of acrid, black mist erupting in all directions.

The black mist seemed to be capable of eroding the very space itself, but everyone was already prepared for this, and they immediately sprang back in retreat while adopting defensive measures.

"I can't even remember how many years I've been trapped here, so I'm certainly overdue for some exercise," the devilish being cackled, and as soon as its voice trailed off, the entire cliff collapsed violently.

Giant devilish creatures of all types of descriptions sprang out of the ground before pouncing at Han Li and the others, who weren't able to retreat very far due to the restriction around the mountain.

Hence, they had no choice but to engage the horde of devilish creatures in battle.

With a flick of his wrist, an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword appeared in Han Li's grasp, and he swung it through the air at an oncoming late-High Zenith Stage three-headed falcon.

A bolt of golden lightning erupted out of the sword, forming a golden lightning sword that struck the middle head of the three-headed falcon, but to Han Li's surprise, a burst of radiant, golden light erupted out of the falcon's head to oppose the golden lightning sword, deflecting the attack away.

Immediately thereafter, its two side heads opened their beaks in unison to let loose a shrill shriek, sending two bursts of corkscrew-shaped golden ripples hurtling toward Han Li from either side.

However, the pair of golden corkscrews had only flown around a thousand feet through the air before slowing down drastically, as if they were gliding through treacle.

Han Li had summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis to slow down the oncoming attack, following which he launched himself straight at the three-headed falcon, channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts as he plunged his sword directly into the creature's heart.

A burst of golden lightning erupted out of the sword, and arcs of golden lightning instantly began to pour out of the wound on the three-headed falcon's chest.

At the same time, a burst of silver flames enveloped the creature's entire body.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and in the face of the lethal combination of Han Li's Divine Devilbane Lightning and Flame of Essence, the three-headed falcon was instantly slain.

In contrast with Han Li, who had only been attacked by a single assailant, Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan were currently being harassed by seven or eight High Zenith Stage devilish creatures, all of which seemed to be very much drawn to the blue pouch in Lan Yan's hand.

It immediately occurred to Han Li that just like the golden sword that Xiong Shan had obtained, the blue pouch had also been serving as the core of the array in the blue palace. Hence, it had to have been a treasure of a very high caliber, so it was no wonder that the Lan siblings were being targeted for it.

The combined powers of these devilish creatures far exceeded that of the Lan siblings, who had already severely exerted themselves after unleashing their nascent soul fusion secret technique earlier, so it didn't take long before they were forced firmly onto the back foot.

A hesitant look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and right as he was about to lend them his assistance, Lan Yan suddenly cast an incantation seal into the blue pouch in her hand.

The pouch immediately began to billow violently, and the sound of rumbling thunder rang out as a blue vortex abruptly emerged from it.

The vortex was flashing with lightning, and there seemed to be a water lightning array inside.

At the moment, Lan Yan and Lan Yuanzi were standing with their backs against each other, and the former suddenly tipped the pouch toward the oncoming horde of devilish creatures.

The blue vortex at the mouth of the pouch accelerated drastically in its revolution as seven or eight blue water dragons erupted out from within before hurtling toward the oncoming devilish assailants.

At the same time, Lan Yan's complexion instantly turned deathly pale, a clear sign of immortal spiritual power overexertion.

Han Li couldn't help but be a little alarmed upon seeing this.

Just how high a caliber of an immortal treasure did this blue pouch have to be to have exerted Lan Yan so severely after just a single use?

Furthermore, it seemed like her law power reserves had also been severely depleted in addition to her immortal spiritual power.

With that in mind, it was more than a little suspicious that Xiong Shan was able to wield that Primordial Ancient Sword as a mere late-Golden Immortal cultivator.

Before Han Li had a chance to ponder this matter any further, another devilish creature pounced at him, and he gave a cold harrumph before engaging it in battle.

The blue water dragons were extremely fast, and as they moved through the air, there seemed to be a pervasive barrier of water law powers around them, preventing the devilish creatures from getting away.

Several of the closest devilish creatures weren't in time to take evasive measures, and the water dragons instantly chomped down onto them.

The devilish creatures screeched and struggled frantically, but were unable to free themselves as they were forcibly dragged back toward the blue pouch.

Their bodies shrank down rapidly as they drew closer to the pouch, and ultimately, they had shrunk down to the size of pebbles before being sucked into the pouch.

As soon as the devilish creatures entered the pouch, they were immediately plunged into the water lightning array within, and the blue vortex began to churn violently while giving off bursts of deafening rumbling.

Before long, strings of agonized howls had begun to ring out from within the pouch, but they were only heard for a brief moment before fading into silence, at which point the devilish creatures inside had already been reduced to nothingness.

Using the blue pouch seemed to have sapped Lan Yan of all of her strength, and she immediately collapsed in a feeble manner.

Lan Yuanzi hurriedly caught her, then propped her up before feeding her a pill while taking the blue pouch from her.

The white bone devilish being let loose a loud shriek upon seeing this, and all of the remaining devilish creatures immediately stopped in their tracks before staging a retreat.

The white bone devilish being's gaze lingered on everyone for a moment long, following which it flapped its bone wings and fled with all of its brethren.

After taking a moment to recover their treasures, everyone gathered together, and Lei Yuce's gaze fell upon the blue pouch in Lan Yuanzi's hand with a displeased look on his face, but he ultimately refrained from assigning any blame.

Instead, he cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "The array here has been severely damaged, so it will take some time to repair. In the meantime, all of you can scour the surrounding area to see if there are any other treasures around."

After that, he departed with Wen Zhong to repair the array, not waiting for a response from everyone else.

Lan Yuanzi and Lan Yan immediately sat down with their legs crossed to continue their recovery.

Lan Yan seemed to have exerted herself even more severely than anticipated, and even after taking some pills, she was still very frail and feeble.

Han Li took a glance at the two of them before departing like everyone else to search the nearby area.

However, at this point, the entire cliff had already been destroyed, so no one was able to find anything aside from some water-attribute materials.

Some time later, Lei Yuce and Wen Zhong returned, and the former declared, "The array has been repaired, we can proceed onward now."

He then called out to Su Anqian, and the three of them continued to make their way up the mountain, followed closely by everyone else.

Han Li was just about to follow along when he suddenly seemed to have sensed something, and he turned his gaze to a certain direction as he peered into the distance with a perplexed look on his face.

However, ultimately, he made no attempt to investigate and departed with everyone else.

Chapter 1095: Collaboration

Shortly after the departure of Han Li and the others, the copper lion and the white bone devil emerged from a nearby mountain face amid a flash of white light, while all of the devilish beings were nowhere to be seen.

The two of them were standing next to each other, and it seemed as if they were familiar acquaintances.

"That human must possess tremendous spiritual sense to have almost seen through my Heavenly Bone Ring," the white bone devil remarked as it opened its mouth to release a white ring.

The ring seemed to have been refined from some type of bone, and it was flashing with a gentle, white light. It didn't appear to be remarkable in any way, but it was able to completely contain the auras of the two devilish beings.

"It looks like you've been working hard on refining your Heavenly Bone Ring during all these years in captivity. It's about to become a fifth tier immortal treasure soon, right?" the copper lion remarked.

"There's no devilish qi in that godforsaken place, making it impossible to cultivate, so I had no choice but to focus on refining my devilish treasures," the white bone devil sighed. "I'm assuming your Lightning Nightmare Saber has to be quite a bit more powerful now as well."

A proud look appeared on the copper lion's face upon hearing this, but that was instantly replaced by a look of dismay at the thought of its destroyed Profound Infernal Divine Hammer.

"I had thought that by using your Heavenly Bone Ring, we would be able to sneak over undetected and exact our revenge on Han Li and Xiong Shan, but it looks like the former's spiritual sense is too powerful for that to be a possibility," the copper lion said in an indignant manner.

"Even after all these years, you still haven't changed at all. Have you not heard of the saying that revenge is a dish best served cold?" the white bone devil asked.

"That's a mantra that only the weak subscribe to!" the copper lion harrumphed coldly, while the white bone devil remained silent with a resigned smile.

"By the way, you told me that your law threads were refined by Han Li, is that true? How could your law ring have been refined by him in such a short time?" the white bone devil asked.

"That bastard has a gourd that's most likely an Essential Immortal Treasure, and it possesses an extremely potent refinement ability," the copper lion explained in a hateful voice.

"I see. Essential Immortal Treasures are born from heaven and earth, and they often contain extremely formidable law powers," the white bone devil mused.

"I have to recover my law threads from Han Li no matter what. Even if he used an Essential Immortal Treasure to refine my law threads, it's only been a short time, so the essential aura of those law threads should still be intact. If I can claim his Essential Immortal Treasure, I should be able to recover my law threads," the copper lion said.

"That's all well and good, but the problem is that the two of us on our own are definitely no match for all of them. I've finally been freed after countless years in captivity, and I have no intention of throwing my life away, even if we are brothers!" the white bone devil harrumphed coldly.

"Rest assured, I may not be all that smart, but I'm not an idiot, either. I understand that confronting them now would be a completely suicidal endeavor, but it seems like those people are planning to search for the rest of the array cores on this level.

“Those greedy bastards definitely won't be able to resist the urge to claim the treasures in the array cores, so I say we follow them and give them a hand where necessary. Once all five of us have been freed, we'll be able to take care of those scoundrels with ease!" the copper lion chuckled.

The white bone devil's eyes narrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he offered no response.

"Is there something wrong with my plan?" the copper lion asked in a perplexed manner.

"The plan is sound, but the problem is that freeing our brothers will require the final three array cores to be broken. Once all five cores are broken, the seal will be weakened to the extreme. If the Dark Heavens Devilish Deity is freed, then all of us will most likely be killed. Don't forget that we played a significant role in how he was trapped here in the first place," the white bone devil said in a concerned manner.

"What do we do then? Are we just not going to save our brothers?" the copper lion asked.

The white bone devil was just about to reply when it suddenly swung around and yelled, "Who's sneaking around there?"

Five beams of white light shot out of its fingertips as it spoke, striking the space nearby before exploding violently to reveal a crimson figure enveloped in golden light.

The five bursts of white light didn't dissipate following their explosion, and they transformed into a giant, white bone hand with bright, white flames burning over its surface before grabbing down at the crimson figure.

The crimson figure wasn'ted fazed at all as the golden light around them spread outward in all directions, stopping the white bone hand cold in its tracks before causing it to shatter and dissipate.

......

Meanwhile, Han Li was flying his way up the mountain when he suddenly turned around to look back down in the direction that he had come from with a cold look in his eyes.

"What is it, Brother Han?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"It's nothing," Han Li replied as he continued onward at a faster speed than before.

Wyrm 3's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but she didn't ask any further questions as she also continued flying up the mountain.

......

The white bone devil was quite taken aback to see this, while the copper lion let loose a furious roar as it summoned its black lightning saber, yet it was stopped by the white bone devil before it could attack the crimson figure.

"Your white bone laws have become more formidable than ever, Fellow Daoist White Bone," the crimson figure remarked, and it was none other than Qi Mozi.

Judging from the enormity of his aura, it seemed that his cultivation base had fully recovered.

A cold gleam of recognition flashed through the white bone devil's eyes at the sight of Qi Mozi.

"Do you know this man, Brother?" the copper lion asked.

"This is Fellow Daoist Qi Mozi, formerly the second disciple to Patriarch Miro of the True Mantra Sect, but he later went on to betray his master and join the Heavenly Court," the white bone devil explained with a disdainful sneer.

"So you're the traitor of the True Mantra Sect! I've certainly heard much about you," the copper lion sneered in mock reverence.

"I heard that you made some very significant contributions leading to the downfall of the True Mantra Sect, so you must currently hold a very lofty position in the Heavenly Court, right?" the white bone devil disparaged.

Qi Mozi wasn't ashamed at all as he smiled and replied, "I had tried to dissuade my master from straying from the right path, but to no avail, so I had no choice but to turn to the Heavenly Court. As for my current position in the Heavenly Court, thanks to the infinite graciousness of the Dao Ancestors, I've been made the chief warden of the Immortal Prison."

At the same time, he flipped a hand over to produce a golden, tiger-head-shaped badge, upon which were inscribed the words "chief warden" in antiquated text.

An indescribable aura was emanating from the badge, causing the nearby space to tremble.

The mockery on the white bone devil's face was immediately replaced by a hint of wariness upon seeing this.

The copper lion spat onto the ground, then scoffed, "I've seen countless traitors in my time, but never one as smug and self-assured as you!"

"You must be the vastly renowned Copper Lion King of the Devil Realm, right? I had always heard that you had a very fiery personality. I must say, I hold a great deal of admiration for people like you," Qi Mozi said with a placid smile, still looking completely unbothered.

The copper lion looked as if it had just swallowed a fly in the face of Qi Mozi's praise, and it spat onto the ground once again, but before it could hurl any more insults at Qi Mozi, it was made to stand down by a stern glare from the white bone devil.

"Congratulations on climbing so high up the ranks, Fellow Daoist Qi Mozi. May I ask why you've come here?" the white bone devil asked.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist White Bone, I'm here of my own accord and not under any orders from the Heavenly Court. On top of that, the Immortal Prison is currently a different place from what it once was under me, so you can rest assured that I won't turn on you. Instead, I propose a collaboration," Qi Mozi replied with a smile.

The wariness in the white bone devil's eyes became even more pronounced upon hearing this, and it asked, "What do you mean by that?"

"Judging from your conversation just now, it sounds like you have some personal differences with those people up ahead. Coincidentally, I also have some enemies among them. You and I are old acquaintances, so why don't we join forces against them?" Qi Mozi proposed.

"You want to join forces? I can tell that you've already reached the Great Encompassment Stage, and you're cultivating the laws of time, so what help could you possibly require from the two of us?" the white bone devil asked.

"There are quite a few people in the group up ahead, all of whom are quite formidable. In particular, one of them is extremely troublesome to deal with, and even I am not well equipped to handle him on my own. I'm sure the two of you are already aware of who I'm talking about," Qi Mozi explained with a smile.

An image of Han Li surfaced in the minds of both devilish beings upon hearing this.